{"prompt":"(49 * 4) - (85 * 2)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"99 * (10 - 5)","answer":"495"}
{"prompt":"17 - 9 + 3","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"99 + 2 - 4 - 25","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"44 * 75","answer":"3300"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 5) - 86","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 10) + (28 + 10)","answer":"738"}
{"prompt":"99 * 40 + 9 + 7","answer":"3976"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 9) + 78","answer":"465"}
{"prompt":"19 + 98","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"2 + (23 - 2 + 5)","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 3) * (95 * 6 - 4)","answer":"62826"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 3) * 10 - (74 - 2)","answer":"978"}
{"prompt":"((24 - 6) - 4) + (45 - 2 + 4)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"((64 + 6) * 3) * 39","answer":"8190"}
{"prompt":"57 * (87 * 8)","answer":"39672"}
{"prompt":"25 - (28 * 6) - 6","answer":"-149"}
{"prompt":"((39 * 5) - 8) - (91 - 5)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"10 + (17 * 7) + 1","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"1 + 4 - 94","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"87 + 93","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"((100 + 2) + 10) + 33","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 1 - 9) - (44 * 9)","answer":"-345"}
{"prompt":"19 + 14 * 5 + 1","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"45 + 66","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"8 * 25","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"67 + (49 * 7) + 9","answer":"419"}
{"prompt":"21 - 25","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"85 + 5","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 5) - 2 * 54","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"74 + 50","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"80 - 4 * 8","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 9) + 9) + (74 - 5)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"98 * 73 - 6","answer":"7148"}
{"prompt":"22 + 45","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"76 + 9 + 3","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 10) - (56 + 3)","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 8) - 31","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"84 + 10","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 6) * 13","answer":"1196"}
{"prompt":"65 - 1 * 9 + 45","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"13 - 31","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"83 - 8","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"1 * 16","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"85 - 9 + 8 * 22","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"67 * 95 + 2","answer":"6367"}
{"prompt":"84 * 90","answer":"7560"}
{"prompt":"31 + 9 * 7 * 58 + 4 + 1","answer":"3690"}
{"prompt":"41 + (27 - 4) + 5","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 6) * 67","answer":"3417"}
{"prompt":"88 * 8 - 12","answer":"692"}
{"prompt":"66 * (42 + 10) * 2","answer":"6864"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 9 * 1) - (8 - 7) - 8","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 7) + (86 - 8) * 8","answer":"683"}
{"prompt":"55 + 13 - 10 * 1","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"21 * (100 - 7)","answer":"1953"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 1) * (36 + 4)","answer":"2400"}
{"prompt":"74 + 74 + 8","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 5) - 3 - 87","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"80 + 6 - 5 + 92","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"51 * 71","answer":"3621"}
{"prompt":"26 + 17","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"70 * 56","answer":"3920"}
{"prompt":"31 + 4 + 70","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 8) - 78","answer":"338"}
{"prompt":"20 - 3 * ((4 * 6) + 7)","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 2) - 8 - 14","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"((23 * 1) * 8) * (88 - 5)","answer":"15272"}
{"prompt":"78 * 10 - 7 - 52","answer":"721"}
{"prompt":"76 + 7 * 7 - 37","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 6) - 4 + 52","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 2) - (50 + 5 + 3)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"49 - 96","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 1) + ((38 * 9) * 2)","answer":"780"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 8) * (97 + 5 * 3)","answer":"14336"}
{"prompt":"53 + 8 - 4","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"74 - 8","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"52 - 2 * ((70 * 5) + 10)","answer":"-668"}
{"prompt":"59 + 2","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"43 + 77 + 9","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"87 + 47 * 5 - 4","answer":"318"}
{"prompt":"27 + 64","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"4 - 27 * 9","answer":"-239"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 7) * 7 * (78 * 1)","answer":"118482"}
{"prompt":"100 * 32","answer":"3200"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 1) * 7 - 87","answer":"543"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 2 + 10) - 18 + 3 * 6","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"38 - 39 + 2 + 9","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"47 * 1 + (41 - 4)","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"17 - (28 + 2) - 8","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 6) - 78","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 6 + 6) - 100 + 5","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"29 + 13","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"80 - (78 - 2 + 10)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"1 + 5 * 38","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"54 * 93","answer":"5022"}
{"prompt":"49 + 69 + 7","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 7) + (95 - 4) - 9","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"20 * 28","answer":"560"}
{"prompt":"19 + 1 + 10 - ((59 - 8) - 4)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"32 + 91","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 7 * 1) + ((71 * 3) + 10)","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 8) * (77 - 4)","answer":"49056"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 2 + 8) * (68 + 7)","answer":"5100"}
{"prompt":"((80 + 5) * 1) * (8 * 6) - 4","answer":"4076"}
{"prompt":"49 - (19 - 1)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"13 * 100","answer":"1300"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 1) * 78","answer":"4992"}
{"prompt":"((83 * 4) * 5) + (55 * 7)","answer":"2045"}
{"prompt":"86 * (32 + 5)","answer":"3182"}
{"prompt":"14 + (51 * 1)","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"90 + 99","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"50 + (72 + 4) - 8","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 3) * 3","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 4) * (46 + 8)","answer":"-162"}
{"prompt":"56 + 80","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"53 - (19 + 7 - 4)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"40 * 2 * 2 * 4","answer":"640"}
{"prompt":"39 + 2 * 66","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"31 - 1 + 8 * 7 - 8","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"71 * 94","answer":"6674"}
{"prompt":"88 - 7 * 4 + (23 - 4) - 2","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"((91 + 5) - 6) * 25","answer":"2250"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 10) + (66 * 2)","answer":"224"}
{"prompt":"27 * 10 * 10 * (48 + 8 - 2)","answer":"145800"}
{"prompt":"23 - 29","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 1 + 6) - ((85 - 2) * 8)","answer":"-601"}
{"prompt":"81 * 4 - 54","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"62 * 1 - 85 * 7","answer":"-533"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 4 + 4) * (28 - 7) * 7","answer":"9849"}
{"prompt":"77 * 43","answer":"3311"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 4) + (51 + 9)","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"((46 - 3) + 3) * 84","answer":"3864"}
{"prompt":"81 - 75","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"40 - 3 * 79","answer":"-197"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 1) * (46 + 3)","answer":"3087"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 7 - 5) * 61 - 6","answer":"3227"}
{"prompt":"93 * 93 + 10 * 6","answer":"8709"}
{"prompt":"83 + 4","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"((58 + 6) + 6) + 94 + 9 + 1","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"90 + 59 - 8","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"19 + 3 + 8 - (8 * 8) * 1","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 2) - 92 * 5","answer":"-444"}
{"prompt":"86 * 9 * 44","answer":"34056"}
{"prompt":"50 * (71 - 10)","answer":"3050"}
{"prompt":"12 + 16","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"19 * 5 - 1 + 88","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"9 + 77 + 8","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 4) - 35 - 9 + 5","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"92 * 75","answer":"6900"}
{"prompt":"59 * (24 + 7) - 1","answer":"1828"}
{"prompt":"77 + (31 - 8)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 4) - ((55 + 2) + 10)","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"97 + 3 - 4","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"43 - 4 * 15","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"50 * 14 - 5","answer":"695"}
{"prompt":"((47 - 10) + 8) * 1","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"((32 * 6) - 9) - 38","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"91 - 50","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"14 - 1 + 1 * 5","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 4) * 10 + 6","answer":"2046"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 8 - 2) * (58 * 6) * 9","answer":"68904"}
{"prompt":"(22 - 7) * (48 * 1) * 7","answer":"5040"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 2 + 1) - (90 * 5 + 7)","answer":"-344"}
{"prompt":"44 * 32","answer":"1408"}
{"prompt":"17 - (84 + 4)","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"45 + 30","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"44 - 55","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"((19 + 3) - 2) + 96","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"34 - (49 - 2) + 5","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"35 + 7 + (69 * 8 - 5)","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"97 - 7 - (38 - 4)","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"100 * 41","answer":"4100"}
{"prompt":"93 + ((6 * 9) * 6)","answer":"417"}
{"prompt":"12 + 62 - 9 - 2","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 4 - 4) - 69 - 1","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"31 * 9 * 77","answer":"21483"}
{"prompt":"2 + 81","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"99 * 21","answer":"2079"}
{"prompt":"96 - 5 * 36","answer":"-84"}
{"prompt":"32 - 91","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 8 + 7) + 56","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"13 * 29","answer":"377"}
{"prompt":"7 * 3 - 2","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 8) - 59","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"49 + 89","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"62 + 10","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"66 - (46 * 1)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 2) - 18","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"((94 - 3) * 2) - (5 * 10)","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"63 + 38 * 4 + 7","answer":"222"}
{"prompt":"((11 + 1) * 10) + 75 + 2","answer":"197"}
{"prompt":"30 - 61 * 8 * 6","answer":"-2898"}
{"prompt":"((59 + 3) + 5) * (24 - 4)","answer":"1340"}
{"prompt":"71 + 74","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"((74 - 1) + 8) - 21","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"16 * (97 + 6)","answer":"1648"}
{"prompt":"57 * 43 + 2","answer":"2453"}
{"prompt":"34 - 77","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"86 - 8 - 87 + 9","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"28 * 2 * 99 - 10 * 8","answer":"5464"}
{"prompt":"88 - (78 * 2) - 10","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"45 - 84 + 5","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"38 * 21","answer":"798"}
{"prompt":"11 * (33 + 10)","answer":"473"}
{"prompt":"52 - (5 - 6 + 4)","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"4 - (56 - 5) * 6","answer":"-302"}
{"prompt":"50 * 5 * (59 - 3 * 3)","answer":"12500"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 6) * 97 * 7","answer":"16296"}
{"prompt":"2 + 7 + 39","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"41 - 6 + (6 - 8)","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"43 - 8 - 89","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"98 * 24 - 10 * 6","answer":"2292"}
{"prompt":"79 + 7","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"23 + 10 * (53 + 3)","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"74 + 56","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"57 * 6 + 8 - (13 * 9)","answer":"233"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 2) + 99","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 6 + 1) + (92 * 9) - 7","answer":"898"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 9) - 82","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"47 + (19 + 6)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 4 - 5) * (5 * 4)","answer":"6620"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 5) * (100 + 7)","answer":"37450"}
{"prompt":"4 * 44 + 9 - 6","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"64 - 41","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"42 - 10 * 85 * 8","answer":"-6758"}
{"prompt":"70 + 2 + 4 + (38 * 7 + 1)","answer":"343"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 10 + 2) - 100 - 5","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"45 * (23 + 7) - 4","answer":"1346"}
{"prompt":"45 * (100 - 10)","answer":"4050"}
{"prompt":"29 + 4 - 84","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 1) * (45 * 9) + 6","answer":"15396"}
{"prompt":"17 + 14","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"47 * (83 * 10 * 9)","answer":"351090"}
{"prompt":"11 - 3 * 7 - (42 + 4)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 9) - ((10 - 10) * 1)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"71 + ((7 - 4) * 5)","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"70 * 95","answer":"6650"}
{"prompt":"16 * 72 + 8","answer":"1160"}
{"prompt":"30 + (1 * 4) + 8","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 4) - 8 + 67 - 10 + 3","answer":"368"}
{"prompt":"68 + 14","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"87 * 6 - (36 * 9)","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"65 * 90","answer":"5850"}
{"prompt":"47 * 49 + 3","answer":"2306"}
{"prompt":"((21 * 10) * 7) * (85 - 6)","answer":"116130"}
{"prompt":"74 + 86 - 1","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"20 - 61","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"50 + (60 - 3 + 1)","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"14 - 1 * 2","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"84 - 1 * 40","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 5) - 1 * ((15 - 5) + 5)","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"63 + 58 * 5","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"43 + 91 - 3","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"54 + 6 + 4 * 91","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"84 - 99 - 3","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"76 * (31 * 5)","answer":"11780"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 9) * ((5 + 8) * 2)","answer":"8892"}
{"prompt":"50 + 48","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 8) + 1 + 68","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"42 * 1","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"48 + 52","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"15 + 59","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 10) + (84 + 9 + 3)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 1 - 9) * 25","answer":"275"}
{"prompt":"29 - (13 * 10) * 5","answer":"-621"}
{"prompt":"98 + 97","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"27 + 68","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"65 + (50 * 6) - 3","answer":"362"}
{"prompt":"56 * 55","answer":"3080"}
{"prompt":"((20 - 7) + 6) + 44","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"13 * 6 * 18","answer":"1404"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 1 + 4) - 50 + 8","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 6) - 89","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"37 + 4 - 7 - 55","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"19 + 40","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 2) + 5 * 56","answer":"356"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 8) * 1 - 28 + 6","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"59 + 44","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"10 + 12 * 7 * 7","answer":"598"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 10 - 2) * 59 - 7","answer":"3002"}
{"prompt":"69 + 96 * 8","answer":"837"}
{"prompt":"44 + 8 + 7 - 62","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"14 - 23","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"((42 * 2) - 8) + 80","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 7) * 86","answer":"3784"}
{"prompt":"48 - ((51 - 2) * 7)","answer":"-295"}
{"prompt":"39 - 5 - 4 + 85","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"40 + 8 - 10 - 94","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 8) + (65 + 5 - 8)","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"66 * 7 - (46 - 10)","answer":"426"}
{"prompt":"45 + (18 + 6 * 4)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"55 - 1 + 5 + 48 * 2","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"2 - 39","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 7) - 41","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"75 + 4 - 9 * 86","answer":"-695"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 10) * 68","answer":"4080"}
{"prompt":"31 * 10 + 80 - 6 * 1","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"1 + 12","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"2 + 2 + 4 * ((24 + 5) * 1)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 10 + 9) - 65","answer":"614"}
{"prompt":"14 * 57","answer":"798"}
{"prompt":"46 - 9 - ((84 * 3) + 3)","answer":"-218"}
{"prompt":"13 - 5 * 5 * (54 + 1)","answer":"-1362"}
{"prompt":"81 * 76 - 2","answer":"6154"}
{"prompt":"55 - ((19 * 6) + 3)","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 8) - (4 - 6)","answer":"730"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 10) * 10 * 1","answer":"300"}
{"prompt":"73 - 75","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"8 + 2 * 8 - 43","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 5 * 5) + 28","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"56 - (56 + 2 * 9)","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"100 + 8 + 8 - ((32 - 9) + 4)","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"50 * 7 + 98","answer":"448"}
{"prompt":"46 - 3 + 62 - 1 + 5","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"40 - 3","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 9) - 56","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"58 + 44","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"96 - 49","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 5) + 3 - 75 * 9","answer":"-591"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 4) * 24","answer":"1320"}
{"prompt":"1 - 10 - 60","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"14 + (18 + 5 + 10)","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"78 * 4 - 26 * 8","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"30 * (28 * 7)","answer":"5880"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 3 - 3) * (30 * 3 - 6)","answer":"18648"}
{"prompt":"((19 - 9) - 10) + 55","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 6 * 2) * 10","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"97 * 36","answer":"3492"}
{"prompt":"((53 - 1) + 1) * 11","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"((34 * 6) + 7) - 23","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"25 * 37","answer":"925"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 5) * 9 - 36","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 8) + 5 + 47 * 6","answer":"295"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 6 - 6) - 51","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"80 + 65 * 7","answer":"535"}
{"prompt":"69 - 74","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 3) + 40","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"81 + (89 - 2)","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 8 * 4) * 28 - 4","answer":"23292"}
{"prompt":"18 - (79 - 9) - 7","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"7 + 3 * 2 - (52 - 2) + 2","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"28 * 12","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"80 - 9 * 53","answer":"-397"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 5 - 9) * 21","answer":"1176"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 1) + 41","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"91 - 57 - 1","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"44 + 4 + 45 * 8","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"84 - 95","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"35 + 40","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 7) - 10 + 5","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 4) * (5 * 4) + 4","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 9) - 7 - 65 + 1 * 3","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"7 * 69","answer":"483"}
{"prompt":"59 * 79","answer":"4661"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 2) + 2 + (74 * 10)","answer":"758"}
{"prompt":"25 * 2 + 20","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 8) + (26 + 3)","answer":"725"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 4) * (72 - 3) - 5","answer":"3583"}
{"prompt":"49 + 53 * 1","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"90 + 5 - 2 + (53 + 1 + 4)","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"37 - (68 * 3)","answer":"-167"}
{"prompt":"23 * (19 * 4)","answer":"1748"}
{"prompt":"(86 + 8) * 7 * 27","answer":"17766"}
{"prompt":"10 + (72 - 2 * 10)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"56 - 97","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 4) + 16","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"4 - 98","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"76 * 12","answer":"912"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 5) - 6 - 36","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"83 * 41","answer":"3403"}
{"prompt":"61 - (71 + 8 - 1)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(90 + 4) + (89 + 7) * 10","answer":"1054"}
{"prompt":"87 + 63","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"65 + 8 + 53","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 4) - 10","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"9 * ((66 + 9) - 9)","answer":"594"}
{"prompt":"85 + 30","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"31 - 66","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"100 + 46 + 2","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"45 - 37","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 5) + 9","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"57 - 68","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"83 - 95 - 2","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"59 * 3 - 99","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"96 - 1 - 8 - 72 * 2 * 8","answer":"-1065"}
{"prompt":"24 * 38","answer":"912"}
{"prompt":"72 * 4 + 9 - (19 * 4) - 6","answer":"215"}
{"prompt":"51 * 26","answer":"1326"}
{"prompt":"88 * 5 * 36 * 3 + 6","answer":"47526"}
{"prompt":"72 + 21","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 6) + 8 * 78 + 3","answer":"909"}
{"prompt":"96 + 88 * 6","answer":"624"}
{"prompt":"85 * 32","answer":"2720"}
{"prompt":"((43 + 5) - 8) + 48","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"((85 * 2) + 5) + ((37 - 7) - 3)","answer":"202"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 6) * 5","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 5) * 4 * 95","answer":"31160"}
{"prompt":"35 * ((33 - 5) - 10)","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 3) + 38","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"30 + 51 + 4","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"75 + 56","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 3) * 7 - 94","answer":"704"}
{"prompt":"92 + 41","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"64 + 8 * 69 - 6 * 10","answer":"556"}
{"prompt":"87 - (11 - 10 * 2)","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"40 * ((89 * 8) + 9)","answer":"28840"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 6) * 8) - 60 - 1","answer":"755"}
{"prompt":"84 + (9 - 4)","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"22 + (87 * 9)","answer":"805"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 10 + 10) + 33","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"96 + 2 + 77","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"3 * ((96 * 1) + 3)","answer":"297"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 5) - ((37 + 5) + 2)","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 4) - 67","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"95 - 47","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 3) * (48 - 7)","answer":"1927"}
{"prompt":"62 - 5","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"92 - 5 + 6 * 18 * 7 * 9","answer":"6891"}
{"prompt":"80 - 5 + 10 - 29 + 9","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"8 * 41","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"49 * 14 - 8","answer":"678"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 9) - 87","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"29 * 95","answer":"2755"}
{"prompt":"(22 - 6) - (22 - 7)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"34 - 6 - 59","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 7 + 8) - 33 * 6","answer":"-134"}
{"prompt":"36 - (5 + 8)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"73 - 10 * 96","answer":"-887"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 4) - 6) + 69 + 5","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"20 + 5 - 3","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 7) + 46","answer":"333"}
{"prompt":"((54 - 1) + 8) * 81","answer":"4941"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 6) - 5","answer":"295"}
{"prompt":"37 + 2 + 9 * 8","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"60 - (6 + 10 - 6)","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"((83 + 5) + 1) - 18","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"43 + 92 * 10","answer":"963"}
{"prompt":"64 * (59 * 6 - 4)","answer":"22400"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 5 * 5) + 42","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"57 - (96 + 6)","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"36 - 4 - 57","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"32 * ((67 + 9) * 6)","answer":"14592"}
{"prompt":"71 * 97","answer":"6887"}
{"prompt":"83 - 10 * 6","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"100 - 69 * 4 - 4","answer":"-180"}
{"prompt":"33 - 53","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"((92 - 4) + 10) + 60","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 1) + 64","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"6 + 1","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"71 - 82","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"43 - 15","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 7) * (95 - 5)","answer":"17640"}
{"prompt":"21 - 10 + ((66 + 6) + 8)","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"67 + 10 + 4 - ((25 + 2) + 1)","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"((65 + 3) + 5) * 75","answer":"5475"}
{"prompt":"50 + 3 * 43","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"13 + 75","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"35 * 3","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"88 * ((68 * 3) * 6)","answer":"107712"}
{"prompt":"36 * 5 + 14","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"35 + (15 - 3) * 6","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"52 - 10 * 63 + 9","answer":"-569"}
{"prompt":"67 - (31 + 7)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"50 * (30 - 10) - 1","answer":"999"}
{"prompt":"42 - 74","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"16 * 6 + ((89 * 2) - 9)","answer":"265"}
{"prompt":"51 + 65","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"34 * 40","answer":"1360"}
{"prompt":"24 - 1","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"8 + 9 * 2 + 2","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 4 * 8) + 31","answer":"1823"}
{"prompt":"69 * (27 + 8 + 4)","answer":"2691"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 8 + 5) + 3","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 9) * 9) - (30 * 9)","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"((33 * 9) * 6) * 8 * 8 * 6","answer":"684288"}
{"prompt":"((22 - 3) + 1) * 94","answer":"1880"}
{"prompt":"15 - 48 + 1","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"8 * 4 - (67 + 10)","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"92 * (86 + 4)","answer":"8280"}
{"prompt":"70 + 5 - 32","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"3 + 86","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"39 - 64","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"7 - (90 * 9)","answer":"-803"}
{"prompt":"33 * 84","answer":"2772"}
{"prompt":"(44 * 6) + 51","answer":"315"}
{"prompt":"84 * 4 * 8 * 26 - 8","answer":"69880"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 5) - 3 + ((84 * 2) * 4)","answer":"1039"}
{"prompt":"61 - (51 - 5)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"92 - ((76 - 6) + 8)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 6) - 18","answer":"342"}
{"prompt":"96 + (72 + 4)","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"22 * 50","answer":"1100"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 9) + (19 * 5 + 5)","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"12 + 2 + 100","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"50 - 15","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 3) * (97 - 6 - 7)","answer":"4872"}
{"prompt":"59 + 1 * 88","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"((48 + 10) * 5) * 3 + 10","answer":"880"}
{"prompt":"53 * 7 - 39","answer":"332"}
{"prompt":"14 + 52 + 8","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"2 + 96","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"60 - 4 * 94","answer":"-316"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 8) * 39","answer":"19656"}
{"prompt":"23 - 6","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"26 - (60 - 1) * 9","answer":"-505"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 9) * (93 * 7)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"27 + 43","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"44 - 93","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 4) * 4) - (54 - 8 * 6)","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"89 * (44 - 8)","answer":"3204"}
{"prompt":"24 + (62 * 4)","answer":"272"}
{"prompt":"74 + 9 - 17","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"5 + (76 + 6 + 3)","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"81 * 32","answer":"2592"}
{"prompt":"67 + (71 + 5)","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 6) + 94","answer":"460"}
{"prompt":"74 * 5 - 25","answer":"345"}
{"prompt":"49 * 4 + 20","answer":"216"}
{"prompt":"((37 + 2) - 10) - 32","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"50 + 68","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"85 + 62","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 1 * 7) + (76 + 5)","answer":"613"}
{"prompt":"5 - 35","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"((93 * 4) + 7) * 27","answer":"10233"}
{"prompt":"53 * ((7 + 2) - 4)","answer":"265"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 4) - 8 - 56 * 4","answer":"-221"}
{"prompt":"44 * 80","answer":"3520"}
{"prompt":"4 * 80","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 8 - 9) * 49","answer":"10535"}
{"prompt":"17 * 1","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"96 - (91 - 8)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"98 * 1","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"93 + 8 - 9 - 88","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"22 + 100","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 3) * 47","answer":"4700"}
{"prompt":"100 * 96 - 2","answer":"9598"}
{"prompt":"87 + (24 * 1)","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"76 * 9 - 1 - 34","answer":"649"}
{"prompt":"((42 * 6) + 4) + 24","answer":"280"}
{"prompt":"19 * 20","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"78 * 9 + 43 * 9","answer":"1089"}
{"prompt":"90 - 82 - 9 + 3","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 5) * ((45 * 1) * 5)","answer":"14175"}
{"prompt":"30 * 83","answer":"2490"}
{"prompt":"94 + 71","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"69 * (46 * 2 - 2)","answer":"6210"}
{"prompt":"75 * (1 * 2 + 5)","answer":"525"}
{"prompt":"72 * (95 - 4)","answer":"6552"}
{"prompt":"90 - (68 + 9)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"50 + 99","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"24 + 22","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 4 + 9) * (23 - 1 * 9)","answer":"3094"}
{"prompt":"76 - 52","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"2 * 21","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 10) - 72 * 9","answer":"-588"}
{"prompt":"84 + 8 * 5","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"8 * (89 * 6)","answer":"4272"}
{"prompt":"69 - 9 * 1 + 75","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"69 * 2 * 10 - (44 - 9)","answer":"1345"}
{"prompt":"3 + 3 * 32","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"84 + 81","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"36 - 61 + 9","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"45 - 90 - 6","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"91 - (73 + 8)","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"48 * 2 * 3 + 4","answer":"292"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 6) - 10 * 74 + 10","answer":"-268"}
{"prompt":"(68 * 6 * 2) + 83 - 3","answer":"896"}
{"prompt":"56 - (43 * 7 - 1)","answer":"-244"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 3) - 9 - 40","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"54 + (51 * 7 + 3)","answer":"414"}
{"prompt":"60 - (37 + 7 * 8)","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 2) * (77 - 2)","answer":"8100"}
{"prompt":"49 + 75","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 3) + (91 * 1)","answer":"259"}
{"prompt":"81 * 10","answer":"810"}
{"prompt":"56 + 9 + 3 + 5 + 4","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 9) + 32 * 9 - 1","answer":"701"}
{"prompt":"44 - 66","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"81 - (100 - 2)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"81 * (26 - 5)","answer":"1701"}
{"prompt":"65 * 9 + (58 + 7)","answer":"650"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 8) + (10 - 10)","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"43 - (96 - 9) * 4","answer":"-305"}
{"prompt":"94 + (61 + 7)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"6 - (65 - 9)","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"15 - 8 - (36 + 3) - 5","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"23 * 8 - 8 - 94","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"21 * 18","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"9 * 7 + 48","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"41 + 85","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 7) * 33","answer":"1056"}
{"prompt":"24 - 90 + 5 * 1","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 8) * 77","answer":"38808"}
{"prompt":"2 - 61","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 4 * 8) - (73 + 4)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"69 + 63","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(10 - 7) * (49 - 6) * 9","answer":"1161"}
{"prompt":"61 - (90 + 7)","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"13 + 3 * 1 - 31 * 6","answer":"-170"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 4) + 10 - (90 * 9 * 8)","answer":"-6434"}
{"prompt":"33 + (19 * 5)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"8 * 38","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"17 + 16 * 5","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"76 - 7 * 7 - 96","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 5 - 2) + 10 * 4 + 8","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"28 * 50","answer":"1400"}
{"prompt":"68 + 2 + (3 + 7)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 2) + 43","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"21 * 10 + 9 * 55","answer":"705"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 3) - 57","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 1) * 77","answer":"3927"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 3) * (24 * 4)","answer":"8544"}
{"prompt":"4 - (7 - 5) + 5","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"92 - 71","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 9) - 4 - 62","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 3) + (56 - 1)","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"36 - 13 * 10","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 4 - 6) * 47","answer":"3337"}
{"prompt":"(66 * 3) * 48 + 7","answer":"9511"}
{"prompt":"46 * 3 + 87","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"((48 + 8) * 9) * (10 - 3 * 3)","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 8) - 64 * 7","answer":"-362"}
{"prompt":"16 * 51 + 3","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"49 * (6 + 2)","answer":"392"}
{"prompt":"3 * 5 + 1 + 5","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"5 + 8 - 99 - 3","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"5 + 6 - 6 - 11","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"12 + 1 + 6 * (7 - 9)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"14 * 69","answer":"966"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 8) + 2 + 93 - 7","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"91 - 10 * 54 + 5","answer":"-444"}
{"prompt":"((26 + 7) - 10) + 21","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"35 + 10 - 10 * 82","answer":"-775"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 1) + 26","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"31 * 90 - 7","answer":"2783"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 7) * ((45 - 1) - 3)","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"8 + (87 - 1) + 8","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 10) + 8 + 81 - 8","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 1) - 4 + 22","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 7) - 53","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 4) + 55","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 1) + 57","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 8) * 29","answer":"19720"}
{"prompt":"66 + 70","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 10 * 1) * 19","answer":"1121"}
{"prompt":"83 + 57","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"94 + 51","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(75 - 2 * 5) + 83","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"7 * (86 - 2)","answer":"588"}
{"prompt":"57 + 53","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 5) - 62","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"47 * ((20 + 5) + 7)","answer":"1504"}
{"prompt":"8 * ((4 + 10) - 2)","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"28 * 30","answer":"840"}
{"prompt":"8 + 99","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"77 - 89 + 4","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"80 - 88","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"15 - 36","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 4) + 3 * 5 * 1","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"88 - 54","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"75 - 10 - 8 - 17","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 10) * 9 - 88","answer":"893"}
{"prompt":"53 - (53 - 9) + 10","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"70 + 81","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"((55 + 5) * 10) + ((60 * 6) + 5)","answer":"965"}
{"prompt":"96 * 1 - 4 + 75 * 7","answer":"617"}
{"prompt":"18 - 22 + 8","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"72 * 2 + 13","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"1 * 72","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 7) * 98","answer":"49392"}
{"prompt":"25 + (57 * 1) * 1","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 4) * 10 + 15","answer":"695"}
{"prompt":"((49 + 3) + 6) * 38 * 6","answer":"13224"}
{"prompt":"77 + 10 + 68","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 9) * 1 * 15","answer":"1005"}
{"prompt":"((70 + 9) * 3) - (42 + 2)","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"83 - 77","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 5) * 72","answer":"1872"}
{"prompt":"12 - ((1 + 6) - 8)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"54 - 52","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(33 - 1) - 4 * 9 * 5","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"27 - 10 * 1 * 58 * 8 - 1","answer":"-4614"}
{"prompt":"55 * 9 + 18","answer":"513"}
{"prompt":"46 - 49","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"34 * 15","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"53 * 19","answer":"1007"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 7 - 10) - 94","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 9) * 28","answer":"1848"}
{"prompt":"51 + 53 + 9 * 8","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 7) - 45","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"6 - 21","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"100 - 95 + 4","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"69 - 1 - 4 - (6 - 6) - 9","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 6) + 3 + (42 + 4)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"60 * 6 * 5 * 4","answer":"7200"}
{"prompt":"57 - 6 * 58 - 3","answer":"-294"}
{"prompt":"67 * 3","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"29 * 80","answer":"2320"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 3) - (40 * 5 + 1)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 7) * 10) + ((50 * 8) * 10)","answer":"5680"}
{"prompt":"33 - 8","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"31 - 39 * 2 - 7","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"75 * (20 + 6) * 4","answer":"7800"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 6) * 3 * (51 * 4)","answer":"88128"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 10) + 2 - 6","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"((48 * 8) - 4) * 72","answer":"27360"}
{"prompt":"45 + (43 + 8 + 10)","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"92 * 2 + 15","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"26 + 22","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"39 - 85","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"12 * 4 + (10 - 3)","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"2 * (22 - 6 * 3)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"45 - 26 * 6","answer":"-111"}
{"prompt":"48 * 17","answer":"816"}
{"prompt":"11 - 3 + (3 - 2) + 10","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(86 * 6) * (7 * 9)","answer":"32508"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 3) * 1 * (10 + 2) * 9","answer":"18468"}
{"prompt":"68 + 94","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"96 * 3 + 2 + 46","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"2 * 4 - (91 - 2)","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"((54 - 4) + 3) + 45","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"50 - ((68 + 5) + 6)","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"56 * 24","answer":"1344"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 5) * 57","answer":"25080"}
{"prompt":"73 + 37 * 7 * 9","answer":"2404"}
{"prompt":"14 * 9 + 85","answer":"211"}
{"prompt":"68 + 6 * 29","answer":"242"}
{"prompt":"2 + 7 + 28","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"74 - (41 * 9)","answer":"-295"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 5) * ((78 * 9) - 10)","answer":"20760"}
{"prompt":"((41 * 10) * 6) + (72 * 9)","answer":"3108"}
{"prompt":"62 - 7 + 60 * 10","answer":"655"}
{"prompt":"47 - 32","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 8) - 10 + 40","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 5) - 4 * (77 - 1)","answer":"-159"}
{"prompt":"8 * 1 * 9 * 86 * 10","answer":"61920"}
{"prompt":"((44 + 9) - 2) * 100","answer":"5100"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 1 * 2) * 87","answer":"12528"}
{"prompt":"97 + 24 - 7","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"86 + 81 + 2","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"47 * 65","answer":"3055"}
{"prompt":"14 * 36 - 5 - 6","answer":"493"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 8) - 1 + 59","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"66 * 31","answer":"2046"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 8) + 79 + 2","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"83 * 23 * 6","answer":"11454"}
{"prompt":"19 * 67","answer":"1273"}
{"prompt":"92 + 38","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 10) + 46","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"80 - 64","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 1) - 10 * 91","answer":"-891"}
{"prompt":"84 - 3 + ((81 + 5) + 2)","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 6 - 3) - 15 - 8 + 3","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"99 - 3 - 40 + 10 + 10","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"39 * 6 * 72 * 4","answer":"67392"}
{"prompt":"58 - 6","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"25 - (30 * 1 * 8)","answer":"-215"}
{"prompt":"86 - 1 + 34","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"90 - 98","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"25 * (39 + 1)","answer":"1000"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 7) * 1","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"71 - 7 + 51","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 4) + (89 * 2)","answer":"534"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 8) * 5 * 87","answer":"25230"}
{"prompt":"47 - (99 - 4)","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 6 * 6) * 20","answer":"1720"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 7) * 8 - (20 - 1)","answer":"549"}
{"prompt":"34 + 46 + 6 * 1","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"99 - 39 + 5","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"98 + (90 - 8)","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"86 - 92","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"93 - ((9 * 8) + 10)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 6) - ((60 * 4) * 8)","answer":"-1911"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 5) * 6 - 56","answer":"316"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 2 - 9) - (15 * 4)","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 9) - ((88 + 10) * 6)","answer":"-571"}
{"prompt":"(62 - 2) * 59 + 3","answer":"3543"}
{"prompt":"75 - 66","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"88 * 1 - 2 - 5 + 9","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"93 - 92","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"26 + 2 - 3 + ((6 - 3) - 2)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"84 + (68 + 9) - 8","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 2 + 3) * (39 + 9) - 8","answer":"856"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 9 * 5) + 93","answer":"2928"}
{"prompt":"3 - 71","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"15 + 61","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"28 + 96","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 2) * 8 * 4 * 7 + 1","answer":"14785"}
{"prompt":"((10 * 9) - 8) + (50 * 5 * 9)","answer":"2332"}
{"prompt":"57 + (24 * 3)","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"((40 - 10) - 6) - (41 * 3)","answer":"-99"}
{"prompt":"26 - 35","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"20 - 10 + 8 * 10","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(77 - 10) * (100 - 2)","answer":"6566"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 5) * 51 - 6","answer":"11724"}
{"prompt":"72 + 7 - 8","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"((2 * 8) - 9) + 90","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"12 * 5 + 7 + ((21 * 4) + 6)","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"4 * (15 * 4)","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"84 * 5 - 98","answer":"322"}
{"prompt":"((76 - 1) - 1) - 71","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"67 * ((11 - 9) + 5)","answer":"469"}
{"prompt":"24 + 79 + 5","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"76 + 9 - ((9 + 7) - 5)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 7 * 5) - (33 + 3) + 6","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 9) + 1 * 9 - 1 - 3","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"27 * 7 + 8 + 28","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"60 * 8","answer":"480"}
{"prompt":"73 + 11","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"85 * (94 * 1)","answer":"7990"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 9) + 7 * (19 - 10)","answer":"927"}
{"prompt":"91 - (60 - 9) * 8","answer":"-317"}
{"prompt":"88 + 10 * 32","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"((43 * 6) + 5) * 68 - 4 * 9","answer":"17848"}
{"prompt":"15 + 48","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 5) * 22 + 5","answer":"2535"}
{"prompt":"50 + (78 - 2)","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"79 - 2 - 7 - (72 - 9 - 1)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"60 * 27","answer":"1620"}
{"prompt":"51 + ((79 * 6) + 4)","answer":"529"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 9) * 8 + 82 + 9","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"72 - 77","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"69 + 14 - 9","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"84 - 18","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"42 * ((91 + 9) + 10)","answer":"4620"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 4) * (11 - 9) + 8","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"68 * (2 * 2 * 2)","answer":"544"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 7) - (32 * 8)","answer":"-199"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 4 + 2) - (19 + 4)","answer":"379"}
{"prompt":"11 + (70 * 10 * 9)","answer":"6311"}
{"prompt":"39 * 7 + 5","answer":"278"}
{"prompt":"50 + 9 - 93","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"5 + 53","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 5) + 6","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 7 * 5) + (51 + 7)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"30 * 10","answer":"300"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 2) + (94 - 10)","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(77 - 4 * 10) - 72 - 5","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 7) + 3) * 64","answer":"10944"}
{"prompt":"((13 - 5) + 8) * 33 * 2 + 5","answer":"1061"}
{"prompt":"9 - 73","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"82 + 72","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 9) * 88","answer":"9416"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 6 * 8) + 75","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"((27 + 8) - 5) + 19","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"28 * (51 * 1)","answer":"1428"}
{"prompt":"9 + 1 + 52","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"30 * 39","answer":"1170"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 4) * 60","answer":"3240"}
{"prompt":"74 - 36","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"11 - 25","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 10) * 48","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"((72 - 1) - 2) + 45 + 4 + 5","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"35 * 50 + 2 * 10","answer":"1770"}
{"prompt":"63 + 4 - 37","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"63 - (26 + 6)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"92 + (98 + 7)","answer":"197"}
{"prompt":"100 - 87 * 9","answer":"-683"}
{"prompt":"5 + (15 - 6)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 7) + 78","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"23 + 9 + 6 * 28 * 1 * 1","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"38 + (66 - 2)","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"((8 + 9) - 7) * (94 - 9 - 4)","answer":"810"}
{"prompt":"70 + 100","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 2 - 1) - ((73 * 10) * 4)","answer":"-2851"}
{"prompt":"97 + 76","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 8 - 7) - (71 - 5)","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 3) * 3 - 30 * 4","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 6) * 15","answer":"900"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 1) + 7 * 44","answer":"354"}
{"prompt":"36 - 60","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 3) + 47 + 2","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"27 - 4 - 17","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"18 * 3 - (21 - 7 * 4)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"84 * 3 * 43","answer":"10836"}
{"prompt":"51 + 1 - 6 + (81 * 10)","answer":"856"}
{"prompt":"52 * (29 + 2)","answer":"1612"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 2) + 76","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 3) * 10 + (72 * 1) + 10","answer":"562"}
{"prompt":"19 * 3 + 80 + 1","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 8) + 34","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"7 + 70","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"46 * 51","answer":"2346"}
{"prompt":"55 - 43 + 6","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"87 - (41 + 10)","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"16 + 3 * 8 - (65 * 1 + 4)","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"94 - 59","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"59 + 10 + 8 - 94","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"9 + 49","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"44 - (49 - 8)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"((38 * 1) * 4) + 76","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 4) - 53 * 6","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"89 * 24","answer":"2136"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 4) + 28","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"66 * 50","answer":"3300"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 10) + 27","answer":"457"}
{"prompt":"8 * (56 + 9)","answer":"520"}
{"prompt":"68 * 80 - 5","answer":"5435"}
{"prompt":"25 + 19","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 8) * 49","answer":"21560"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 8 * 3) + (62 * 2)","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 5) - 49 + 1","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 10) + 2 * 79","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"50 + 50","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"62 + ((65 - 10) * 8)","answer":"502"}
{"prompt":"88 + 14","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"99 - 3 - 53 + 8 - 10","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"40 * 63","answer":"2520"}
{"prompt":"71 * 43","answer":"3053"}
{"prompt":"54 * 17 + 6 * 7","answer":"960"}
{"prompt":"41 + 10 - 6 * 96","answer":"-525"}
{"prompt":"44 * (16 * 8) + 4","answer":"5636"}
{"prompt":"96 * 34","answer":"3264"}
{"prompt":"78 + 74","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"58 * 32","answer":"1856"}
{"prompt":"71 - 28","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"55 + (65 * 9)","answer":"640"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 4) - 6","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 3 + 4) - (31 - 10)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"65 * (79 * 8)","answer":"41080"}
{"prompt":"((42 * 9) * 5) * ((88 - 5) + 4)","answer":"164430"}
{"prompt":"90 * 9 - 7 + 2 - 4 + 3","answer":"804"}
{"prompt":"89 + 9 + (87 + 10)","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"60 + (77 - 4) - 7","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"76 + (79 - 1 + 5)","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"79 * 53","answer":"4187"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 4) - 28","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"62 - 46 - 4","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 2) + (19 + 8)","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"47 + ((92 * 5) * 8)","answer":"3727"}
{"prompt":"51 + 10 - 65","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"9 + ((70 * 7) + 10)","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"43 - 80 + 10 - 1","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 4) * 88","answer":"10560"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 7) + 7 + 20","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"35 * 57","answer":"1995"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 10) * (22 * 4 + 5)","answer":"-651"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 4) * 28","answer":"1904"}
{"prompt":"73 - (95 * 10)","answer":"-877"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 7) * (22 - 1)","answer":"2163"}
{"prompt":"9 - 4 + (28 * 2)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"10 + 3 * 17 * 7","answer":"367"}
{"prompt":"62 - 92","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"80 * 55","answer":"4400"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 5) - 1 - 1 * 7","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 1 + 6) * (35 + 6 + 3)","answer":"3740"}
{"prompt":"72 - 8","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"81 + 6","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"56 * (31 * 7)","answer":"12152"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 4) - ((1 * 2) - 7)","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"82 - 17","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"38 - (65 + 9)","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"93 * 21","answer":"1953"}
{"prompt":"((25 * 5) - 2) - 48 - 9","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 5) * 52","answer":"312"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 7) - 49 * 4","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"51 - 29 * 1","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 5 + 2) - 10","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"38 + 52","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 4) * (29 - 7)","answer":"2178"}
{"prompt":"31 + ((63 - 9) * 3)","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 3 * 6) - 30","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 1) + (59 * 1)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(33 - 4) * 44","answer":"1276"}
{"prompt":"34 - 52 * 2","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"77 + 3 + (38 - 6)","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"63 - ((34 - 2) - 9)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"58 - 7 + 40","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"39 + 33","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"82 + 61 + 3","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"((68 + 9) - 6) * 31","answer":"2201"}
{"prompt":"97 - 44","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"92 + 83 + 5 * 3","answer":"190"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 1) * 33 + 10","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"70 + 23","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"1 - 52 * 7 * 2","answer":"-727"}
{"prompt":"35 - ((71 + 1) - 2)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"77 - 7 - 7 * (20 - 2)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"70 * (16 * 4)","answer":"4480"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 2) - (37 * 10)","answer":"-330"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 1) * 41","answer":"2624"}
{"prompt":"38 * 9 + (49 + 5)","answer":"396"}
{"prompt":"9 + 74 * 9 + 5","answer":"680"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 2) - 47","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"4 * 98","answer":"392"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 3) + 47 - 10","answer":"325"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 5) - 96 * 2","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"9 + 70","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 8) * ((9 - 2) - 1)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"77 + 4 * 2 * 64","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"21 * 48 + 9 + 1","answer":"1018"}
{"prompt":"89 * 10 * 3 * 86 * 2 * 3","answer":"1377720"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 6 + 8) + 93","answer":"395"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 9) + (20 - 8)","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"2 * 29","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 7) + 5 * (83 + 6)","answer":"524"}
{"prompt":"28 - 7 - 10 - 4","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"47 + 50","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"((57 * 3) + 6) - 76 - 6","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"28 * (16 * 7) + 5","answer":"3141"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 1) * 88 + 8 * 1","answer":"8016"}
{"prompt":"58 + 5 * 20 * 8","answer":"858"}
{"prompt":"38 * 62","answer":"2356"}
{"prompt":"((37 - 9) - 7) * ((84 + 9) + 2)","answer":"1995"}
{"prompt":"66 - 6 - 9","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"85 + 60","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"60 - 4 + (33 * 6)","answer":"254"}
{"prompt":"56 - 30 + 3 * 8","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"66 - 5 * 3","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 1) - 2 * (64 * 10)","answer":"-1267"}
{"prompt":"95 + 6","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"70 * (15 * 3)","answer":"3150"}
{"prompt":"93 - 41 * 9","answer":"-276"}
{"prompt":"86 - 8 + 10 + 90","answer":"178"}
{"prompt":"66 + 3 * 54","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"37 * 71 - 4 * 4","answer":"2611"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 10) * 5 * 69 + 3 - 8","answer":"4825"}
{"prompt":"91 - 74","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"((16 * 6) + 6) + (64 * 1)","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"49 + 63","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"((60 + 3) - 2) - ((34 - 7) + 8)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"99 - 71","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"53 * 92 * 4 - 8","answer":"19496"}
{"prompt":"67 * (24 + 4)","answer":"1876"}
{"prompt":"14 * 8 + 1 - 5","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 3) * (21 * 10 * 8)","answer":"110880"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 8 * 10) - 30","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"62 * 17","answer":"1054"}
{"prompt":"99 + 33","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"34 + 35","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"5 - 6 * 4","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 9) + (7 + 7 * 3)","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 8 + 3) + 11 + 10","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"19 - (13 * 6)","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"30 * 6 * 5 * 25","answer":"22500"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 6) + 9 * 44","answer":"435"}
{"prompt":"51 - 6 + (79 * 2)","answer":"203"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 9) + 4 - (64 + 3)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"8 - 9 + 76 + 8 + 7","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"((33 - 9) - 8) * 93","answer":"1488"}
{"prompt":"98 + 54 - 2 - 10","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"79 + 4 * 30","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"72 + 10","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"87 + 2","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 10 + 1) - 11","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"97 + 2 + (3 + 10)","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 4) * 72 + 1","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"59 + (57 - 7 + 2)","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"73 * (27 - 1)","answer":"1898"}
{"prompt":"85 * 4 + 87 - 1","answer":"426"}
{"prompt":"78 - (23 + 10 + 7)","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"8 + 3 * 46 - 1 - 7","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"37 + 2 - 65","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"62 - 65 * 1","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"57 - 96","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"96 * (1 + 2)","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"52 + 11","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"6 - 49","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"72 * 53 + 3","answer":"3819"}
{"prompt":"80 + 14","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 4 + 6) * 45","answer":"2610"}
{"prompt":"1 * 47","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"9 * (1 - 7 + 5)","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"92 * 10 - 4 + (7 + 6) - 4","answer":"925"}
{"prompt":"19 - 6 * 2 + 3 * 6 * 5","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"11 * 39","answer":"429"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 3 - 9) + 61 + 7","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(86 + 5) - 17","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"25 - (7 + 1)","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"42 + 8 + 6 - ((19 * 7) - 10)","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"((41 * 10) - 2) - ((48 * 4) * 2)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 1) + 9 + 56","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"88 + 2 - 10 + (15 - 8)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"((82 - 2) + 7) * 20 - 1","answer":"1739"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 3) - 72 * 5","answer":"-358"}
{"prompt":"25 - (13 + 7 + 6)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"59 - (85 - 10) + 6","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"73 + 70","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"28 * 70","answer":"1960"}
{"prompt":"21 * 60","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"51 * (89 - 2 + 10)","answer":"4947"}
{"prompt":"2 - 30","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"3 + 15 - 2","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"55 * 85 + 1","answer":"4676"}
{"prompt":"31 + 6 - 11 * 9","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 2) * 10 * 79 - 3","answer":"80577"}
{"prompt":"52 * 9 + ((52 * 9) - 10)","answer":"926"}
{"prompt":"3 + 8 + 6 + 14 + 4 * 10","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"44 - 3 * 30 - 7","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"20 - 2 - 9 + 15","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"((98 * 9) * 5) - 64","answer":"4346"}
{"prompt":"1 + 54","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"71 - (14 - 2 - 2)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 4) - 9 + 52 - 10 * 8","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"((72 + 1) - 3) + 78 * 1","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"1 + 67","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"((100 + 2) + 1) * 42","answer":"4326"}
{"prompt":"93 * 64","answer":"5952"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 3 + 2) - (61 + 3)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"79 - 86","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"55 - 17 * 8","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"26 + (54 + 10 - 8)","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"1 - 4","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 4) + 1 + 28","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"99 * 87","answer":"8613"}
{"prompt":"54 * 60 + 3","answer":"3243"}
{"prompt":"90 * 14","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 10) * 24","answer":"1104"}
{"prompt":"64 - 16","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"98 - 91","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 6) + (73 * 4) * 4","answer":"1214"}
{"prompt":"20 - 4","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"92 * ((71 + 3) * 1)","answer":"6808"}
{"prompt":"28 + (77 + 4) * 4","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"96 - (84 + 7) + 4","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"26 - ((69 - 4) - 1)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"8 * (47 - 7)","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"89 + ((13 * 3) - 9)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"62 * 6 - 1 + 79","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 2) - 9 - 35 + 4","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"14 + (68 + 9)","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"((20 + 3) * 1) - (15 - 4) + 2","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 7) + 6 - 13","answer":"644"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 7) + 9 + (97 + 2)","answer":"290"}
{"prompt":"2 + 1 + (66 * 10)","answer":"663"}
{"prompt":"((44 - 10) * 3) * 28","answer":"2856"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 2) - 9 + 32 + 1","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 4) - (1 * 4)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"17 - 23","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 2) + 3 * 14 * 6 * 8","answer":"2050"}
{"prompt":"40 * 15","answer":"600"}
{"prompt":"11 * 10 - 8 - 69","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"78 - (72 + 2 * 8)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 4) - 1 * 20 + 2","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"65 + 6 + 5 - ((56 * 4) * 2)","answer":"-372"}
{"prompt":"((91 + 2) - 4) - 51","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"70 + 7 - 49 + 2","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 5) + 9 - 88","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"14 + 6 - 97","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 6) - 1 - 57","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"47 + 4 - 8 - ((34 - 9) * 8)","answer":"-157"}
{"prompt":"44 + 60","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"6 - (43 - 9)","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 2) - 10 - 43 + 3","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"87 * 91 + 7 + 5","answer":"7929"}
{"prompt":"69 * 10 + 5 - 34","answer":"661"}
{"prompt":"83 + 6 + 86","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"27 + 4 - 45","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"58 * 98","answer":"5684"}
{"prompt":"44 + (41 + 2)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"70 - 13","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"2 - 53","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"69 * (11 - 6 + 10)","answer":"1035"}
{"prompt":"20 - (96 - 4)","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"52 + 47","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 1 * 1) + 36 - 10","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"12 + 6 + 100 - 10","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"4 - 2 + 1","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"7 + 3 + 79","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"99 + 59","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"33 - 70 - 1 - 2","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"35 + (64 + 6)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"14 - (20 + 4)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"50 + 63","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1) - 69","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"19 - 21 * 4","answer":"-65"}
{"prompt":"93 + 9 + 1 * 83","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 9) * 74","answer":"666"}
{"prompt":"71 - 10 - 9 - 100","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"((40 - 4) - 1) + 43","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"90 + 87","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"81 - 26","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 8 * 4) - 3","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"77 - 40","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"76 + 99","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 3) + 45","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"79 - (65 + 9) + 7","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"10 + (61 * 8 - 7)","answer":"491"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 1) - 83","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 2) - 18 + 6","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"62 + (40 * 3)","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"64 - 2 * 3","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 6) - 3 - 29","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"73 - 90","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"29 - 7 - 27","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"61 + 4 - 47","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 3 - 7) + 59 * 7","answer":"468"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 6) - 4 * 3","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"15 + 10 * 72","answer":"735"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 3) * 57","answer":"3477"}
{"prompt":"58 * (43 + 4 - 6)","answer":"2378"}
{"prompt":"86 - (33 - 6)","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"2 * 4 + 5 * 11","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 10) + 6 * (85 * 7) + 8","answer":"3683"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 3 + 6) + 100","answer":"178"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 8) - 4","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"9 - 8","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"10 - 58 + 1","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 7) + 36","answer":"183"}
{"prompt":"60 * 4 * 4 * 3","answer":"2880"}
{"prompt":"89 * 9 + 3 + 85","answer":"889"}
{"prompt":"71 * (96 + 1) - 1","answer":"6886"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 5) - 26","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"78 - 79","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"25 - 7 * 8","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"80 - (13 * 8)","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"33 - 90","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"44 + 6 * 1 + 52","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"95 + 9 + 37","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"((4 + 7) + 9) + ((20 + 10) - 6)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"69 + 91","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"35 * 9 + 4 - (99 + 9)","answer":"211"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 6 * 10) * (89 - 2)","answer":"511560"}
{"prompt":"74 + 70","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"64 - 88","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"83 * 52 + 5","answer":"4321"}
{"prompt":"31 + (54 - 9)","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"31 * 9 * 3 - (22 + 3) * 4","answer":"737"}
{"prompt":"44 - 20","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"3 + 13","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"87 + ((67 - 3) * 2)","answer":"215"}
{"prompt":"47 + (96 + 2)","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 9) * 99 * 5 - 3","answer":"14352"}
{"prompt":"31 + 9 * 48","answer":"463"}
{"prompt":"51 - 88","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"87 * 48","answer":"4176"}
{"prompt":"73 * 4","answer":"292"}
{"prompt":"51 * 2 + 64 * 2","answer":"230"}
{"prompt":"38 * 2 * 20","answer":"1520"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 4) + 7 - (89 + 8)","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"1 * (92 * 3 - 10)","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"22 * ((40 + 3) * 10)","answer":"9460"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 8) - (11 + 7)","answer":"646"}
{"prompt":"41 + 56","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 6) + 10 * 45","answer":"810"}
{"prompt":"64 - (1 + 7) + 2","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"37 * 81 - 7 + 3","answer":"2993"}
{"prompt":"24 - 9 * 5 * 67","answer":"-2991"}
{"prompt":"19 + 60","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 6) - 32 * 9","answer":"-254"}
{"prompt":"37 * 26","answer":"962"}
{"prompt":"92 * 6 - 80","answer":"472"}
{"prompt":"67 * 76","answer":"5092"}
{"prompt":"51 + 2 * 8 - 18 * 4","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 10) + 6 + (18 - 9) - 10","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"74 - 10 + 48","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"85 - 96 - 7 - 10","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"79 * 6 + 35","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"41 + 96","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"92 + 2 + 47","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(22 * 2) + 33","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 7) * 92","answer":"6072"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 8) - 87","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"6 * 67","answer":"402"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 3 - 4) + 91","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"63 - ((71 - 5) * 5)","answer":"-267"}
{"prompt":"6 * 3 * 49 - 10","answer":"872"}
{"prompt":"65 * (83 - 6)","answer":"5005"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 6) - 78","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"41 - (87 * 3 * 10)","answer":"-2569"}
{"prompt":"10 - (35 - 6)","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"78 + (56 - 1)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"45 * ((35 + 6) - 2)","answer":"1755"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 10 + 4) - (81 - 3)","answer":"566"}
{"prompt":"52 + 1 * 15","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"11 - 13","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"34 * 76","answer":"2584"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 6) * 60 * 9 + 7","answer":"181447"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 3) - 8 + (29 * 3 - 2)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"25 + 47","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"66 - 6 * 22","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"73 + (29 * 5) + 9","answer":"227"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 3) - 73","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"72 + 3 * 91","answer":"345"}
{"prompt":"76 - 10 + 7","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 8) + 44","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"((39 - 3) - 5) - ((58 + 10) * 3)","answer":"-173"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 7 - 10) + 82","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 6) - (35 + 6)","answer":"313"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 10 * 1) * 67","answer":"1742"}
{"prompt":"5 + 66","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"((90 * 3) - 2) * (58 + 5)","answer":"16884"}
{"prompt":"29 * ((83 - 4) + 1)","answer":"2320"}
{"prompt":"29 - (8 - 5)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"16 - 8 - 10 - (52 * 10)","answer":"-522"}
{"prompt":"55 - 76","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"24 + 1 - (63 - 10 * 6)","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"64 + 51 + 4","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 1 + 3) * (43 - 2 - 2)","answer":"546"}
{"prompt":"92 * (58 + 10) * 5","answer":"31280"}
{"prompt":"75 - (90 + 8)","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 8) * 9 + 15","answer":"726"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 7) + (22 * 6)","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"79 * (15 - 7)","answer":"632"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 9) * 4 * 50 * 3","answer":"62400"}
{"prompt":"29 + 44","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 8 - 7) - 56 * 4","answer":"-168"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 5 * 9) + (69 * 6) * 1","answer":"370"}
{"prompt":"6 - 73","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"25 + 75 - 5","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"45 - 30 * 1 - 10","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"83 * (23 * 6)","answer":"11454"}
{"prompt":"15 * 3 + 54","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"72 * (81 * 7 * 7)","answer":"285768"}
{"prompt":"(10 + 1) * 51","answer":"561"}
{"prompt":"36 - 74 * 6 - 5","answer":"-413"}
{"prompt":"41 * 6 + 5 - ((86 + 5) + 4)","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 7) + 9 + 2","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"5 - (47 + 8)","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"10 * 18","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"91 * 86","answer":"7826"}
{"prompt":"25 - 10 - 2 * (85 - 9 - 8)","answer":"-121"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 6) + 35","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"95 * 3 * 86","answer":"24510"}
{"prompt":"48 + 9 + 85","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"59 + 11","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 8 + 8) * 68 + 10","answer":"44618"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 2) - 22","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 9) - 8 + 78","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"26 * 66 - 2","answer":"1714"}
{"prompt":"3 * (99 * 10) * 2","answer":"5940"}
{"prompt":"2 - 8 + 48","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"41 * 6 * 52 - 10","answer":"12782"}
{"prompt":"61 * 6 + 4 - 47","answer":"323"}
{"prompt":"46 - 10 + 31","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"40 + ((72 + 10) * 7)","answer":"614"}
{"prompt":"44 - 98","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"51 * 5 - 100","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"2 * 6 * 10 + 58 + 1","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"65 * 8 - ((64 - 6) * 6)","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 8) - 20","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"16 - 81 - 5","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 4) - ((81 + 10) * 5)","answer":"-399"}
{"prompt":"67 - 64","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"22 + 58 + 10","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"27 + 10 - 3 * 48","answer":"-107"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 4 * 6) - (18 - 3) * 3","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"98 * 21","answer":"2058"}
{"prompt":"10 + 44","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"16 + 66","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"76 * 4 + 4 * (40 * 4) - 4","answer":"940"}
{"prompt":"42 - 4 * 79","answer":"-274"}
{"prompt":"100 - 8 * 3 - 40","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 4) + 49","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"40 * 4 + 34","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 5) + 70 + 3","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 9) + 91","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"26 - 100","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"97 * 64","answer":"6208"}
{"prompt":"34 + 55 + 4 - 5","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 9) * 3 + 89","answer":"1034"}
{"prompt":"55 - 42","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"98 + 3 - 6 * 95","answer":"-469"}
{"prompt":"49 - 71","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"4 + 37","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"44 * 24","answer":"1056"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 2) + 42","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"41 + 6 + 56 * 2 + 5","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"37 + 5 - 6","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 1) - (79 * 4) - 8","answer":"-294"}
{"prompt":"100 + (62 - 3 + 7)","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"49 + 13","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"82 - 7 * 99","answer":"-611"}
{"prompt":"66 + 35","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 9) + ((9 * 4) - 8)","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"15 + 36","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"64 * 92","answer":"5888"}
{"prompt":"((42 + 1) - 3) + (27 + 3 + 8)","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"62 - (59 * 8)","answer":"-410"}
{"prompt":"6 + (61 * 2)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"51 * 89 * 4","answer":"18156"}
{"prompt":"52 - 52","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"70 - 55 * 4 + 7","answer":"-143"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 2 - 9) + ((71 - 3) * 4)","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"67 - (47 - 7)","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"92 * 21 * 5 - 3","answer":"9657"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 10) + 39 * 8 + 3","answer":"655"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 10) + 4 * 85","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"92 - 38","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 7 - 2) - 73","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 4) - 19 * 10","answer":"-171"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 1 - 5) * 76","answer":"4712"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 5) - ((59 * 2) * 10)","answer":"-1095"}
{"prompt":"83 * (7 * 10)","answer":"5810"}
{"prompt":"54 * (80 + 3)","answer":"4482"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 8) + 5","answer":"381"}
{"prompt":"90 + 75","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"(75 - 9) - ((45 + 1) * 1)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"40 * 3 + 9 - 1 * 4","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 10) - (37 * 6 - 4)","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"41 + 70","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"89 - (87 * 4) - 8","answer":"-267"}
{"prompt":"35 * 6 * 66","answer":"13860"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 1) - 30 + 8 - 1","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"30 + 44","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"24 * (64 + 5)","answer":"1656"}
{"prompt":"65 + 10 + (10 + 5 * 9)","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"((71 - 10) - 9) + (35 * 9) + 8","answer":"375"}
{"prompt":"46 - 70","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"41 * 54 - 3","answer":"2211"}
{"prompt":"39 * (93 * 1)","answer":"3627"}
{"prompt":"15 + (19 * 8)","answer":"167"}
{"prompt":"87 - 1","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"74 + (44 - 2)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"45 - 18","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"59 * 8","answer":"472"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 9 - 10) - (85 * 1)","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"78 + (79 * 4 * 6)","answer":"1974"}
{"prompt":"13 - (52 + 6)","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"19 - 40 * 4 * 8","answer":"-1261"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 8) + 5 + 55 - 7","answer":"357"}
{"prompt":"72 + 63 - 1","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 9) * (26 * 6)","answer":"3432"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 6) - 90","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 2) + 72 + 1","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"21 * ((88 + 7) * 7)","answer":"13965"}
{"prompt":"92 * (30 + 9)","answer":"3588"}
{"prompt":"((47 - 9) * 8) * (48 * 7)","answer":"102144"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 6) - 65 + 2","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"34 + 8 + 52","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"65 + 9 + (35 * 9 - 7)","answer":"382"}
{"prompt":"45 + 47","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"3 - 61","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"33 - 99","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"47 * 62","answer":"2914"}
{"prompt":"((64 * 7) * 10) * 28","answer":"125440"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 7) + 8 * 2","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 10) * 93","answer":"79050"}
{"prompt":"(48 + 8) + 9 * 44","answer":"452"}
{"prompt":"75 + 59 * 4","answer":"311"}
{"prompt":"41 - (3 * 5) - 10","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"63 * 9","answer":"567"}
{"prompt":"79 * 41 - 8","answer":"3231"}
{"prompt":"89 - 51","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"65 - ((46 + 10) + 5)","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 7 + 5) + 66","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"25 + 92 * 6","answer":"577"}
{"prompt":"49 + (81 - 5) * 6","answer":"505"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 10) - 53","answer":"737"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 8) * 5 * 7","answer":"5600"}
{"prompt":"24 - 50","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"64 * 9 * 17","answer":"9792"}
{"prompt":"56 + (38 * 9) - 2","answer":"396"}
{"prompt":"62 + 44 + 4 * 2","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"75 * (13 + 7) * 7","answer":"10500"}
{"prompt":"12 * 93 + 7","answer":"1123"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 1 + 2) + 9","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"54 - (40 + 3)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"98 - 8 + 6 * 95","answer":"660"}
{"prompt":"48 + 1 - 5 * 38","answer":"-141"}
{"prompt":"79 + 98","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"7 - 16","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"84 - 41","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 3) * 79","answer":"1659"}
{"prompt":"13 - 14","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"53 - 87 * 1 * 2","answer":"-121"}
{"prompt":"5 * 96","answer":"480"}
{"prompt":"(22 - 5) * 76","answer":"1292"}
{"prompt":"11 * 57 * 5","answer":"3135"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 2 * 2) + 82","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"37 + 24","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 5) - 6 + 13","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"84 - 8 - 9","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"27 - (61 - 3) + 1","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"71 * (52 - 4)","answer":"3408"}
{"prompt":"93 + 95 - 3 * 5","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"29 - 10 + 48 + 4","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"60 * 9 * 3 - 20 + 4","answer":"1604"}
{"prompt":"5 - 87 + 1 * 4","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"6 + 9 * 89","answer":"807"}
{"prompt":"11 + 9 * 1 - 80","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"44 * 59 + 9 + 5","answer":"2610"}
{"prompt":"94 * 2 + (95 + 8 * 3)","answer":"307"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 4) + 39","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"71 + 52 * 2","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"11 + 49","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"33 + 25","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"54 * 3 - 1 + 23","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"92 - 6 + 50","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(89 - 5 + 6) * 64","answer":"5760"}
{"prompt":"64 + 50","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"64 + 5","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"56 + 31 + 6","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"46 + 4 * 18 * 5","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"((52 - 5) * 5) + (71 * 8)","answer":"803"}
{"prompt":"54 + 6 - 39","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"31 - 5 + (23 - 4)","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"91 * (21 + 8 * 2)","answer":"3367"}
{"prompt":"19 * 3 + 43","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"30 - (5 - 3 * 5)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"4 + ((35 - 9) + 2)","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"47 * 61","answer":"2867"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 9 + 9) + (76 - 5)","answer":"296"}
{"prompt":"84 - 98 - 10","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 3) * 14","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"82 * 10 - 79","answer":"741"}
{"prompt":"79 * (55 - 6) * 2","answer":"7742"}
{"prompt":"29 + 9 * 99","answer":"920"}
{"prompt":"((98 - 5) * 3) - 85 + 4","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"1 + (4 + 3)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"((74 * 1) - 10) + 5 - 5","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"47 * 94 * 7","answer":"30926"}
{"prompt":"69 * 87","answer":"6003"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 10 - 10) + 78","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"((31 - 2) - 6) + 60","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"7 + 33","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 1) - 14","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"53 * 36 - 7","answer":"1901"}
{"prompt":"34 + 96","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"45 * 26","answer":"1170"}
{"prompt":"(33 - 9) + 7","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 6) * (37 + 4)","answer":"3116"}
{"prompt":"66 + 93","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"12 + (69 + 9)","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"((24 - 4) - 5) + 26","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"66 + 35","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"89 + 60 * 1","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"57 - 88","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"95 * 22","answer":"2090"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 9) + 20 * 5 + 3","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 1) * 85 + 1","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"28 + 53","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"30 * 10 + 11 + 9 + 7","answer":"327"}
{"prompt":"62 * 84","answer":"5208"}
{"prompt":"23 + 2","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"72 - 10 - 8 + (47 + 7 - 9)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"10 * 53","answer":"530"}
{"prompt":"93 - 1 + 8 + ((86 + 10) + 2)","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"27 - 39","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"29 + 30","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 10) - 54","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 2) * 5 - (1 * 6)","answer":"274"}
{"prompt":"91 * 7 * 87 - 8 - 6","answer":"55405"}
{"prompt":"32 + 1 - 77","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 10) - (89 - 10)","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(47 + 5) * 1 + (24 * 7)","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"48 + 74","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"71 * 7 * 47","answer":"23359"}
{"prompt":"29 + 36","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"89 * 62","answer":"5518"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 4) - 81 - 8","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"25 * ((92 * 8) * 2)","answer":"36800"}
{"prompt":"47 + 6 * (42 + 5)","answer":"329"}
{"prompt":"85 - 50","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"54 - 32","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"56 + 2 + 5 * 26","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 1 + 3) - (32 + 3)","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"((36 - 8) * 3) - 52 * 5","answer":"-176"}
{"prompt":"92 * 49","answer":"4508"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 9) + 8) * (21 + 4)","answer":"750"}
{"prompt":"67 + 10 - 8","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"52 - 5 - 2 * 8","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"85 - 5 * 7 - (83 * 7) + 8","answer":"-523"}
{"prompt":"94 - (27 + 2) - 9","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 9) + (41 - 7) * 9","answer":"362"}
{"prompt":"40 * 6 + 1","answer":"241"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 1) + 1 - 48","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"34 * 91","answer":"3094"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 4) - 69 + 10","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"66 * 98","answer":"6468"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 3 + 5) + (87 - 1)","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 7) - 55","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"75 - (44 - 4) + 7","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"9 * 45","answer":"405"}
{"prompt":"97 + 20","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"25 * 60 * 7","answer":"10500"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 8) * 8 + 68","answer":"732"}
{"prompt":"81 - (66 - 4)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"8 * 3 + 7 * (43 * 5)","answer":"1529"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 6) * 43 + 10 * 2","answer":"1783"}
{"prompt":"18 - ((97 * 5) + 7)","answer":"-474"}
{"prompt":"2 + 5 + 41","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 2) * (92 * 10) - 8","answer":"161912"}
{"prompt":"34 - (78 - 2)","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"95 - 6 - 8 + 35","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"93 - 95 - 4","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 2 + 5) * (50 * 7)","answer":"7350"}
{"prompt":"93 + 9 * (7 * 10)","answer":"723"}
{"prompt":"((86 - 10) * 7) * 9","answer":"4788"}
{"prompt":"62 + (86 - 2)","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"43 - (20 + 9)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"36 - 54","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"50 - 27 + 5","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"16 - 6 + 21","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 1) + 25","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 4) * 92","answer":"9936"}
{"prompt":"98 - 8 - 62","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"((21 + 6) * 3) * 66","answer":"5346"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 10) - 34","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 5) - 5 * (40 * 7)","answer":"-1397"}
{"prompt":"60 - 15","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"54 * 10","answer":"540"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 9) - 24 * 3","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"57 + (2 - 1) - 9","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"26 + 8 + (80 * 8)","answer":"674"}
{"prompt":"44 + 6 * 11 - 1 + 8","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"54 * 92 + 9","answer":"4977"}
{"prompt":"18 + 87","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"45 + 29","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"76 * 7 - 44","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"44 - 10 + 35","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 9) - 81","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 10 - 3) + (97 * 1)","answer":"274"}
{"prompt":"((34 - 2) * 7) + 61 - 2","answer":"283"}
{"prompt":"90 + 61","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"30 * 58","answer":"1740"}
{"prompt":"45 + 4 - 2 * 61 * 9","answer":"-1049"}
{"prompt":"9 * 24 + 4","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 3 * 10) - (29 + 9) - 8","answer":"2234"}
{"prompt":"78 + 40","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"91 * 8 + 42","answer":"770"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 4) * 60","answer":"21360"}
{"prompt":"89 * (71 * 6)","answer":"37914"}
{"prompt":"44 * 72 * 6","answer":"19008"}
{"prompt":"67 - 30","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"100 - (59 - 2)","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"((58 - 4) - 3) + 1","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"90 + 9 * 8 + 2","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"78 - 2 - 58 * 7","answer":"-330"}
{"prompt":"93 + (47 - 3) + 6","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"79 + 57 + 8","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"35 * 6 - 1 + 64 + 4 * 10","answer":"313"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 2) - 4 + 79","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 7) + (64 - 4)","answer":"473"}
{"prompt":"92 * (68 + 2 + 5)","answer":"6900"}
{"prompt":"68 + 55 + 3 - 9","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"86 * (42 - 7)","answer":"3010"}
{"prompt":"44 + 56","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"36 + 10","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"76 * 2 * 6 + 67","answer":"979"}
{"prompt":"83 + 91","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"82 - (6 * 9 * 3)","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"((18 - 7) * 5) + (72 - 5)","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 5) * (98 + 3)","answer":"4141"}
{"prompt":"6 + 7 + 2 - ((26 - 9) * 1)","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 10) - ((2 * 6) - 5)","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 7) + (16 * 10)","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"83 + ((34 + 6) - 10)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"38 * 44","answer":"1672"}
{"prompt":"17 * 9 + 4 * 34","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"75 + 100","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 3) - (33 - 8 - 6)","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 7) * 6 - (50 + 7)","answer":"387"}
{"prompt":"60 - 45 - 6","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"27 * ((18 * 1) - 8)","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"73 - 86","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"39 * 70 - 7","answer":"2723"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 7) - 52 * 6 * 9","answer":"-2736"}
{"prompt":"91 + (87 + 10 + 4)","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"36 * 34","answer":"1224"}
{"prompt":"82 - 2 * 63","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"100 - 20 * 9","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"5 + 59 - 5 * 4","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"31 + ((62 - 10) * 3)","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 3 + 2) - 64","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 7) * 62","answer":"3038"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 4 - 10) * (24 + 8)","answer":"768"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 4) * 8 + 33","answer":"721"}
{"prompt":"(10 + 5 * 4) - (95 - 7)","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 2) + 1 - ((60 * 6) + 1)","answer":"-202"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 6) - 55","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"35 - 18","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 7) + 1 + 81 * 9","answer":"800"}
{"prompt":"81 + (66 + 5)","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"12 * 73","answer":"876"}
{"prompt":"((97 * 4) - 5) * (75 + 4) - 8","answer":"30249"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 6) * 83","answer":"3071"}
{"prompt":"24 * 71","answer":"1704"}
{"prompt":"73 - 78 + 7 * 2","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"((4 + 8) * 4) + 22 + 8","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 8) - 41","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 9) - ((52 + 10) * 1)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 8) * (60 * 8 + 8)","answer":"49776"}
{"prompt":"18 - 19 * 5 + 2","answer":"-75"}
{"prompt":"38 - (86 + 4 + 4)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"29 - (39 * 7)","answer":"-244"}
{"prompt":"8 + 30","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(10 - 9) - 99 + 2 - 4","answer":"-100"}
{"prompt":"36 * 19 + 6","answer":"690"}
{"prompt":"1 * 67 * 10","answer":"670"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 2) - 8 - 50 + 5 - 10","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"90 - ((40 + 1) - 9)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"86 - 98","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"46 * 91 * 4","answer":"16744"}
{"prompt":"((79 - 4) + 10) * 77","answer":"6545"}
{"prompt":"20 - 38 * 10","answer":"-360"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 8) * 46 + 3","answer":"14355"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 7) - 10 - 99","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"44 - 3 * 53 * 9","answer":"-1387"}
{"prompt":"38 - 71","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 2) + 1 * 3","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"98 + 52 - 3","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"41 + 7 + (43 + 1)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"8 * (99 - 7 * 1)","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"93 + 8 - 1 - (52 * 8 + 8)","answer":"-324"}
{"prompt":"73 * 26","answer":"1898"}
{"prompt":"28 * 5 + 21","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"80 - (89 * 2) * 3","answer":"-454"}
{"prompt":"43 + 5 - 15 * 3 * 5","answer":"-177"}
{"prompt":"54 * 10 - 35","answer":"505"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 8 - 7) * ((44 - 9) + 4)","answer":"351"}
{"prompt":"98 + 50 + 9","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"((63 - 3) - 3) + 27","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"64 + 8 * 11","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"77 + 55","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"65 + 10 * 40","answer":"465"}
{"prompt":"65 - 71 * 3","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"47 - 9 * 7 * 31","answer":"-1906"}
{"prompt":"90 * 48","answer":"4320"}
{"prompt":"31 * 14","answer":"434"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 10) * (18 * 6)","answer":"17280"}
{"prompt":"86 + 96 + 5","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"40 - 84","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"42 - (92 * 2)","answer":"-142"}
{"prompt":"27 + 78","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"94 - 50 - 4","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"46 + 10 * 4 - 46 + 7 - 7","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(62 * 3) + 9 + (6 + 5)","answer":"206"}
{"prompt":"38 * (10 - 5)","answer":"190"}
{"prompt":"74 - 6 * 76","answer":"-382"}
{"prompt":"20 * 31","answer":"620"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 9 + 2) * 95","answer":"75430"}
{"prompt":"48 + 34","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"42 + 95","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 5) - 4","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"64 + 40 - 9 + 10","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"73 + ((52 * 10) - 2)","answer":"591"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 1) - 6 - ((74 - 3) - 6)","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"20 - 6 + 64","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"83 + 39 - 5 * 5","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"7 * (68 - 10)","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"12 - 33","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"23 - 71","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"((46 * 2) * 4) * 8","answer":"2944"}
{"prompt":"43 - 72","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"36 * 6 + 7 + (69 * 1)","answer":"292"}
{"prompt":"64 * (24 * 4)","answer":"6144"}
{"prompt":"76 + 33","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"((91 - 7) * 6) + 45","answer":"549"}
{"prompt":"94 + 35","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"8 * 6 - (31 + 6)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 9) - 3 + 5","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"37 + 68","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 4) * 10 - (74 * 7)","answer":"2322"}
{"prompt":"97 + 21","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 2) * (61 + 8)","answer":"2553"}
{"prompt":"17 - 88","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"90 + 40 + 5","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"15 * 2 - 1 + 20 + 1","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"83 - ((75 + 2) - 5)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"84 * 78","answer":"6552"}
{"prompt":"17 + (99 + 10 - 1)","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"66 + 2 + 10 * 7","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"42 + 9 - 10","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"29 - 10 * (89 - 9)","answer":"-771"}
{"prompt":"51 * 99 - 8 + 4","answer":"5045"}
{"prompt":"86 - 17 - 2 + 7","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 5) - 81 + 1 * 5","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"91 * ((85 * 7) + 7)","answer":"54782"}
{"prompt":"(81 + 1) - 4 * 7","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 5) * (87 + 10 + 6)","answer":"31415"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 8 * 9) + 66","answer":"498"}
{"prompt":"81 + (62 * 4) + 10","answer":"339"}
{"prompt":"78 - 32 - 1","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"48 + 7 - 10 + 78","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 1) - 9 * 85 - 1","answer":"-762"}
{"prompt":"27 - (34 - 1)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"37 * 29","answer":"1073"}
{"prompt":"97 * 3 + 10 + 6 - 6","answer":"301"}
{"prompt":"74 + (92 * 6)","answer":"626"}
{"prompt":"85 * 10 - 2 - 16 + 5 - 1","answer":"836"}
{"prompt":"92 * 94","answer":"8648"}
{"prompt":"80 + ((1 - 3) + 3)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"90 * 3","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"64 * 91","answer":"5824"}
{"prompt":"50 - 39","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 7) * 70","answer":"1680"}
{"prompt":"14 + 55","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"52 - 96","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"59 - 17 * 6 * 8","answer":"-757"}
{"prompt":"80 * 74 - 10","answer":"5910"}
{"prompt":"29 - (89 + 1)","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"88 * 31 + 4","answer":"2732"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 7) * 1 + 13","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"10 + (87 + 1)","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"100 + 80","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"26 + (87 - 8) - 3","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 2) - 3 * 77","answer":"-155"}
{"prompt":"4 - 84","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"18 * 25","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"33 * 1 - 8 * 23","answer":"-151"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 9) + 86","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 1) * 75","answer":"2250"}
{"prompt":"100 - 31","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"33 + 96","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"38 * 91","answer":"3458"}
{"prompt":"27 + 42","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"77 * 43","answer":"3311"}
{"prompt":"8 + 8 - 11","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"28 * 5 + 6 + (53 + 4)","answer":"203"}
{"prompt":"((8 - 9) - 5) + ((96 - 5) * 3)","answer":"267"}
{"prompt":"20 * 3","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"24 - 4 + 37","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"68 + (61 * 6) + 6","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"42 - 57","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"75 + 18","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 3 - 6) * 52 + 10","answer":"11710"}
{"prompt":"70 - 93 * 7","answer":"-581"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 4) * 3","answer":"267"}
{"prompt":"((32 * 4) + 6) + 13 + 4 - 4","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"92 - 18","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 1) + 94","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"26 * 3 * 98 - 3 * 8","answer":"7620"}
{"prompt":"24 * 6 - (92 - 6)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 6) + 20","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"24 + ((1 - 3) + 3)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"64 * 1 - ((89 - 6) - 7)","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"67 - 3 * 34","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"20 * 64","answer":"1280"}
{"prompt":"50 - (11 * 6) * 6","answer":"-346"}
{"prompt":"38 - 17","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"45 - (14 + 3 - 4)","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"24 + (11 + 5)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"10 + 5 - 46","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 3) + 9","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 5) + 68","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"59 * 59 - 3","answer":"3478"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 5) * 7 + 3","answer":"2663"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 6 - 5) + ((15 + 10) - 8)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"70 + 62","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 6) - 9 - 5","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 8 - 6) - 91","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"49 + 2","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 4) * 77 * 6","answer":"33264"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 3) * 4) - 13","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"80 + 3 + 89","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"58 * ((48 * 1) + 10)","answer":"3364"}
{"prompt":"44 + (29 + 10) - 8","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"77 + 10 * 9 * 53 + 8","answer":"4855"}
{"prompt":"46 * 1 * 2 - 18 * 5","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"71 * 7 * 72","answer":"35784"}
{"prompt":"((82 - 5) - 6) + (67 - 3)","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 6 + 5) * 79","answer":"44477"}
{"prompt":"100 + (13 + 2 + 5)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 5) + (54 - 1) - 2","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"((34 + 10) + 5) - 39","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 2) + 5","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"34 - 60","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"59 + (65 - 5)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 6) - ((6 * 7) - 1)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"81 + 82","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 5 * 7) * 16 * 5","answer":"1040"}
{"prompt":"24 - 1 * (61 * 8) + 3","answer":"-461"}
{"prompt":"29 * (10 * 5)","answer":"1450"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 9) - (26 - 6) + 9","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"77 + 10 * 10 + 46","answer":"223"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 1) - 5 * 8","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"89 * 7 - 45 - 10","answer":"568"}
{"prompt":"15 - 13","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"32 * 4 * 2 - 9 * 5","answer":"211"}
{"prompt":"98 + 17","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"100 - 2 + 2 * 8","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"((77 - 7) - 9) * 34","answer":"2074"}
{"prompt":"52 - (78 - 5)","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"96 - (44 - 10 * 10)","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"85 * 4 + 68","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"98 + 7 - 5 - 52","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"52 + 8 - (93 * 4 - 3)","answer":"-309"}
{"prompt":"32 * (3 - 7)","answer":"-128"}
{"prompt":"83 - 1 - 30 * 7","answer":"-128"}
{"prompt":"34 + 91","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"((25 + 5) - 7) - ((17 - 10) + 6)","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 3) - 86","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"3 * ((62 * 7) - 2)","answer":"1296"}
{"prompt":"62 + 97","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"3 * 8 - 99 - 5","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"34 + 2 - 4 - (21 * 5)","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"71 + ((81 * 6) * 10)","answer":"4931"}
{"prompt":"7 - 7 - 9 - 46","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 4) + 97 + 6 * 7","answer":"395"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 10 + 1) * (22 - 4 * 8)","answer":"-2510"}
{"prompt":"9 * 73","answer":"657"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 3) + (12 * 9) - 5","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"11 + 29","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 4) * 50","answer":"2950"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 9) + 63","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"70 * (85 - 9)","answer":"5320"}
{"prompt":"(62 * 2) - 1 + (81 + 5)","answer":"209"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 10) * 1 - (25 + 1) - 10","answer":"464"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 1) + 53","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"56 + (34 + 8)","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"58 + 7 - 72","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 8) - 2 - 1 - 8","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"22 * 20 - 9","answer":"431"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 2) + 13 * 2","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 1) - 4 * ((83 + 1) - 6)","answer":"-257"}
{"prompt":"40 + 5","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"26 * 65","answer":"1690"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 10) - 9 + 6","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"9 + (21 - 1)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 8 + 3) * 20","answer":"2220"}
{"prompt":"82 - 5 - 10 - 62","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"85 * 2 * (51 * 9)","answer":"78030"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 9) + 7 * 65","answer":"519"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 1 - 6) + 78 + 10","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 3) + (50 + 1)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"44 + 7 * 26","answer":"226"}
{"prompt":"20 - 5","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"69 - 9 - 3 - 55","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"13 + 9 * 45","answer":"418"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 10) * (57 - 10)","answer":"3196"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 4) * 32","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"34 + (71 + 5)","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"43 + (76 - 1) - 7","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 1 * 6) + 63 * 5","answer":"349"}
{"prompt":"90 * 35","answer":"3150"}
{"prompt":"61 - 50","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"50 + 16","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"32 - 46","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"54 + 22","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 9) + 74","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"96 + 10 - 5 + (29 * 7)","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"67 + 79","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 2 + 5) - 84","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 10) + 10 + 67","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"16 - 2 - 94","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"((32 + 6) - 3) + (42 + 7)","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"95 - 74 - 3","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"85 * 5 + (49 + 7 * 7)","answer":"523"}
{"prompt":"77 * 68","answer":"5236"}
{"prompt":"95 + 89","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 4 + 5) + 87 + 4","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"(81 + 7) - 7 + ((33 * 9) + 3)","answer":"381"}
{"prompt":"37 * 58","answer":"2146"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 1 - 5) - 56","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"3 - 58","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"98 - 2 * 96","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"((83 + 6) * 1) + 1","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"55 + (6 * 3)","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"28 * 9 - 69 * 5","answer":"-93"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 8 - 3) + (73 + 7 * 6)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"8 + 8 + 82","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"85 * (76 + 4)","answer":"6800"}
{"prompt":"75 - 47","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 3 + 2) - 68","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"20 * 69 * 9","answer":"12420"}
{"prompt":"82 * (71 - 7)","answer":"5248"}
{"prompt":"2 + 10 - 67","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 1) * 2 - 15","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"5 - 25","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"33 - 5 - 52","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"17 + (99 + 5) * 2","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 9 + 9) * 6","answer":"1512"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 9) * (93 + 7) * 9","answer":"291600"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 5) + 8 - 22 + 1 + 3","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"65 - 6 + 7 * 62","answer":"493"}
{"prompt":"55 + 81","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 3) - (40 + 9 - 10)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 5) * 10 * (79 + 7)","answer":"18060"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 3) - 48 + 10 + 2","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"30 - 58 + 8 - 3","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(42 + 1) + 11 + 3","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"60 - 97","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 9 + 5) * 61","answer":"1586"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 7) + 77 + 8","answer":"316"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 9) + 92","answer":"542"}
{"prompt":"64 * 92","answer":"5888"}
{"prompt":"34 + (1 * 1)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 7) * 9 - 78","answer":"633"}
{"prompt":"85 * 15","answer":"1275"}
{"prompt":"69 + 46","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 1) * 48","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 5) * (72 - 9)","answer":"3402"}
{"prompt":"60 - 82","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"77 - ((21 + 2) - 3)","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"69 + 81","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 8) - 7 * 83 * 3","answer":"-1666"}
{"prompt":"2 * 91","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"((52 + 5) + 2) + 26 - 8","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"50 - 50","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 1 - 8) + 88","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"92 + 6 - 47","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((67 - 9) - 2) * (30 * 8 + 5)","answer":"13720"}
{"prompt":"100 * 38 - 8 - 1","answer":"3791"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 9 * 8) * 30","answer":"2430"}
{"prompt":"74 * (63 + 7) - 6","answer":"5174"}
{"prompt":"((51 * 6) - 5) - (43 + 2) + 10","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"95 + (86 - 5)","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"59 - ((58 + 9) + 10)","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"94 - 6 + 91","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"38 - 57 - 2","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"57 + 3 + 1 * 77","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"(62 - 6) * (51 - 7) * 2","answer":"4928"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 10 + 3) * (38 * 9)","answer":"24282"}
{"prompt":"31 * 53","answer":"1643"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 7) + 49 + 10 - 3","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"64 - (2 * 7) + 6","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"58 * (43 * 3)","answer":"7482"}
{"prompt":"11 - 73","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"94 - 6 - 8","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"78 - 2 * 8 - 39","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"19 - 9 + 60","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"24 * 44 + 7 + 5","answer":"1068"}
{"prompt":"45 + 2","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"88 * (82 - 2)","answer":"7040"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 10) - 1 * 45","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"35 - 69 - 4 + 6","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"4 - (43 - 8)","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"38 * 40 + 2","answer":"1522"}
{"prompt":"64 - 77","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"16 + 3 + 14","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"15 * (99 + 8)","answer":"1605"}
{"prompt":"95 * 2 + 56","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 9) + 19","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"62 * 29","answer":"1798"}
{"prompt":"77 - (53 + 1) - 1","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"13 - 6 + 34","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"54 * (57 * 10)","answer":"30780"}
{"prompt":"21 + 100","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"83 + 2 - 9 - 61","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"4 * 9 * 3 * (17 - 10) * 5","answer":"3780"}
{"prompt":"(3 + 4) + 1 + 55","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 7) * 5 + (66 * 10 - 5)","answer":"1075"}
{"prompt":"25 - ((75 * 8) - 9)","answer":"-566"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 1 * 6) - 40","answer":"386"}
{"prompt":"99 - 96","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 6) + 10 - 89","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"34 - (6 + 1) + 5","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 7) - ((37 + 2) + 1)","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"53 - 51 - 5","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"((17 - 3) + 1) - 15 * 2 + 10","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"92 - 9 + 2","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"33 * 43 * 8","answer":"11352"}
{"prompt":"70 - (69 * 3)","answer":"-137"}
{"prompt":"28 + 49","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"100 - (25 - 3) + 7","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"((9 - 2) + 2) * 30","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"68 + 40","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 5 + 5) * 71","answer":"14555"}
{"prompt":"20 * 70","answer":"1400"}
{"prompt":"33 + 93","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"68 * 5 + 13","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 9 * 7) * 69","answer":"-3795"}
{"prompt":"53 - 1 * 2 * 77 * 7 * 10","answer":"-10727"}
{"prompt":"29 * (76 * 6 * 3)","answer":"39672"}
{"prompt":"30 - 16","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 2) - (50 * 8 - 8)","answer":"-316"}
{"prompt":"82 * 33","answer":"2706"}
{"prompt":"72 - (8 * 4) * 4","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"39 * 88","answer":"3432"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 10) - 4) + 95 - 6 - 9","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"4 * 82","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"18 + 4 + 70","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"49 * (2 + 3) - 1","answer":"244"}
{"prompt":"37 * 35 - 3","answer":"1292"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 5) * 8 - 54","answer":"226"}
{"prompt":"89 - (15 + 3)","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 7 + 3) - 64","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"95 * 1 - (43 + 4) - 6","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"27 * 82","answer":"2214"}
{"prompt":"25 - 6 * 10 + 34","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"84 * ((61 * 3) + 1)","answer":"15456"}
{"prompt":"76 * (70 * 8)","answer":"42560"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 8) - 3 * 58","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"18 - (14 * 6 * 3)","answer":"-234"}
{"prompt":"((45 * 8) - 8) + 26 * 3 - 2","answer":"428"}
{"prompt":"((11 + 2) - 6) - 71 * 10","answer":"-703"}
{"prompt":"12 - 99","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"96 - 8 * 82","answer":"-560"}
{"prompt":"68 - 22","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 9 * 7) * (60 * 1)","answer":"1740"}
{"prompt":"(15 * 4) + 7 - 8","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"56 - 87","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 9) * 8 * 75","answer":"58800"}
{"prompt":"24 - (67 * 5) * 10","answer":"-3326"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 2) + 9 + 32","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"71 - ((40 + 3) + 9)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"83 + 13","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 6) * (69 * 8)","answer":"552"}
{"prompt":"37 - 2 - 4 - 80 + 6 + 1","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"6 + 4 - (12 + 8)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"40 - 71","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"49 - 2 - 21 * 7 + 8","answer":"-92"}
{"prompt":"33 * 17","answer":"561"}
{"prompt":"100 + 31","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 3 + 7) * 65 + 4 + 9","answer":"598"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 5) + 26 * 3 + 8","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 1) * 9 + 4","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 4) * 36","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 8) - 63","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"43 * 58 * 9 + 4","answer":"22450"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 10 - 4) + 73","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"67 - 3 - 68 * 3","answer":"-140"}
{"prompt":"78 * ((97 + 6) * 5)","answer":"40170"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 2) + 84","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 4) - (54 + 7)","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 9) - 96","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 1) - 31","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"34 - 88 + 5 + 2","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"81 + 78","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"28 - 46","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 10) - 65","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"38 - ((41 + 5) * 2)","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"68 - 26","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"88 * ((75 - 8) * 3)","answer":"17688"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 6 + 9) - (29 + 9) - 4","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 6 + 1) + (35 * 6)","answer":"261"}
{"prompt":"79 + 88 + 2 - 6","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"40 + ((4 - 1) + 4)","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"26 - 68","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"68 - (25 * 6 + 1)","answer":"-83"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((33 + 2) * 5)","answer":"-135"}
{"prompt":"4 - 32 * 9","answer":"-284"}
{"prompt":"12 + 84","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"8 - 9 * (74 * 2)","answer":"-1324"}
{"prompt":"87 + 10 + 8 - 3","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"12 - ((14 - 4) + 2)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"43 + 57","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 8) + 8 + 100 + 4 - 1","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"56 + (6 + 5)","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"50 + 65","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"9 - 1 + (20 + 1)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"17 - (55 + 9 * 7)","answer":"-101"}
{"prompt":"60 * 5 - 41","answer":"259"}
{"prompt":"24 + 25","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"11 - 53 * 8 - 8","answer":"-421"}
{"prompt":"66 - 36 * 6","answer":"-150"}
{"prompt":"58 * ((60 * 2) + 7)","answer":"7366"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 3) + 7 - (24 - 5 + 1)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"74 - (21 * 7)","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"1 + 2 * ((52 * 3) * 9)","answer":"2809"}
{"prompt":"86 * 55","answer":"4730"}
{"prompt":"((78 * 2) + 6) + 96","answer":"258"}
{"prompt":"87 + 4 - 13 - 8","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"20 * 3 - 6 * 82","answer":"-432"}
{"prompt":"86 * 44","answer":"3784"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 4) * 93","answer":"34968"}
{"prompt":"61 - 18","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 5) + 9 * (33 - 3 + 6)","answer":"334"}
{"prompt":"9 - 2 - (30 * 3) - 6","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 8) - 49","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 10) + 58 * 3","answer":"257"}
{"prompt":"85 * (85 * 3 + 3)","answer":"21930"}
{"prompt":"26 * 10 - (62 + 7)","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"68 - ((73 * 6) - 8)","answer":"-362"}
{"prompt":"23 + 18 + 8 + 4","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"77 * 71","answer":"5467"}
{"prompt":"63 + 87","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"41 - 95","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"89 + 7 - 82","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"70 * (97 + 4)","answer":"7070"}
{"prompt":"12 - (52 + 6)","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"8 - 41","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"14 * 7 + 9 - 19","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"96 - 39","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"51 + 10 * (84 * 4) - 10","answer":"3401"}
{"prompt":"69 - 84","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 8) + (14 + 6)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"56 + 79 - 1 + 10","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"30 * 60 * 6","answer":"10800"}
{"prompt":"15 - 5 * (88 * 1)","answer":"-425"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 6) * 67","answer":"18894"}
{"prompt":"97 + ((40 + 9) * 6)","answer":"391"}
{"prompt":"85 * ((91 - 10) + 5)","answer":"7310"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 4) - 100","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"49 + 73","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"82 * 44","answer":"3608"}
{"prompt":"38 + 75","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"32 - 76 * 2","answer":"-120"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 5) - 7 - ((21 * 6) + 10)","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 3) - 48","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"5 - 23","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 7) - 5 + ((20 + 4) - 2)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"33 - (27 * 6)","answer":"-129"}
{"prompt":"21 + ((77 * 4) * 8)","answer":"2485"}
{"prompt":"10 - 91","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 8) + 20","answer":"260"}
{"prompt":"30 - (53 * 5)","answer":"-235"}
{"prompt":"51 * 8 + 10 + 76","answer":"494"}
{"prompt":"66 * 3 + (23 * 3) - 6","answer":"261"}
{"prompt":"42 + 34 * 6","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 7) - 40","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"((2 - 2) * 2) - ((45 - 2) - 8)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"10 + 71","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 10) * (95 + 5 + 2)","answer":"8262"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 9) + (28 * 3)","answer":"759"}
{"prompt":"18 - 4 + 72","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"64 - 10 - 100","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"((57 - 8) * 8) - 65","answer":"327"}
{"prompt":"51 * (29 + 3 + 3)","answer":"1785"}
{"prompt":"99 * 3 - (1 + 2)","answer":"294"}
{"prompt":"58 - 5 - 3","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 2) * 1 + 68 + 6","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"86 + 3 + 47","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"42 + 27","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"76 - 5 + ((29 + 9) * 6)","answer":"299"}
{"prompt":"90 * 10 + 3","answer":"903"}
{"prompt":"11 * 6 + 47 - 1 * 5","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"75 * 74","answer":"5550"}
{"prompt":"100 - 8 + 33 * 10 - 6","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 4 + 10) * 61","answer":"3172"}
{"prompt":"97 + 1 - 24","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"29 + 75","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"68 * 76","answer":"5168"}
{"prompt":"70 - 87 + 7","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"((3 - 2) - 10) + 96","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"3 + (72 - 7)","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"30 - (35 * 2 * 5)","answer":"-320"}
{"prompt":"((59 * 8) - 8) + 40 + 4","answer":"508"}
{"prompt":"28 - 39","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"73 * (69 + 5)","answer":"5402"}
{"prompt":"35 - 2 + 8","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"45 + 3 * 44","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"54 - 25","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 7) + 4 - 14","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"92 - 49","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 6) - 7 + (74 + 4)","answer":"569"}
{"prompt":"74 - 7 * 3 + 85","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"85 - 10 * 8 + (12 + 9) + 10","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(77 - 8) - 46","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"49 - 6 - 65","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"17 - 64","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 1 + 6) + 52","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"((19 - 8) + 2) * (2 + 7)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"68 + 5 - (82 - 10)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 7) - 9 * 13","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"59 + 89 + 2 * 2","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"90 - (50 + 7)","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"50 + 9 * (44 + 7)","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"((38 + 4) - 9) - (90 - 7)","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"30 + ((8 * 2) * 2)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"34 - (81 * 8) * 7","answer":"-4502"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 10) - 18","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"49 + 4 - 66 * 9","answer":"-541"}
{"prompt":"93 - ((20 + 3) + 2)","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 8) - 80","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"97 * (92 + 5 * 7)","answer":"12319"}
{"prompt":"70 + ((73 + 3) + 10)","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"57 * 10 * 10 * (72 - 10)","answer":"353400"}
{"prompt":"48 * 22 - 10","answer":"1046"}
{"prompt":"17 * 83","answer":"1411"}
{"prompt":"6 + 94","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"91 + 42","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"23 * (61 * 5)","answer":"7015"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 4 * 5) - 62","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 3 * 7) * 97","answer":"11543"}
{"prompt":"95 + 92","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"58 + 8 + (39 * 5)","answer":"261"}
{"prompt":"69 + 32","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 8) * 44","answer":"3124"}
{"prompt":"82 + 21 * 2 * 6","answer":"334"}
{"prompt":"58 * 58 - 6","answer":"3358"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 4) * 5 * (63 + 10)","answer":"134320"}
{"prompt":"18 - 10","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"54 - 49","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"17 + 28 * 8","answer":"241"}
{"prompt":"69 * 1 - 5 + 75","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"66 - 96","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"8 + (57 - 2 * 1)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 6 + 6) + 52 * 2 * 9","answer":"942"}
{"prompt":"36 * 9 - 95","answer":"229"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 2 - 1) - 60","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"78 - 33 + 5","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 6) + 2 - 9 * 3","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"27 * 18 * 8","answer":"3888"}
{"prompt":"4 * 89 - 4","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"43 * 6 * 41 - 4 + 3","answer":"10577"}
{"prompt":"58 + 2 + 95","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 2) - 27","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"67 + (84 - 2) * 6","answer":"559"}
{"prompt":"100 - 100 * 4","answer":"-300"}
{"prompt":"79 + 72","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"70 - (2 + 7) * 4","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"3 - 76","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"12 * 40","answer":"480"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 4) + 8 * ((60 * 4) - 2)","answer":"1901"}
{"prompt":"21 - 52","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"67 - (26 * 3 + 6)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"69 - 72","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"82 - 15 * 10","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"8 - 7 * (51 - 4 * 7)","answer":"-153"}
{"prompt":"30 + 61 - 8","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"63 * 7 - 28 + 4","answer":"417"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 3) * 10) - 36 * 1 * 10","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"53 * 5 + 2 * 51","answer":"367"}
{"prompt":"62 + 10 - 92","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"9 - 2 * 10 * 42","answer":"-831"}
{"prompt":"76 * (43 * 2) + 6","answer":"6542"}
{"prompt":"36 + 88","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"30 - 10 * 52","answer":"-490"}
{"prompt":"95 * 9 * 87 - 8 * 1","answer":"74377"}
{"prompt":"25 * (10 - 6)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"63 + 13","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"58 - (17 + 3)","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"31 * (3 * 4) - 1","answer":"371"}
{"prompt":"64 + (32 + 2) + 6","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"43 - 8 + 4 + 93","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"37 - 25","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"30 + ((63 + 1) + 6)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 6) - 35","answer":"463"}
{"prompt":"60 + 5 + 7 - ((77 + 1) * 7)","answer":"-474"}
{"prompt":"((11 * 5) + 1) + 71 * 1 + 2","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"(75 - 7) + (6 - 1)","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"11 - 95 - 8","answer":"-92"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 7) + 88 - 3","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"12 + 18 + 9","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 6) - 77","answer":"277"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 2) + 49","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(88 + 4) + 98","answer":"190"}
{"prompt":"2 - (1 + 1)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"3 + (18 - 9 - 5)","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 7) * 49","answer":"1715"}
{"prompt":"81 + 32","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"30 + 7","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 7) + 92","answer":"232"}
{"prompt":"32 * (91 * 2)","answer":"5824"}
{"prompt":"11 + 5 - 50","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"79 - 6 - 41","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"((60 * 8) + 10) - 56","answer":"434"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 7 - 9) + (45 - 10)","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 2 * 9) * 66 + 4","answer":"90292"}
{"prompt":"((91 - 4) - 10) - 83","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"14 * (25 - 9)","answer":"224"}
{"prompt":"99 + (85 + 5)","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 9 * 8) + (55 - 2) - 9","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"64 * (57 + 7) * 5","answer":"20480"}
{"prompt":"94 + 8 * ((87 * 3) - 9)","answer":"2110"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 6) + 3 - 82 - 10 + 10","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"41 - 9 + 5 * (65 * 9)","answer":"2957"}
{"prompt":"70 - (8 + 1 + 8)","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"66 - 2 - 23","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 5) - 2","answer":"268"}
{"prompt":"56 * 3 + (34 * 8) * 7","answer":"2072"}
{"prompt":"86 - 73","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 4 * 5) + 67","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"59 * 94","answer":"5546"}
{"prompt":"25 + 56","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"65 + (29 * 7 + 7)","answer":"275"}
{"prompt":"((96 + 3) * 2) + 79","answer":"277"}
{"prompt":"93 - 24","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"73 * (21 * 7) - 5","answer":"10726"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 8) * (71 - 2) - 9","answer":"4683"}
{"prompt":"40 * 52 + 6","answer":"2086"}
{"prompt":"100 * 94 * 10","answer":"94000"}
{"prompt":"33 + (10 - 8) - 7","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"67 * 79","answer":"5293"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 3) + 12","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"36 + 48","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"67 - 48","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"21 * 36","answer":"756"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 9) + 60","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"77 + 70 - 3 - 1","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"56 * 1 - 5 * (98 + 6)","answer":"-464"}
{"prompt":"2 + (66 + 8)","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(58 * 8) + 73","answer":"537"}
{"prompt":"44 * (95 + 10)","answer":"4620"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 9) - 32","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"20 - 6 * (40 - 5) - 7","answer":"-197"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 10) * 7 - 84","answer":"6076"}
{"prompt":"23 - 100","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"16 * 39 + 4","answer":"628"}
{"prompt":"74 + (70 + 1 * 7)","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"((74 - 9) - 6) - 97 + 6","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"51 * (14 - 2) * 9","answer":"5508"}
{"prompt":"((7 * 10) - 5) - (58 - 8 + 8)","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"5 + 5 + 45","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"84 + (76 * 10)","answer":"844"}
{"prompt":"77 * 22","answer":"1694"}
{"prompt":"72 + 75","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"88 - 4 * 19 * 6","answer":"-368"}
{"prompt":"42 * (40 * 7)","answer":"11760"}
{"prompt":"21 + 3 + 53","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"60 - 60","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"((59 - 2) * 8) - 59","answer":"397"}
{"prompt":"75 - 4 * 7 * (39 * 2)","answer":"-2109"}
{"prompt":"71 * 60","answer":"4260"}
{"prompt":"89 + 4 - 9 * (12 - 9)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"((2 - 10) - 6) - 55 - 4","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"(65 * 10) + (36 + 2) - 6","answer":"682"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 2) + 37","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 2) - 50","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"89 - 80","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"20 * 5 * 6","answer":"600"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 9) * (84 - 1) * 9","answer":"262197"}
{"prompt":"24 + 2 - 9 * 30","answer":"-244"}
{"prompt":"27 * (8 + 2 + 8)","answer":"486"}
{"prompt":"((49 - 5) + 6) + 99 - 2","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"15 - 8 - 1 * 22","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"58 * (18 * 2)","answer":"2088"}
{"prompt":"4 * 9 * (9 + 5 * 9)","answer":"1944"}
{"prompt":"6 - 3 - 5 + (100 + 5)","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"((3 * 6) - 1) - (63 - 8)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"(62 - 10) * 44","answer":"2288"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 8) + 6 + (48 - 4)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"86 + 6 * 3 - 7 - 8 + 9","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 4) * 95","answer":"30020"}
{"prompt":"77 - 42","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"74 - 87","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"2 * (47 + 7 - 8)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"69 - 7 * 6 + 53","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"3 - (37 + 5) + 2","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"24 + (95 * 10 * 9)","answer":"8574"}
{"prompt":"63 + 50 + 6","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"54 - 33","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"((95 * 2) + 6) + (51 * 8)","answer":"604"}
{"prompt":"53 + 64","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"50 * 6 - (52 - 1)","answer":"249"}
{"prompt":"35 * 63","answer":"2205"}
{"prompt":"16 * 55 * 1","answer":"880"}
{"prompt":"60 * 36 + 8 * 4","answer":"2192"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 1 - 3) - 26","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"97 + 31 - 8 + 5","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 10) + ((85 * 6) - 4)","answer":"986"}
{"prompt":"35 + 5 - 62","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"92 * 26","answer":"2392"}
{"prompt":"48 - 6 - 5 + 71 - 5","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"99 - 55","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"3 + 57","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"27 * (19 - 8 - 5)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"21 + 89 * 1 * 2","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"91 - (90 * 5 + 10)","answer":"-369"}
{"prompt":"32 * 3 - (44 - 1 - 1)","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"76 * 43","answer":"3268"}
{"prompt":"47 - 87","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"81 + ((53 * 7) * 8)","answer":"3049"}
{"prompt":"80 + (98 - 8 + 6)","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 6) + 5 + (63 - 9)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 9) - 10 + ((40 * 10) - 1)","answer":"1055"}
{"prompt":"(32 + 5) - 3 - (50 + 1) * 9","answer":"-425"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 6) + 67","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 8) - 1 + 39","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"90 - 16","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"59 * (72 + 8) * 6","answer":"28320"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 1) + 31","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"59 - 24","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"42 + (47 - 2)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"75 + 71","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"78 + 46 * 10","answer":"538"}
{"prompt":"36 * 99 + 2","answer":"3566"}
{"prompt":"((49 + 10) * 6) - (74 + 6 - 9)","answer":"283"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 6) * 62","answer":"1426"}
{"prompt":"27 * 14","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"29 * 8","answer":"232"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 8) + 10","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"82 * 53","answer":"4346"}
{"prompt":"9 * 19","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"((76 * 2) - 1) - 14","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 7 * 1) * 44","answer":"9240"}
{"prompt":"59 + 3","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"49 + 9 + 9 - 57","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 2) * (83 * 8) - 3","answer":"112877"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 4) - 6 + (92 * 7)","answer":"702"}
{"prompt":"65 * 95","answer":"6175"}
{"prompt":"92 * 57","answer":"5244"}
{"prompt":"34 * 87","answer":"2958"}
{"prompt":"60 * 18","answer":"1080"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 3 * 5) - ((55 * 7) + 10)","answer":"-318"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 9) + 69 + 5","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"95 * 40","answer":"3800"}
{"prompt":"66 + 1 * (22 + 7)","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"32 - (53 * 7)","answer":"-339"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 1 - 1) - ((34 * 9) + 2)","answer":"-302"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 3) * 1 - 69","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"83 + 10 - 6 * 83","answer":"-405"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 4 - 1) + (71 - 2)","answer":"428"}
{"prompt":"((44 - 10) - 6) + (14 * 1) + 3","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"75 + 73 + 1","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 4 - 3) * 37","answer":"1739"}
{"prompt":"85 + 8","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"78 - (100 + 5 * 5)","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"((79 + 3) + 5) + ((31 * 8) - 8)","answer":"327"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 10) - 3 + (54 - 8 * 3)","answer":"497"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 5) * 39","answer":"13065"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 5) - 93 + 1","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 2) - 4 + 86","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"99 - 9 * 2 * (81 - 7 - 8)","answer":"-1089"}
{"prompt":"65 + ((96 + 5) * 6)","answer":"671"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 9 + 6) * 21","answer":"16569"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 1) + 1","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"45 * (65 + 9 - 4)","answer":"3150"}
{"prompt":"15 + 5 * 10 - 94","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"77 - 84","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"97 - (50 + 7)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"6 - (23 * 5) * 3","answer":"-339"}
{"prompt":"60 + 61 - 10","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"12 - 2 - 50","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"87 + 94 - 9 - 3","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 7 * 1) + 32","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"62 * 71","answer":"4402"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 2) * 43","answer":"2408"}
{"prompt":"((49 - 4) + 1) + (24 + 7)","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"30 - 62","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"76 * (33 * 5 - 5)","answer":"12160"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 9) + 1 * 54","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 9) * 80 + 5","answer":"2405"}
{"prompt":"(97 - 8) + 35","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"63 * (70 - 7)","answer":"3969"}
{"prompt":"85 + 8 - 85 + 10","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"((65 * 3) + 2) + (1 + 4)","answer":"202"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 2) - (34 + 3)","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 1) * 6 - 5 * 9","answer":"249"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 8) + 46 * 7 - 2","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"56 - 20","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 10) * 4 + 71 + 2 - 6","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"100 - 57 + 8","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 6) - ((64 - 3) - 9)","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"1 - (55 * 2) - 3","answer":"-112"}
{"prompt":"69 * ((88 + 7) * 8)","answer":"52440"}
{"prompt":"((43 + 1) - 7) - 26","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 8 * 2) * (47 * 7)","answer":"25991"}
{"prompt":"87 - 97","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"2 * 84","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 6 - 10) * 82","answer":"574"}
{"prompt":"46 * (8 * 7 * 6)","answer":"15456"}
{"prompt":"35 + 10 - 54","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"8 + 10 * 83 + 1","answer":"839"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 1) - (17 - 10) * 4","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"16 * 16 * 8","answer":"2048"}
{"prompt":"72 + 9 * 5 + 91","answer":"208"}
{"prompt":"54 - (16 + 2) * 5","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"10 * 10 * 8 * (13 + 6) * 7","answer":"106400"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 8) + 32","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"15 + 6 + 3 + 38","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"21 - 37","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 2) * 2 * 93 - 3 - 6","answer":"3525"}
{"prompt":"80 - 30","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"2 * 3 * 81","answer":"486"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 6) + 2 + 4","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"26 - 43","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"50 - ((39 * 5) * 4)","answer":"-730"}
{"prompt":"32 * 44","answer":"1408"}
{"prompt":"34 - 65","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"29 * 2 - 11","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"((32 + 3) - 5) * (31 * 4 + 3)","answer":"3810"}
{"prompt":"5 * 10 + 80 - 8","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"88 - 44","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"61 - 1 - 10 - 75","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"62 + 3 * 2 - 35","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 9 * 1) + (34 - 1) - 3","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"7 - 28","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 5 * 10) * 98","answer":"1862"}
{"prompt":"((43 + 4) + 6) - 71","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 10) * ((63 - 1) + 6)","answer":"1768"}
{"prompt":"(79 - 2) * ((97 - 2) - 8)","answer":"6699"}
{"prompt":"49 * 99","answer":"4851"}
{"prompt":"47 * 18","answer":"846"}
{"prompt":"82 * 78","answer":"6396"}
{"prompt":"62 * 77","answer":"4774"}
{"prompt":"1 + 2 - 74","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"6 * 5","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"23 - 50","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"14 - 70","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 7) * 30","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 1) * ((83 + 9) - 8)","answer":"7056"}
{"prompt":"52 - 10 * 33 * 10","answer":"-3248"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 5) * 15","answer":"2775"}
{"prompt":"91 * 12","answer":"1092"}
{"prompt":"((87 - 7) + 1) + 10","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"93 * 27 - 9","answer":"2502"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 7) - (65 + 2 * 7)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"50 * (43 + 10)","answer":"2650"}
{"prompt":"33 - 4 + 5 + 26","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"58 * 2 + 6 + 34","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 3) * 8 + 24","answer":"520"}
{"prompt":"40 + 84","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 8) + 8 + (87 + 10)","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"37 * 7 - 63","answer":"196"}
{"prompt":"55 + 11 - 4","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 2) * (87 * 5) - 5","answer":"27835"}
{"prompt":"11 * 9 + 8 * 88 + 10","answer":"813"}
{"prompt":"4 - (93 * 8)","answer":"-740"}
{"prompt":"3 - 77","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"20 * 45","answer":"900"}
{"prompt":"34 * (73 - 6)","answer":"2278"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 8) + 2 - 35","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 7) - 6 - (72 * 1 - 10)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"24 * 83","answer":"1992"}
{"prompt":"10 - 1 + (79 * 3)","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"1 + (90 - 5) * 5","answer":"426"}
{"prompt":"36 * 10 * 20","answer":"7200"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 4) + 75","answer":"203"}
{"prompt":"80 + 11","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"48 + 3 + 47","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 2 + 8) * 13 + 6 + 9","answer":"2615"}
{"prompt":"61 * 8 * 24","answer":"11712"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 1) * (48 - 9) + 1","answer":"235"}
{"prompt":"((72 * 1) + 9) * 23","answer":"1863"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 6) + 67 + 6","answer":"361"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 3) - 7 * (49 * 7) * 1","answer":"-2290"}
{"prompt":"93 * 78 + 2 - 5","answer":"7251"}
{"prompt":"21 + 3 + 1 - 12","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 8) + 5 + (36 - 8)","answer":"393"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 1) * 20","answer":"280"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 9 - 9) + 34","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"10 - (81 + 5)","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"59 * ((8 + 9) + 7)","answer":"1416"}
{"prompt":"17 + (42 - 9)","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"((71 + 2) + 10) - 62","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"100 - 10 - (87 - 1) * 8","answer":"-598"}
{"prompt":"92 * (14 * 8)","answer":"10304"}
{"prompt":"42 - 32","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"56 - 28","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"39 + 4","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"((36 * 7) - 4) * 18","answer":"4464"}
{"prompt":"79 - (18 - 1) * 1","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"40 * 3 - 85","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 7 * 5) * 9","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"56 - 69","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"36 + 12","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 7) + (13 - 1)","answer":"411"}
{"prompt":"47 - 47 * 3","answer":"-94"}
{"prompt":"3 - (61 - 5)","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"46 + (13 * 10) * 6","answer":"826"}
{"prompt":"27 * 4 + 26","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"93 + 7 * 96","answer":"765"}
{"prompt":"68 + (54 * 3) * 9","answer":"1526"}
{"prompt":"92 * 30 + 8 * 3","answer":"2784"}
{"prompt":"25 + ((6 + 7) + 7)","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 8) + 7 + 72","answer":"783"}
{"prompt":"35 - (59 - 10) + 9","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"80 - (13 + 1) - 8","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"94 - 71","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"24 - ((55 - 3) - 3)","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 3) + 9 - 62 + 6","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"25 - 19","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"63 - 88","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"43 - 11","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 5) * (100 + 3) + 4","answer":"9068"}
{"prompt":"34 * 2 * 30 - 6","answer":"2034"}
{"prompt":"93 + 4 + (49 * 4)","answer":"293"}
{"prompt":"66 * 41","answer":"2706"}
{"prompt":"95 + (20 * 1)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"42 - 8 - ((64 + 9) * 4)","answer":"-258"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 6) * 66 - 6","answer":"3624"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 8) - 29 + 4","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 10) + 78","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 6) - (9 - 8)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"33 * 7 * 28 + 6","answer":"6474"}
{"prompt":"42 - 4","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"57 - 44","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"16 - 10 - 57 + 5","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"12 + 6 * 51 + 5 * 7","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"63 + 7 - 8 - 75","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"89 * (97 + 4 - 5)","answer":"8544"}
{"prompt":"64 * 1 + (26 * 10) + 1","answer":"325"}
{"prompt":"49 * 5 + 51","answer":"296"}
{"prompt":"39 * 17","answer":"663"}
{"prompt":"13 + 1","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"18 + 10 * 4 - 63","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 6) - 45","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"71 * 82","answer":"5822"}
{"prompt":"((8 - 7) - 4) * 40","answer":"-120"}
{"prompt":"70 * 54","answer":"3780"}
{"prompt":"((30 + 1) * 5) * 50","answer":"7750"}
{"prompt":"87 * 7 - 20","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"62 * 41","answer":"2542"}
{"prompt":"60 * 9","answer":"540"}
{"prompt":"38 - 74","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 10 * 5) + (73 - 6 * 5)","answer":"3993"}
{"prompt":"53 + 10 * 1 + (51 - 5 * 3)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"39 + 9 - (40 - 1 - 9)","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 8) + 5 + 20 * 3","answer":"769"}
{"prompt":"89 - 23 * 1","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"26 - (57 - 1) * 7","answer":"-366"}
{"prompt":"80 - 9 * 6 + 8","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"87 - 49","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 5) + 6 + 68 + 7","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 10 * 4) - (56 * 1 + 8)","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"67 * ((72 - 5) + 2)","answer":"4623"}
{"prompt":"48 * (31 * 2 * 5)","answer":"14880"}
{"prompt":"17 + (85 + 6)","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"56 - 19","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"28 + 30","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"44 * 9 * (100 * 1)","answer":"39600"}
{"prompt":"5 * (26 + 6 * 4)","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"63 - 59","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 6) + 89","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 7) + (29 - 6 * 6)","answer":"623"}
{"prompt":"38 - 1","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"54 - 44","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"75 * 97 * 2","answer":"14550"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 4) - 88 + 6","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"82 + 34 * 10","answer":"422"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 6) * 4","answer":"2184"}
{"prompt":"39 + (12 + 8)","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"51 * 73","answer":"3723"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 8) * 4 * 3","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"1 + 57","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"57 * 2 - (58 * 2 - 7)","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"24 - 60 + 10 + 6","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 10 * 7) - ((47 + 6) * 5)","answer":"-97"}
{"prompt":"95 * 8 * (36 - 8)","answer":"21280"}
{"prompt":"2 * ((73 * 9) - 5)","answer":"1304"}
{"prompt":"46 - 84 * 10","answer":"-794"}
{"prompt":"10 * 7","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 4) + (3 + 9 - 9)","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"((43 * 8) - 3) - 37","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 3) * 2 + (57 + 8) - 1","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"16 + 9 * 41","answer":"385"}
{"prompt":"36 + (2 * 8)","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"80 + 30","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"8 + 88","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"28 * 10 * (86 - 8)","answer":"21840"}
{"prompt":"80 + 95","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"86 - 88","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"60 + ((33 - 2) + 4)","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"68 + ((58 + 4) - 3)","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"44 - 88","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"22 + 32","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"5 - (39 - 1)","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 6) - (62 - 7 + 2)","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"22 + 2 - 88","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"49 * 72","answer":"3528"}
{"prompt":"96 - 92","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"6 + 75","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"11 - 55","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"42 * 2 - 5 + 38","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(65 * 9 - 5) - 90 + 9 * 9","answer":"571"}
{"prompt":"13 - 95","answer":"-82"}
{"prompt":"95 - 1 - (39 - 4) + 6","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 9 * 7) - 59","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"87 - 7","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"3 - 35","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"30 * (42 - 3)","answer":"1170"}
{"prompt":"68 + 3 - 31","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 1 - 6) + (97 + 10)","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 6) * 6 - 9 - 2","answer":"385"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 10 + 9) + 95 * 1","answer":"212"}
{"prompt":"60 - 69","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"69 + (76 * 10)","answer":"829"}
{"prompt":"37 * 39 + 2","answer":"1445"}
{"prompt":"94 + 78","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"32 + 92 - 7","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"29 + 40 + 7","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"64 + 43","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"84 * 95","answer":"7980"}
{"prompt":"47 + (54 - 6 - 5)","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"94 - 7 + 8 + (91 + 2)","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"65 * (72 + 3 - 2)","answer":"4745"}
{"prompt":"87 * 41","answer":"3567"}
{"prompt":"13 - 79","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"5 - 18 + 8 - 1","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"44 * 48","answer":"2112"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 8) + 6 + (23 - 1)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"((24 + 4) - 9) - (33 + 2) - 6","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"62 + 7 * 7 * 78","answer":"3884"}
{"prompt":"99 - (77 + 1)","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 2 * 1) - 62","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"76 + ((8 * 7) * 8)","answer":"524"}
{"prompt":"91 * 46","answer":"4186"}
{"prompt":"10 + 57 - 6","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"43 * 77","answer":"3311"}
{"prompt":"49 - 16","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 1) - 5 * 18","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"40 * ((7 * 5) - 5)","answer":"1200"}
{"prompt":"96 + (45 - 8)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 7) - (45 + 8) - 6","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"25 - 40","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"56 - (49 - 10 - 3)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 1) * 5 * (39 - 9)","answer":"600"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 6) + 80","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"76 * ((58 * 4) - 8)","answer":"17024"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 3 - 9) * 25","answer":"5475"}
{"prompt":"98 * 57","answer":"5586"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 7) * 3 - 10","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"94 * (66 * 1)","answer":"6204"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 5 - 9) * 79","answer":"1659"}
{"prompt":"10 + 1 - 9 * (28 * 7)","answer":"-1753"}
{"prompt":"87 * 2","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"15 + 42 * 5","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 3) + 56 * 6 * 4","answer":"1366"}
{"prompt":"88 - 52","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"67 * 83","answer":"5561"}
{"prompt":"62 - 19 * 6","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"9 * 47 * 3 + 1","answer":"1270"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 2) + 4 - (50 + 4 * 3)","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"17 - 42","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 9) * (1 + 8)","answer":"585"}
{"prompt":"93 - 50","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"47 * 20","answer":"940"}
{"prompt":"45 + 2 * 4 * 70","answer":"605"}
{"prompt":"71 * 1 + 2 + ((81 * 4) * 2)","answer":"721"}
{"prompt":"36 * (34 * 4)","answer":"4896"}
{"prompt":"85 * 4","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"77 + 4","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"65 - ((93 - 3) - 3)","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"91 * 50","answer":"4550"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 7) + 63","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"45 + 79 + 9","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 3) + 17","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"39 - 53 * 8","answer":"-385"}
{"prompt":"12 + (49 + 8 + 8)","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"58 * 9 - 55 * 9","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"77 - 44","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 4 * 8) + (4 + 8) - 1","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"64 * (80 + 3 * 9)","answer":"6848"}
{"prompt":"16 + 1 + 53","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"87 * (95 * 1)","answer":"8265"}
{"prompt":"86 * 93","answer":"7998"}
{"prompt":"88 * (26 + 7) - 6","answer":"2898"}
{"prompt":"36 - (85 * 9)","answer":"-729"}
{"prompt":"49 * 5 - 7 - 98","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 2) - (88 - 4) * 9","answer":"-678"}
{"prompt":"95 * 26","answer":"2470"}
{"prompt":"63 + 85","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"62 * (85 * 9)","answer":"47430"}
{"prompt":"13 + (32 * 4)","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"57 * 96 * 6 + 3","answer":"32835"}
{"prompt":"32 - 46","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"84 - 69","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"17 - (21 - 1)","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((45 - 3) + 2)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 5) - 52","answer":"223"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 3) + 4 - 29","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"48 + ((77 * 5) - 5)","answer":"428"}
{"prompt":"34 * 57","answer":"1938"}
{"prompt":"96 + ((86 * 8) * 9)","answer":"6288"}
{"prompt":"15 + 60 * 4","answer":"255"}
{"prompt":"((35 - 3) - 8) * 71 + 1","answer":"1705"}
{"prompt":"28 + 3 * 10 - 73","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1) - (80 * 2)","answer":"-123"}
{"prompt":"80 * ((73 * 4) + 2)","answer":"23520"}
{"prompt":"32 + 63","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"68 * 28 + 5","answer":"1909"}
{"prompt":"78 + 9 - 8 + 75","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 3) + 8 + 2","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"27 * 10 * 82","answer":"22140"}
{"prompt":"78 * 37 - 9","answer":"2877"}
{"prompt":"27 + 29 * 4 + 7","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"65 + 10 - 20","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"78 * 92","answer":"7176"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 4 - 9) * (14 - 10)","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"35 * 4 + 9 + 79","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"46 + (100 - 10)","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 7) * 23","answer":"1449"}
{"prompt":"4 * 91","answer":"364"}
{"prompt":"28 + (2 + 3)","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"17 - 18 + 3 + 6","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"76 * 1 + 83","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"51 * 83 - 10","answer":"4223"}
{"prompt":"23 * 84","answer":"1932"}
{"prompt":"97 + 5 + 7 * 13","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"89 + 3 + 9 * 44","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"29 + ((7 * 5) * 6)","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"35 + 24","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"27 * 80","answer":"2160"}
{"prompt":"58 + 2 + 56 * 6","answer":"396"}
{"prompt":"89 - 6 - 73 * 2","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"73 - 5 * 7 * 42 * 8","answer":"-11687"}
{"prompt":"59 * 32","answer":"1888"}
{"prompt":"16 - (46 + 2)","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"43 - 4 + 65","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"77 * (18 * 2) * 1","answer":"2772"}
{"prompt":"95 - 38","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"86 * 7 * (90 + 3)","answer":"55986"}
{"prompt":"19 * 97","answer":"1843"}
{"prompt":"23 + 60 - 7","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"17 * 1 + 59","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 5) - 75","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 5 + 10) + ((27 + 4) + 3)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 1) * 7 * 74 + 7","answer":"8813"}
{"prompt":"55 - 5 + 10 * (21 + 4)","answer":"300"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 5) + 25 + 1 * 1","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 3 - 6) * 57","answer":"1938"}
{"prompt":"10 - 41","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 7) * 55","answer":"1815"}
{"prompt":"66 + 4 + 89 + 10","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 10) - 54","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"26 - 70","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"19 + 31","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"83 - 53","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"61 - (47 * 10 - 6)","answer":"-403"}
{"prompt":"14 + (27 - 9) + 1","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 9) * 1 - 74","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"15 + 4 * 66","answer":"279"}
{"prompt":"18 + ((27 - 3) - 5)","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 1) * 31","answer":"2449"}
{"prompt":"54 * 13","answer":"702"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 9) * 33","answer":"2409"}
{"prompt":"96 * 7 + 16","answer":"688"}
{"prompt":"68 - (78 + 9) - 9","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"4 * 63 * 2","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"11 - 44","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"72 + 4 * 7 - 79","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"((57 * 5) * 2) - 58","answer":"512"}
{"prompt":"82 - 9","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"83 + 1 + (67 + 1 - 6)","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"((41 * 9) - 8) * 66","answer":"23826"}
{"prompt":"97 + 2 + ((2 - 5) - 7)","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(45 - 7) + 34","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"89 - 10 - 37","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 6 * 1) - ((52 * 8) + 3)","answer":"-358"}
{"prompt":"((49 - 2) + 4) * 29 + 1","answer":"1480"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 7) + 37 * 2 * 7","answer":"1218"}
{"prompt":"11 - 87 - 1","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"89 * 98","answer":"8722"}
{"prompt":"37 - 5 - 9 * 92","answer":"-796"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 9) + 9 - 69","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"64 * (32 - 8)","answer":"1536"}
{"prompt":"61 - 9","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"41 + 20 - 7","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 8) + 9) + 50 - 6","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 10) - (40 + 7 + 4)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"76 * 5 + 9 - 95 + 7 * 10","answer":"364"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 2) + 8 * 68","answer":"614"}
{"prompt":"90 + 7 - 2 + 87 - 3","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 1 + 4) * 78 + 1 * 4","answer":"6634"}
{"prompt":"78 * 3 * 4 - 1","answer":"935"}
{"prompt":"((18 + 10) + 6) + 51 * 8","answer":"442"}
{"prompt":"50 + 89 - 8","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"46 * 46","answer":"2116"}
{"prompt":"29 * 8","answer":"232"}
{"prompt":"58 + 12 - 7","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"74 * 7","answer":"518"}
{"prompt":"35 * 74","answer":"2590"}
{"prompt":"((78 * 1) - 4) + 84","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 9) * ((85 * 5) - 8)","answer":"183897"}
{"prompt":"51 + 5 - 8 + 3","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"39 - 41","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"8 * (70 * 5)","answer":"2800"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 4) * (72 - 4)","answer":"5712"}
{"prompt":"47 + 15","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 10) * 46","answer":"1334"}
{"prompt":"19 - ((11 * 3) * 8)","answer":"-245"}
{"prompt":"(58 - 6) + 23","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"6 * 84","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 7) * 86","answer":"688"}
{"prompt":"79 - 29","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(97 - 7) - 3","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"((4 * 10) * 10) + (92 - 6)","answer":"486"}
{"prompt":"32 - 41","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 6) - 4 - 26","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"55 + 56","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"28 + 3 * 2 + 91","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(58 - 7 - 1) - 80","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"65 + 5","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"67 * 8 * ((52 - 3) * 3)","answer":"78792"}
{"prompt":"((23 + 10) - 3) * 89","answer":"2670"}
{"prompt":"38 - 10 + ((48 - 4) + 5)","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"26 * 2 * 2 - (9 * 6)","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"31 + 46 + 1 + 6","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"91 * ((39 * 2) - 3)","answer":"6825"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 3 + 7) * 75","answer":"13350"}
{"prompt":"3 + 8 - 32 - 10 * 6","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"87 - 3","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"28 + 6 + 8 + (49 * 5)","answer":"287"}
{"prompt":"100 + 74 + 8 + 8","answer":"190"}
{"prompt":"9 * 29","answer":"261"}
{"prompt":"31 - 12 * 9","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"8 + 85 * 10","answer":"858"}
{"prompt":"82 - 4 * 33","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 6) + 2 + 65","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 6) - 51","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"45 * 1","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"87 - 5 + 95 * 5","answer":"557"}
{"prompt":"61 - 2","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"17 - 46","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"92 * 10 + 7 + (64 - 10)","answer":"981"}
{"prompt":"((47 - 8) * 8) * 37","answer":"11544"}
{"prompt":"88 * 4","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"16 + 4 * 9 + 49 - 7","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"83 + 51 * 7","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 9) + 63 * 3","answer":"621"}
{"prompt":"36 - ((20 - 10) - 4)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 3) * 3 * 10 + 10","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"4 * 36 * 6","answer":"864"}
{"prompt":"56 * 61","answer":"3416"}
{"prompt":"32 + 18","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"64 * 61","answer":"3904"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 7 + 5) - (10 * 8)","answer":"275"}
{"prompt":"55 + 4 - (43 + 4)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 2) + (84 + 8)","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(68 * 10 - 9) + 22","answer":"693"}
{"prompt":"((49 + 7) - 5) + 37","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 7) - 10 + 58","answer":"307"}
{"prompt":"4 * 96","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"12 + 28","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 5 - 6) * 97","answer":"9409"}
{"prompt":"84 + 34 * 8 - 3","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"47 + 7 - 5 + 91","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"80 * 26 + 8","answer":"2088"}
{"prompt":"8 * 3 + 52 - 4","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"46 + 73","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"40 + (4 * 8)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"78 - 77 - 10","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"22 * (90 + 8)","answer":"2156"}
{"prompt":"31 + 19","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"39 - 2 + (7 - 5)","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"71 - 32","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"41 - 15","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"((25 + 5) * 3) + 69 * 9","answer":"711"}
{"prompt":"48 - 7 - (31 - 6) - 6","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"83 - 86","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"94 * 95 + 8","answer":"8938"}
{"prompt":"29 * (94 - 6) * 10","answer":"25520"}
{"prompt":"19 - (13 - 2)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"13 - 93","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"86 * 35","answer":"3010"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 10 * 5) + 24","answer":"2074"}
{"prompt":"97 - 10","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"87 - 56 * 2","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"75 - 77 - 10 * 9","answer":"-92"}
{"prompt":"24 + 19","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"44 + 95","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"69 * 28","answer":"1932"}
{"prompt":"85 * 50","answer":"4250"}
{"prompt":"92 * 66 + 10 + 6","answer":"6088"}
{"prompt":"51 * ((80 - 3) - 10)","answer":"3417"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 10) - 24","answer":"936"}
{"prompt":"81 - (87 - 3)","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"90 + 36","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"74 + 2","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"28 + (33 * 3) * 3","answer":"325"}
{"prompt":"65 + 19","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"35 + 41 * 1","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"46 + 2 * ((85 - 8) * 10)","answer":"1586"}
{"prompt":"38 - 9 + 1 + 97","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"56 + 35 * 8","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"79 + 56","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"75 + (54 - 3) - 6","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 4) * 9 * (18 + 4) - 5","answer":"12469"}
{"prompt":"7 * 61 * 7","answer":"2989"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 1) - 3 - 70","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"16 + ((24 + 9) * 5)","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"83 * 29","answer":"2407"}
{"prompt":"21 * 12","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"86 * 93","answer":"7998"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 6 - 2) * 87","answer":"9048"}
{"prompt":"1 + 71","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"39 * (69 - 5) - 7","answer":"2489"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 6) + 6","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"45 + 6 + 8 + 43 + 10","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"71 - ((22 * 7) + 10)","answer":"-93"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 5) - 5 - 31","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"3 - 62","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"79 - 80","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"7 - 7 + (26 + 2)","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"((2 + 1) * 3) + 63","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"21 - 17","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"89 + (81 + 4)","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"17 * 15","answer":"255"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 5) * 54","answer":"3024"}
{"prompt":"89 * 9 + 16","answer":"817"}
{"prompt":"29 - (35 * 5) - 6","answer":"-152"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 3) + 8 - 76","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"80 - 2 * 7 * 13 - 3 * 1","answer":"-105"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 2 - 9) + 38","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"85 - 44","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 1 + 7) * 61","answer":"793"}
{"prompt":"81 * 31 - 7 - 3","answer":"2501"}
{"prompt":"37 - 89","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"22 - 1 + 9 + 32 + 5 + 7","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"38 * 24 + 1","answer":"913"}
{"prompt":"42 * 15","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"35 - 9 - 21","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"95 + 10 - 3 - (37 - 10) * 3","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 10) + 75 - 4 - 7","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"17 + 4 * 1 - 75","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"43 + 1 + 46","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"76 * 76 + 4 - 7","answer":"5773"}
{"prompt":"39 * (35 * 10) * 8","answer":"109200"}
{"prompt":"26 - 3 + 69","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 5 + 1) + (88 * 9) + 5","answer":"1233"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 6) + 9 + 91 - 3","answer":"283"}
{"prompt":"52 - 88","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"33 * (84 - 6) + 8","answer":"2582"}
{"prompt":"59 + 79 + 8 + 1","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 3 * 9) - 31","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"27 * 68 + 5","answer":"1841"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 6) - (99 - 10) * 8","answer":"-328"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 6) * 15 + 9 * 5","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"10 + 14","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 6) - 97","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"59 * 56","answer":"3304"}
{"prompt":"91 - 11 + 3","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"55 - (77 + 2 * 7)","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"7 * 4","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"50 + (100 - 8 - 9)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 7) - 2","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"22 + 4 - 7 + 96","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"44 * ((39 * 3) * 6)","answer":"30888"}
{"prompt":"92 + 30","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"5 * 24 * 2 * 5","answer":"1200"}
{"prompt":"61 * (59 - 3)","answer":"3416"}
{"prompt":"52 * ((64 * 3) * 4)","answer":"39936"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 5 - 6) * (30 + 1 - 3)","answer":"196"}
{"prompt":"79 - 63","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"39 - 1 - 10","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 8) * 81","answer":"5913"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 8) + (32 * 1)","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"69 + 7 + 23","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(79 + 2) * (14 * 3)","answer":"3402"}
{"prompt":"93 + 78","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"45 + 12","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"80 - 5 - ((6 * 4) * 1)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"19 - (76 - 9) + 10","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"23 - 8 - (66 * 10)","answer":"-645"}
{"prompt":"77 + 2 + 2 + (22 - 10 + 3)","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 8) + 5 * 95","answer":"572"}
{"prompt":"27 - 7 - 2 - ((11 * 1) + 10)","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"65 + 54 * 1","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"31 + 52","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 2) - 38","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 7) - (66 + 4 * 10)","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 5 + 2) * 40 * 1","answer":"3280"}
{"prompt":"77 + (46 - 10)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"82 - 7 * 1 + (59 + 9) + 7","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"78 + 95","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"51 + 84","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"74 + 66","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"73 - 72","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 7) - 5) + 11","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"((100 - 7) * 1) - 75","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"42 * (18 * 2)","answer":"1512"}
{"prompt":"11 - 5 + (17 - 8)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"4 + 89","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 8) - 29","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"51 + 7 + 77 - 6 - 5","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"48 + 66 + 4","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"88 * 70","answer":"6160"}
{"prompt":"59 - 8","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(60 + 9) * 5 - 46","answer":"299"}
{"prompt":"91 - 10 - 76 - 10","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"29 + 25","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 7) - 2 + 75","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 10 + 9) * (31 + 10)","answer":"18819"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 10) + (80 - 3 - 1)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"28 + 52","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"22 + 65 * 10","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"98 * 8","answer":"784"}
{"prompt":"17 + 86","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 7) + 44","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"95 + (61 + 5) * 7","answer":"557"}
{"prompt":"13 + 6 * 7 + (88 + 4)","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"99 + 6","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"35 + (11 + 10)","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 5 * 2) - 50","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"((75 * 10) - 10) + 77 + 8 - 7","answer":"818"}
{"prompt":"34 + 76","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"92 * 72 - 4","answer":"6620"}
{"prompt":"61 * 5 - 20","answer":"285"}
{"prompt":"81 * 94","answer":"7614"}
{"prompt":"((9 + 3) + 5) - 49","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"21 + 10 + 5 * 14 * 5","answer":"381"}
{"prompt":"93 + 35","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"((53 - 2) - 10) + ((74 * 9) * 8)","answer":"5369"}
{"prompt":"1 - ((3 + 2) * 9)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 8 * 1) + 24","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"56 - (97 - 3 * 6)","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"84 - 24 + 6 - 5","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"((53 * 9) * 4) * 18","answer":"34344"}
{"prompt":"69 - 9 * 1 * 25 - 4 - 5","answer":"-165"}
{"prompt":"53 - 100","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 9) - (83 - 7 - 6)","answer":"299"}
{"prompt":"22 * (67 * 9 * 1)","answer":"13266"}
{"prompt":"45 + 61","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 9) * (20 - 2)","answer":"14904"}
{"prompt":"44 * 2 - 1 * 22","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"95 * (79 + 1)","answer":"7600"}
{"prompt":"28 - (11 + 5) - 4","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 10) * 2 - 59","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"100 - 6 * (17 - 10) * 10","answer":"-320"}
{"prompt":"99 + 6 - (33 * 1)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"77 + 28","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"72 - 10 + 24","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"76 - (91 * 10 * 2)","answer":"-1744"}
{"prompt":"80 * 6 + 70 * 3 * 8","answer":"2160"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 10 + 3) - ((19 + 3) + 10)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"((15 + 10) + 9) * 9","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 2) + (36 * 6 - 8)","answer":"245"}
{"prompt":"66 - 70","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"48 * 86","answer":"4128"}
{"prompt":"62 * 13","answer":"806"}
{"prompt":"21 + ((52 * 7) + 9)","answer":"394"}
{"prompt":"82 * 7 * (54 + 3)","answer":"32718"}
{"prompt":"18 - (14 + 3) - 5","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"24 + 62","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"23 + 4 + 63","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"45 + 30","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"26 * 10 + 1","answer":"261"}
{"prompt":"88 * 9 - 73","answer":"719"}
{"prompt":"(44 * 4 + 4) * 26 + 3","answer":"4683"}
{"prompt":"84 - 92","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"72 - 70 - 2 * 6","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(42 * 10) - 31","answer":"389"}
{"prompt":"34 + 5 * 9 + 48","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"51 * (31 - 1) + 2","answer":"1532"}
{"prompt":"56 + 33","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 2) * (80 + 8)","answer":"4576"}
{"prompt":"97 + (18 + 1) + 6","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"25 * 7","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 3) * 83","answer":"2656"}
{"prompt":"97 - 3 - 2 - 30 + 3","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 7 + 7) * 58","answer":"21112"}
{"prompt":"75 - 42","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 4) - 7 + 61 - 9 + 8","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"86 - 16","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"21 + 6 - (65 + 6)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"6 * 7 * 20 * 10","answer":"8400"}
{"prompt":"39 + (77 + 2) + 6","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 6) - 6","answer":"582"}
{"prompt":"60 + 13","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"34 + (64 - 2) * 7","answer":"468"}
{"prompt":"73 * 2 - 100","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"13 - 69","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 2 - 1) - (56 + 4) + 8","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"((64 * 3) * 7) + 81","answer":"1425"}
{"prompt":"71 - 78","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"30 - 3 * (64 * 8)","answer":"-1506"}
{"prompt":"89 + 18 - 8","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"65 + 89","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"66 * 3 * 79","answer":"15642"}
{"prompt":"81 * 5 - (58 * 5 * 9)","answer":"-2205"}
{"prompt":"100 - 15","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 6) + 21 - 1 + 2","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"38 * 86","answer":"3268"}
{"prompt":"90 + 2 + 8 + (50 - 6 + 6)","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"97 + (53 + 6)","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"71 * ((85 - 4) * 2)","answer":"11502"}
{"prompt":"15 - 8 + 10 + 80","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 9) + 10) - ((34 * 8) + 1)","answer":"-218"}
{"prompt":"58 - ((98 + 10) - 8)","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"5 * 17","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"((51 * 6) + 4) * 94","answer":"29140"}
{"prompt":"((59 + 9) + 1) * 56","answer":"3864"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 3) - 4","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"92 - 7 + 1 * 72","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"((81 * 6) - 9) - (30 * 6) - 8","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"72 + (67 + 4)","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"87 + (44 * 8) - 1","answer":"438"}
{"prompt":"15 + 40 + 8","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"39 + 31","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"64 - 40","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 1 + 8) * 34","answer":"3332"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 8) - 9 + 3","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"39 + ((47 + 5) * 6)","answer":"351"}
{"prompt":"92 - 7","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"32 - 69","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"74 + 36","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"55 - 100","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"95 * 9 * 97","answer":"82935"}
{"prompt":"77 * (32 - 1)","answer":"2387"}
{"prompt":"45 + 1 * 11","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"83 * 8 - 42","answer":"622"}
{"prompt":"95 - 46","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"82 + 78 - 10","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"63 + 87","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"95 + 5","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"78 * 2 + 36","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"35 + 89","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 10 - 8) - 14 * 7 * 6","answer":"-489"}
{"prompt":"48 * 4","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"((90 + 4) - 9) + 48","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"96 * 2 * 67","answer":"12864"}
{"prompt":"3 + (88 + 2) - 1","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"71 * 54","answer":"3834"}
{"prompt":"5 + 52","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"79 + ((91 * 9) - 6)","answer":"892"}
{"prompt":"((1 - 10) - 2) * (3 - 6) * 4","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"20 * 52 * 8","answer":"8320"}
{"prompt":"68 * 2 - (91 * 6) * 5","answer":"-2594"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 3) * 28","answer":"2240"}
{"prompt":"48 - 83","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"18 - (6 + 4) * 5","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"89 + 29 * 3 * 10","answer":"959"}
{"prompt":"26 - 23 - 1 + 6","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"((95 - 8) * 7) - 95 - 5","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 5 + 9) - 61","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 1) * 9 * (33 + 6)","answer":"10530"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 7) * 21","answer":"1344"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 5) - 51","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"12 * (36 + 7) + 10","answer":"526"}
{"prompt":"56 * (6 * 7 - 4)","answer":"2128"}
{"prompt":"50 * 15","answer":"750"}
{"prompt":"47 + 38","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"28 + 55","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"34 * (60 * 2 + 1)","answer":"4114"}
{"prompt":"58 - 33 - 5","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"34 * (29 + 6)","answer":"1190"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 9 * 9) + (77 - 1) - 2","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"46 - 38 - 3","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"38 * 7 - 72","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 3) * 5) - (55 * 7) - 4","answer":"-134"}
{"prompt":"54 - 4 - 13 + 9","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"54 - 6 - 57","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 3) + 61","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"46 * (61 * 5) - 2","answer":"14028"}
{"prompt":"95 - 9","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 9) + 84 * 8","answer":"718"}
{"prompt":"43 * 79","answer":"3397"}
{"prompt":"((57 * 4) * 3) * 55","answer":"37620"}
{"prompt":"49 + 6 * 8 + 1","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"31 - (98 + 5 + 3)","answer":"-75"}
{"prompt":"64 - (95 - 10 - 1)","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"93 - 90","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"39 * 72","answer":"2808"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 9) + 8 * 24","answer":"489"}
{"prompt":"64 - 2 - 73","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 4 * 3) + 87","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 10) * 3 * ((47 * 4) * 2)","answer":"642960"}
{"prompt":"62 * 9 + (57 - 4)","answer":"611"}
{"prompt":"72 - 4 * 4 + 54 - 10","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 1) * 6 - 3","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 4) * 7 * 28","answer":"15484"}
{"prompt":"55 + (61 * 10)","answer":"665"}
{"prompt":"93 * 6 - 1","answer":"557"}
{"prompt":"77 * 46 + 9 * 3","answer":"3569"}
{"prompt":"13 * 22 + 10 + 10","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"34 - 69","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"31 - ((23 * 9) * 8)","answer":"-1625"}
{"prompt":"((11 - 6) - 4) - 29","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"60 + 2 - 3 + 18","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"21 + 7 + 8 - 11 * 7 - 6","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"74 + 1 * 7 + 10","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"59 - 1","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"62 * 5 - 94 * 10 - 3","answer":"-633"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 3) - 15","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"30 + 86","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"34 + 28","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"36 * ((36 - 1) - 10)","answer":"900"}
{"prompt":"10 - (61 - 4)","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"100 * 88","answer":"8800"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 4) * 7 + (27 * 7 + 10)","answer":"780"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 1) + 66","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 9) + (60 + 9 + 9)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"94 * 75 * 2","answer":"14100"}
{"prompt":"((4 * 1) * 6) - (44 + 2 * 4)","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 10) + 32","answer":"222"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 8) - (23 - 7)","answer":"496"}
{"prompt":"71 - 49","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"56 + ((58 - 1) - 9)","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"99 * 52","answer":"5148"}
{"prompt":"((70 - 1) - 5) - 93","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"87 - 71","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"45 + (85 + 4) + 8","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 8) + 93","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 1) * 8 + (67 * 2 + 2)","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"35 + 4 + 10 + 76","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"49 + 6 + 5 - 5 + 5","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"80 * 3 * 46","answer":"11040"}
{"prompt":"83 - 5 - (40 * 10)","answer":"-322"}
{"prompt":"38 - 59","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"20 - 93","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"((38 * 8) + 10) * ((3 + 8) - 9)","answer":"628"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 10) - 78","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"57 * 44","answer":"2508"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 7) * 6 - 17","answer":"2461"}
{"prompt":"47 * 43","answer":"2021"}
{"prompt":"51 * 63","answer":"3213"}
{"prompt":"73 + 39","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"65 - (20 + 10)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"19 * 43","answer":"817"}
{"prompt":"(66 * 1) - 56","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"1 - (62 + 7) + 10","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 5) - 46 - 3","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"37 * 51","answer":"1887"}
{"prompt":"20 - 64","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"82 * (47 * 2)","answer":"7708"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 7) + 63 + 6","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 8) + 9 + (79 * 8)","answer":"652"}
{"prompt":"46 + ((11 + 4) - 4)","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"72 + ((51 + 5) - 6)","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 7) * 68 + 4","answer":"344"}
{"prompt":"11 + 3","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"15 - 78","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"42 + 61 + 6 * 10","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 3) * ((90 - 8) - 4)","answer":"21528"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 4) * 8 + ((67 + 3) - 5)","answer":"849"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 8) - 45","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"87 * 44","answer":"3828"}
{"prompt":"53 - 4 - 6 - 29","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"92 + 2 * 4","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 4) - ((30 * 2) - 6)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"65 * 6 - 59 - 7","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"95 * 4 - 60","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"38 * (21 - 3) - 6","answer":"678"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 7) + 8 + 9 * 9","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"((45 + 1) * 10) - 16","answer":"444"}
{"prompt":"88 * 19 + 1","answer":"1673"}
{"prompt":"38 * 91","answer":"3458"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 1) - 7 - ((18 + 8) + 4)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"53 * 3 * 36","answer":"5724"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 2) + (61 - 2) * 8","answer":"478"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 10 * 1) - (78 * 6) - 7","answer":"-455"}
{"prompt":"77 + 34 * 10","answer":"417"}
{"prompt":"42 * 73 + 6","answer":"3072"}
{"prompt":"57 + 8 - 3 - 55","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"21 - 10 * 10 + ((76 - 9) - 9)","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"79 + (55 - 5)","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"30 * 24","answer":"720"}
{"prompt":"((2 + 2) * 4) * 7 * 5","answer":"560"}
{"prompt":"54 * 14 + 2","answer":"758"}
{"prompt":"99 * ((28 + 4) + 6)","answer":"3762"}
{"prompt":"20 + 6 - 5","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"14 * (75 * 10)","answer":"10500"}
{"prompt":"33 - ((90 + 7) - 7)","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 8) * 38","answer":"2926"}
{"prompt":"45 + (21 * 9) - 1","answer":"233"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 10) + 66 * 8","answer":"571"}
{"prompt":"100 * ((25 - 6) * 8)","answer":"15200"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 5) + 62","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 6) + 62 - 9 * 10","answer":"218"}
{"prompt":"4 + 4 + 13","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"((61 + 3) + 7) + 71","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 7 * 3) * 15","answer":"1545"}
{"prompt":"24 * 49","answer":"1176"}
{"prompt":"49 * 17","answer":"833"}
{"prompt":"54 + 39 - 2","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"62 * 7 * 10 + 71","answer":"4411"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 8) * 10 - (16 - 4) * 2","answer":"4776"}
{"prompt":"86 - 9 + 8 + 53 + 9","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"63 + 83","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"89 * 97 - 5 - 6","answer":"8622"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 7) + 38","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"75 - (15 - 4)","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"93 - 88","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 3) * 1 - 96","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"48 * 9","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"66 * 3 * 4 - 13","answer":"779"}
{"prompt":"73 + 99","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"52 * ((20 + 6) + 3)","answer":"1508"}
{"prompt":"56 + ((69 * 1) * 4)","answer":"332"}
{"prompt":"6 + 1","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 9) - ((85 + 10) + 6)","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"77 - 89","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"6 - (85 - 6) - 7","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 6) * 27 - 8 * 7","answer":"1456"}
{"prompt":"100 * ((1 + 8) + 10)","answer":"1900"}
{"prompt":"11 - 1 * 6 - (8 * 6) * 7","answer":"-331"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 6 + 10) * 93 + 1","answer":"466"}
{"prompt":"14 + 56","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"94 - 9","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"11 * 10 - 6 + 9","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 2 * 10) * 96","answer":"2976"}
{"prompt":"((66 * 6) * 8) - 49","answer":"3119"}
{"prompt":"18 + 1 + 27","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"26 + 3 + 3 * ((74 * 10) - 5)","answer":"2234"}
{"prompt":"87 * 8 + 64","answer":"760"}
{"prompt":"24 + 96 - 9 - 9","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"((20 + 9) + 5) + 98","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"27 - (68 * 9)","answer":"-585"}
{"prompt":"24 - 5 + 18","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"17 * (68 * 5 + 10)","answer":"5950"}
{"prompt":"25 * 88 - 1","answer":"2199"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 9) * 32","answer":"6624"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 10) + 29","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 9) + 1 - 40 + 7","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"7 - 90","answer":"-83"}
{"prompt":"40 * 75 - 9","answer":"2991"}
{"prompt":"69 + 56","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 5) - 6 * (68 + 6)","answer":"-347"}
{"prompt":"75 - 85","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"42 * (51 - 9)","answer":"1764"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 6 + 5) * 4","answer":"216"}
{"prompt":"99 + 78 * 5","answer":"489"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 10) * 9 + (64 - 1 - 8)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"34 + 54","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 8) * (41 * 5)","answer":"47560"}
{"prompt":"46 - 4 * 73","answer":"-246"}
{"prompt":"23 - 6 - 8 - 83 - 5 * 10","answer":"-124"}
{"prompt":"19 - 61","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"10 - 62 * 6","answer":"-362"}
{"prompt":"73 + 8 * 85","answer":"753"}
{"prompt":"53 * 9 + 5","answer":"482"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 5) * 49","answer":"3479"}
{"prompt":"28 - 3 + (99 - 1) - 7","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 8) - 3 - 39","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"61 - (59 - 9 - 8)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"14 - 10 + 7 * ((94 - 2) - 8)","answer":"592"}
{"prompt":"47 * 3","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"56 - ((11 + 8) * 9)","answer":"-115"}
{"prompt":"15 - (42 + 8)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 9) * 2 * ((81 - 10) - 4)","answer":"7504"}
{"prompt":"6 + 1 * 9 - (57 - 1 * 7)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"((97 * 3) - 8) - 75 - 10 - 5","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"89 * (79 + 5 + 10)","answer":"8366"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 10) - 94 + 6","answer":"-97"}
{"prompt":"88 - 5","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"89 - 28","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"47 - 62 * 1 * 3","answer":"-139"}
{"prompt":"10 + 8 + 7","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"((32 + 4) + 5) - 75 * 6","answer":"-409"}
{"prompt":"44 + 16","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"75 * 6 - 37 - 10","answer":"403"}
{"prompt":"89 * 68","answer":"6052"}
{"prompt":"21 + 98","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 2) - 42","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 7) * 8 - 62","answer":"666"}
{"prompt":"82 + (72 - 1)","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"53 - 42","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(82 - 1) + (31 * 4 + 8)","answer":"213"}
{"prompt":"8 * 67","answer":"536"}
{"prompt":"10 * (36 - 3 - 2)","answer":"310"}
{"prompt":"74 + ((1 - 5) - 10)","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"81 + 3 * 76 * 7","answer":"1677"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 4) * 7 + 23 * 7","answer":"217"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 10) - (77 * 3)","answer":"579"}
{"prompt":"47 * 3 + 93","answer":"234"}
{"prompt":"2 - 8 - 72","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"72 + 3 * 4 * 64 + 10","answer":"850"}
{"prompt":"42 * 4 * 51","answer":"8568"}
{"prompt":"23 - (10 + 7) - 9","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"42 * 95 * 4","answer":"15960"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 2) - 2 + 62","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"48 + 47 + 3 - 10","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"29 * 84 + 5","answer":"2441"}
{"prompt":"90 * 8 * 81 - 7","answer":"58313"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 8 - 4) - 40","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"((85 * 4) - 9) * 61","answer":"20191"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 4 * 8) - (33 - 4) - 10","answer":"825"}
{"prompt":"92 + 43 + 9","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 5) * 9 + 77 * 5","answer":"1195"}
{"prompt":"73 * 22","answer":"1606"}
{"prompt":"28 * 50","answer":"1400"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 7) - 9 * 40","answer":"-315"}
{"prompt":"94 + (100 - 7) - 8","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 10) - (98 + 8 - 3)","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"2 + 3 - (63 - 9)","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"12 - 56","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"11 * 4 * (16 + 7)","answer":"1012"}
{"prompt":"((67 - 7) + 10) * (89 + 2) * 10","answer":"63700"}
{"prompt":"96 - 3 - 9 - (62 + 7)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"8 * 3 - 39","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 10) - 10 - 17","answer":"743"}
{"prompt":"73 * 8 * 57","answer":"33288"}
{"prompt":"2 - 9 * 6 - 81","answer":"-133"}
{"prompt":"90 + ((45 * 6) - 6)","answer":"354"}
{"prompt":"13 - 10 + 26 - 2","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"100 + 7 * (40 - 6) * 4","answer":"1052"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 2 - 5) - (52 + 1) + 9","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 4) + 9 + ((33 + 4) * 5)","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 10) - (64 - 2)","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 3) * (1 - 7)","answer":"-150"}
{"prompt":"70 * 25","answer":"1750"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 2) + 4 + (6 + 3) * 8","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"17 * 18 + 5","answer":"311"}
{"prompt":"24 - 21","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"77 * (35 - 7)","answer":"2156"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 7) * 3","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"63 - 5 + 5 + 53","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 4) - 77","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"67 + 4 - 70","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"86 * 9 * 9 + 63 + 3","answer":"7032"}
{"prompt":"32 - 13 * 10 * 6","answer":"-748"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 3) - 79","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"((14 - 2) * 4) * 71","answer":"3408"}
{"prompt":"72 * 9 * 10 * 27 * 6 * 3","answer":"3149280"}
{"prompt":"((93 + 7) * 5) * 36 * 1","answer":"18000"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 7) + 48","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"75 * 10 + 10 * 49 - 7 + 1","answer":"1234"}
{"prompt":"52 + 3 + 87","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"((46 - 6) + 2) - 16 + 8","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"74 - 81","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"85 - 10 + (44 - 2)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 8) + 26 - 3","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"96 + 2 - (2 + 9) - 7","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"62 * 4 - 1 - 94","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"57 + 6 - (75 + 9)","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"31 * (2 - 1)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 4 - 4) * (23 * 10)","answer":"230"}
{"prompt":"43 + (46 + 2)","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"79 * 4","answer":"316"}
{"prompt":"86 - 27","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"70 * 7 - (47 - 8)","answer":"451"}
{"prompt":"4 + 39","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"95 * 72","answer":"6840"}
{"prompt":"27 * 66","answer":"1782"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 8) - 6 + (48 * 10 * 5)","answer":"2404"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 8) - 98","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"46 + 43","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"39 - 47","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"43 + (55 - 3 * 6)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"80 - ((33 - 8) - 9)","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 10) * 55","answer":"43450"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 1 - 6) - 21","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"54 - (59 * 1)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 9) + 18 * 4","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"10 * 10 * 6 * 58","answer":"34800"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 4) - 50","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 4) + 10 - 93 + 3","answer":"312"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 1) - 10 + 34 + 2 - 5","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"10 + 63","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"21 - 1","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"81 * 3 + (62 - 9 * 3)","answer":"278"}
{"prompt":"92 * ((32 + 5) + 4)","answer":"3772"}
{"prompt":"2 - 12 - 1 * 4","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"6 + 59","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"71 - (90 + 8 - 8)","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 3 + 10) * 60","answer":"1920"}
{"prompt":"8 * 8 + 8 * 36","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"42 + 5","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"59 * 94","answer":"5546"}
{"prompt":"((52 - 4) - 1) - 43 + 5","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 7 * 3) - (75 - 4) * 9","answer":"-559"}
{"prompt":"80 - 10 + 3","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"81 - 91","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"1 * 39","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"100 + (1 + 4)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 5) - 57","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"((31 - 3) - 3) - 78","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"90 * (5 * 2) * 3","answer":"2700"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 9 - 9) + 58","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"73 * 5 * (72 * 5)","answer":"131400"}
{"prompt":"54 - 8 * 2 - (43 - 6 - 10)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"((32 + 5) + 10) * 20","answer":"940"}
{"prompt":"((25 - 9) - 3) * 66","answer":"858"}
{"prompt":"71 - 71","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 8) + 59","answer":"315"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 1) + 2 * 47","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 10 - 7) + 12","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 4) - 76","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"95 + 41 - 5 - 8","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"4 * 3 + 2 - 29","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 9) + (1 * 2) - 10","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"62 * (1 + 2) - 7","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"47 * (44 + 4)","answer":"2256"}
{"prompt":"76 + 2 - 10 + 25","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 3) - (80 - 4)","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"69 - 80","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 9) - 4 + 47 + 8","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 7) * (59 * 9)","answer":"22302"}
{"prompt":"((16 + 2) + 5) * 14 * 1","answer":"322"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 5 * 8) + 70","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 6) + (6 + 2 * 5)","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"15 * (35 + 4) + 2","answer":"587"}
{"prompt":"12 * 10 * 30","answer":"3600"}
{"prompt":"75 * 23","answer":"1725"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 4) + 26 + 4","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 4 + 8) * 43","answer":"1849"}
{"prompt":"26 * 26","answer":"676"}
{"prompt":"26 * 10 * 2 * 3","answer":"1560"}
{"prompt":"36 * 98","answer":"3528"}
{"prompt":"((71 * 2) + 6) - 88","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 10) + (49 + 6) - 7","answer":"718"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 3) * 2 - 58","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"72 + (43 + 6)","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"43 + ((13 + 1) * 3)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"37 * 40 + 6 + 5","answer":"1491"}
{"prompt":"31 - 1 * 9","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 7 - 7) - (10 + 6)","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"14 + 8 - 59 - 4 * 10","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"18 - 10 - 54","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"14 - 73","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"95 * 79","answer":"7505"}
{"prompt":"38 - (45 + 9 * 9)","answer":"-88"}
{"prompt":"100 * (51 - 2)","answer":"4900"}
{"prompt":"74 * 56","answer":"4144"}
{"prompt":"64 + 4 + 9 * 74","answer":"734"}
{"prompt":"40 + 73 - 9 + 4","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"62 + 56","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"58 - 86","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 10) + 7 - (82 - 4)","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 6) - 27 - 2","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"80 + 3 + 8","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"42 + 7","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"17 - 6 + 2 * 4","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"63 + 10 + (43 - 6)","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"88 - ((13 * 8) * 7)","answer":"-640"}
{"prompt":"42 * 28","answer":"1176"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 6) + 7 + (34 * 9 - 3)","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"22 * ((59 + 5) - 1)","answer":"1386"}
{"prompt":"(44 - 1) - 24","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"39 + 55","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(17 + 2) - (28 - 2 - 9)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"90 * 99","answer":"8910"}
{"prompt":"((4 + 10) - 10) - 71","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 1 * 9) * (53 - 5) + 2","answer":"1346"}
{"prompt":"20 - (13 + 3 + 2)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"69 * 6 * 15","answer":"6210"}
{"prompt":"60 - 26","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 2) + 4 + 71","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"61 * 9 + 8 - (78 * 2)","answer":"401"}
{"prompt":"26 - 1 - 39","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"99 * 57","answer":"5643"}
{"prompt":"9 - 4 * 88","answer":"-343"}
{"prompt":"7 + 66","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"54 + ((30 * 5) * 7)","answer":"1104"}
{"prompt":"3 * 9","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 7) - ((94 * 2) * 3)","answer":"-326"}
{"prompt":"((73 + 6) * 7) + 26","answer":"579"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 2) + 82 + 8","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"30 - 74","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"33 * (6 + 1)","answer":"231"}
{"prompt":"21 * (34 - 2)","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"59 - (75 - 10 - 7)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 3) - 7 + (97 * 9)","answer":"874"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 7) + (96 * 4)","answer":"436"}
{"prompt":"7 * 6 * 10 * (21 - 3)","answer":"7560"}
{"prompt":"56 - (46 - 5 * 4)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"28 + (36 * 2)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"9 - 14","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 5 + 3) + (71 * 7)","answer":"513"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 10 * 5) - 14","answer":"1486"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 3) + 4 * 18","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 9) + 6 + 61","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"86 + (90 - 4) + 2","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"10 - (32 * 2 - 5)","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 10 - 7) + 65","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 7 * 4) - 32","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"51 - (44 * 5)","answer":"-169"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 9 + 5) + (26 - 5)","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 6) + 40","answer":"310"}
{"prompt":"((7 - 4) - 8) - 85","answer":"-90"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 2 - 3) * (36 + 1)","answer":"6771"}
{"prompt":"100 + 5 * 99","answer":"595"}
{"prompt":"13 * 88 - 7 + 1","answer":"1138"}
{"prompt":"65 - (77 * 10)","answer":"-705"}
{"prompt":"93 - 49","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 5) - (20 - 8)","answer":"233"}
{"prompt":"4 + 91","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 6) - 96","answer":"372"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 10) + (99 * 9) + 5","answer":"967"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 9) + 43","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(42 * 9) + ((6 + 2) * 1)","answer":"386"}
{"prompt":"99 + 34","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"86 - 95","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"39 + 7 - 4","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"29 + 63","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"72 + 64","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"57 - 2 + (60 + 7 + 6)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 1) - 63","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"27 + 55","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 6) - 10 + 4","answer":"282"}
{"prompt":"81 - (94 * 4)","answer":"-295"}
{"prompt":"13 * 15","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 5) + 49","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"91 - 72","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 6) * 5 * 85 - 9","answer":"30591"}
{"prompt":"7 - 27","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"33 - (59 - 10 + 7)","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"92 + 6 * 7 + (66 * 2) - 9","answer":"257"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 7) - 7","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"80 + (19 + 9)","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 7) * 38","answer":"12768"}
{"prompt":"28 - 49","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 4) + 4 - (17 - 2)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"22 - (71 + 2 + 2)","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"((69 + 1) * 9) * 17","answer":"10710"}
{"prompt":"77 + 23","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"9 + 3 * 16","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 1) + ((85 - 5) + 6)","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"47 * 17 + 4","answer":"803"}
{"prompt":"78 - 36","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"30 * 8","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"8 + 4 + 7 * 2","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"45 * 31","answer":"1395"}
{"prompt":"8 - 6 - 30","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"30 - (30 * 8)","answer":"-210"}
{"prompt":"80 + ((13 * 10) - 9)","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 3) * (13 + 8)","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"12 + 8 + (98 + 9)","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"55 - 56","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"70 + 8 + ((77 - 5) + 5)","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 3 * 7) * 49","answer":"79233"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 6) * ((66 + 5) - 6)","answer":"4225"}
{"prompt":"38 + 51","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"10 + 5 + (36 + 5 * 2)","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"24 * (88 + 3)","answer":"2184"}
{"prompt":"98 * 11","answer":"1078"}
{"prompt":"10 * 5 + 2 - 23 * 2","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"43 * 4 + 9 * 2","answer":"190"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 2 * 2) - 76 + 8 + 5","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"50 + (21 + 8)","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 8 * 3) + 5","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"9 - 7 - 39","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"74 - 4 * 7 + 66 - 5","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"3 + (43 * 3)","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"10 + (23 - 10)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"44 - (72 + 4) * 5","answer":"-336"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 1 + 2) * 4","answer":"296"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 6 + 6) * 55 + 3 * 3","answer":"30699"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 3) * 35","answer":"1995"}
{"prompt":"60 * 7 - 60","answer":"360"}
{"prompt":"55 * 7 + 97","answer":"482"}
{"prompt":"48 + 100","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 8) * 23","answer":"874"}
{"prompt":"96 - 82","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"61 - 63","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"57 * ((31 * 10) - 5)","answer":"17385"}
{"prompt":"33 - 7 - 6 - 5","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"93 - 4 + 33","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 9) + 3 + 12 - 5","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"62 * 47 + 3 - 2","answer":"2915"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 5) + 1 + 36","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"65 * 74","answer":"4810"}
{"prompt":"73 - 77","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"91 * (75 + 1)","answer":"6916"}
{"prompt":"67 * 5 + 76","answer":"411"}
{"prompt":"60 + 35 - 7","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"((52 + 2) - 9) + 11 - 10","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"1 + 8 * (49 * 8)","answer":"3137"}
{"prompt":"20 + 6 * 10 - (92 - 1 + 3)","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 2 - 4) - 18","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"2 * ((94 * 7) + 5)","answer":"1326"}
{"prompt":"49 + 26 + 1","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"29 + 6 + ((32 * 4) + 2)","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"59 + (45 - 2 * 9)","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"67 - (27 - 4)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"59 + 52 - 4 + 1","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 10) + 49","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"51 - 2 * 52","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"90 + 5 - 10 - 66 + 4 + 5","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 4) * 3 + 90","answer":"273"}
{"prompt":"86 - 95","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"85 * 3 + 59","answer":"314"}
{"prompt":"89 - 3 * 8 - 97 * 6","answer":"-517"}
{"prompt":"81 + 32","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"10 * 10 + 10","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"72 - 34","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"98 - (99 - 1)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 9) * 56 + 10","answer":"12106"}
{"prompt":"38 - 69 - 7","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"94 - 96 + 8 - 6","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"98 * 10 + 51","answer":"1031"}
{"prompt":"41 - 59","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"38 - 77","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 4) - 24","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 6) * 36","answer":"3240"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 1) - 42","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"68 * 27","answer":"1836"}
{"prompt":"62 + 43 * 9 * 10","answer":"3932"}
{"prompt":"45 - 19 + 4","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 10) * 64","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"10 + 90","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"12 * 9 - 53 + 3","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 1) + 40","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 2) - 5 + (26 - 7)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"44 - ((64 + 4) * 6)","answer":"-364"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 6) - (49 * 1) + 9","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 8) * 46 - 5","answer":"3951"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 5 * 6) * 93","answer":"-2697"}
{"prompt":"83 * (95 + 9)","answer":"8632"}
{"prompt":"9 - 7 + 28","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 2 * 10) - 77 - 7 * 5","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"4 - 64","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 8) + 3 - 99","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"28 - 1 + 2 * 2 * 2","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"17 + 63","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"2 * 15 - 9","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"39 + 15 * 6","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"71 * 89 * 6 + 4","answer":"37918"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 2) - 9 - (98 * 2) * 4","answer":"-708"}
{"prompt":"80 * (85 + 9 - 10)","answer":"6720"}
{"prompt":"91 - (62 + 2) * 9","answer":"-485"}
{"prompt":"100 + 72","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"11 * 8 - 8 - 8","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"90 - 21 - 8","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"53 + (69 + 8)","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"9 * 6 - (43 * 4) - 10","answer":"-128"}
{"prompt":"73 + (6 + 6 * 9)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"82 * 62","answer":"5084"}
{"prompt":"19 + (58 * 9) + 6","answer":"547"}
{"prompt":"(81 + 5) - ((27 * 6) - 3)","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"28 + 99","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"13 + 7 * 33","answer":"244"}
{"prompt":"76 * 10 + 9 + 5","answer":"774"}
{"prompt":"2 + 10","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 8) - 2 * 17","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"60 - ((13 - 5) * 8)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"85 + 4 - 98","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"75 - 78 * 9","answer":"-627"}
{"prompt":"23 + ((64 - 4) * 7)","answer":"443"}
{"prompt":"50 + 4 - ((3 - 4) + 4)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"24 - 22","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"27 * 10 - 4 * 5","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 8) + (68 - 1)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 7) * 8 - (33 * 9) + 1","answer":"-136"}
{"prompt":"67 * 74","answer":"4958"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 10) * 4 - 54","answer":"2066"}
{"prompt":"18 + 66 + 1 + 4","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"14 * 9","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 7) - 9) * 21","answer":"1806"}
{"prompt":"37 - 7 * (30 - 8 + 2)","answer":"-131"}
{"prompt":"49 + 8 - (95 * 9)","answer":"-798"}
{"prompt":"87 - 66","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"49 * 7 - (58 + 5 + 2)","answer":"278"}
{"prompt":"71 + 45","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"75 * 14","answer":"1050"}
{"prompt":"63 - 63 * 6 - 2","answer":"-317"}
{"prompt":"(48 + 5) + 50 - 9","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"71 - 67 * 9 + 8","answer":"-524"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 3 - 9) * 56","answer":"4200"}
{"prompt":"79 + 5 + 9 * (41 + 4 - 9)","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"6 + 2 + 76","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"22 * 29 * 2","answer":"1276"}
{"prompt":"60 + 8 + 4","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 1 - 2) + (34 + 1)","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"8 - (13 - 6 + 2)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"82 + 47","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"10 - (27 + 8 + 2)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 10 * 3) - 58","answer":"872"}
{"prompt":"90 * 2 - 68 + 8 - 4","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"6 * 99","answer":"594"}
{"prompt":"76 - 54","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 7) + 5 * 77","answer":"382"}
{"prompt":"79 + 17","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"33 * 79 + 6","answer":"2613"}
{"prompt":"50 * 11 - 5","answer":"545"}
{"prompt":"43 - 66 - 8","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"40 * 11","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"6 + (54 - 2)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"5 - 89","answer":"-84"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 8) - (7 + 2)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"45 - 4 * 71","answer":"-239"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 7) + 59","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"75 - 25","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"67 * 89 - 1","answer":"5962"}
{"prompt":"30 + 5 * 6 - 63","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"87 + ((30 + 6) * 10)","answer":"447"}
{"prompt":"14 + 9 - 57","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"((44 * 10) * 7) + 39 * 10","answer":"3470"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 5) - 9","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"92 * (11 - 2)","answer":"828"}
{"prompt":"13 * 10 + 43","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"99 - 21","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"21 + 49","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"22 + 94 * 6","answer":"586"}
{"prompt":"69 + 2 * 89","answer":"247"}
{"prompt":"99 + 43","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 7) + 66 + 3","answer":"454"}
{"prompt":"48 + 9","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"36 * 31","answer":"1116"}
{"prompt":"100 + 1 + 34","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"97 - 39","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"99 - 95","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"56 - (59 + 3)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"57 + 88","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"94 + 8 * (83 * 1) + 10","answer":"768"}
{"prompt":"7 - (90 - 2)","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 2) * 5 * 8","answer":"2320"}
{"prompt":"23 + 5 - 4 + (67 + 2) - 9","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"20 - 6 + 2","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 4) - 7 + (50 + 7) + 4","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"30 - 28","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"94 + 54","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"62 + 68","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"41 - 8 - 33","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"87 - ((76 - 8) - 1)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"78 + 66","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"49 * 83","answer":"4067"}
{"prompt":"10 + 51","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"1 + 66 * 2","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 9 - 6) - 21 * 4 - 8","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(58 - 9) - 96 - 3","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((4 * 5) - 6)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"52 * 5 * 14","answer":"3640"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 6) + (2 - 1 * 7)","answer":"205"}
{"prompt":"93 + 12","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 10) + 1 + 35 + 4","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 3) - 48 - 4 * 6","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"87 - (20 * 9)","answer":"-93"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 8) - ((47 - 4) * 1)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 4) - 3 + (76 - 5)","answer":"364"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 3) - 4 * ((52 * 1) * 7)","answer":"-1361"}
{"prompt":"95 - 5 - 42","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((93 + 10) + 5) * (77 - 10 - 10)","answer":"6156"}
{"prompt":"4 * 7 + 88","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"62 * (97 + 9)","answer":"6572"}
{"prompt":"98 + 39","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"22 * 3 * 6 - 98","answer":"298"}
{"prompt":"27 + 67","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"44 * 8 * 43","answer":"15136"}
{"prompt":"36 - 6 * (95 + 5) * 3","answer":"-1764"}
{"prompt":"46 * 98","answer":"4508"}
{"prompt":"17 + (34 + 7)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"48 - (24 * 5)","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 10) - 10 * 28","answer":"-238"}
{"prompt":"((97 - 10) * 5) * (67 + 8)","answer":"32625"}
{"prompt":"37 * ((89 - 3) + 1)","answer":"3219"}
{"prompt":"97 * 46","answer":"4462"}
{"prompt":"68 * 5 * 1","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"73 + 37","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"21 - 91","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"38 - (26 - 6 - 10)","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(45 - 10) + (97 + 7) * 3","answer":"347"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 3) * 8 * 27","answer":"19440"}
{"prompt":"43 + 93 * 7","answer":"694"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 8) + 32","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"17 * 5 * (16 - 6)","answer":"850"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 3) * (63 + 10 + 9)","answer":"2788"}
{"prompt":"29 + 39 + 10","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"29 * (19 * 3 - 4)","answer":"1537"}
{"prompt":"80 + 5 + 74","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"68 + 3","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"((27 * 5) * 9) * 69","answer":"83835"}
{"prompt":"((44 * 5) - 5) - 83 * 9 * 5","answer":"-3520"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 6) * 8 * 87","answer":"29232"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 6 * 7) * 20","answer":"1200"}
{"prompt":"23 + 97 * 6 * 7","answer":"4097"}
{"prompt":"62 + 45","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"57 * 7 - 95 + 2","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 6) - 88","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"54 - 97","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"93 - 87","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"65 * 6 + (25 + 3)","answer":"418"}
{"prompt":"83 * 90 * 3","answer":"22410"}
{"prompt":"81 * 5 * 2 - 46 - 6","answer":"758"}
{"prompt":"93 * 17","answer":"1581"}
{"prompt":"89 - (52 - 3)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"32 - 51 - 8","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"82 - (79 - 8)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"5 * 47","answer":"235"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 8) - 36","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"((59 - 4) - 10) - (1 * 3)","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 8) * 5 + 17","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"14 - 70","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"34 - (30 + 9)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"7 - (79 - 6)","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 9) - (63 + 9)","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"37 * (46 + 7) + 3","answer":"1964"}
{"prompt":"82 * 10 - 53 - 8 - 7","answer":"752"}
{"prompt":"66 + 9 + 9 - 92 + 2","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"2 + (71 - 1)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 5) * 6 * (9 * 2) * 7","answer":"264600"}
{"prompt":"((21 - 5) * 7) + 37","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"27 - 73","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"16 - 79","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"35 + (22 + 3) - 2","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 10) - 6 + 93","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 2) - 4 - (25 - 10) + 6","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"65 - 25","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"34 - 83","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"65 - 4 - 3 - 37 + 3","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 8) * (4 - 10) + 4","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"93 - (63 + 2 + 3)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"((77 - 5) * 7) + 99","answer":"603"}
{"prompt":"86 - 16","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"41 + 51","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 4) + (73 - 2)","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"80 - 14","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"24 * 46","answer":"1104"}
{"prompt":"81 + 80","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"77 - 69","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 9) + (55 * 8 - 1)","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"((93 + 9) * 5) - 58 * 5","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"21 + 31","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"41 * 36","answer":"1476"}
{"prompt":"39 - 23","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 2) * 39","answer":"858"}
{"prompt":"((22 + 6) + 8) * 85","answer":"3060"}
{"prompt":"94 * (98 + 8 * 9)","answer":"15980"}
{"prompt":"75 * 49","answer":"3675"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 9 * 6) * 100","answer":"210600"}
{"prompt":"99 + (48 * 5)","answer":"339"}
{"prompt":"(73 * 5) + 72","answer":"437"}
{"prompt":"30 + 27","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"78 + 40 - 6","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 8 - 10) * (95 - 7)","answer":"-264"}
{"prompt":"30 + 10 + 6 * 98 + 4","answer":"632"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 2) - 68 * 7 + 3","answer":"-405"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 4) * 20 - 9","answer":"631"}
{"prompt":"98 * 44","answer":"4312"}
{"prompt":"99 + 71","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 5) - (73 + 1)","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"85 + 10 * 5 - 22 + 8 - 1","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"14 - (2 - 3 * 6)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"((43 - 7) - 4) + 22 - 6","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 2) - 10 + 86","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"34 * 2 - 91","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"7 - 52","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"((54 * 7) * 1) * 17","answer":"6426"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 2) + 97","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 4) + 42","answer":"398"}
{"prompt":"28 * 8 * 5 + 9","answer":"1129"}
{"prompt":"9 * (1 + 6 + 4)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 8) - 72","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"97 * ((50 - 4) + 4)","answer":"4850"}
{"prompt":"38 * 5 - 10","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"30 - (80 - 3)","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 3) * 9 * 92","answer":"21528"}
{"prompt":"27 + 64 - 6","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 3) - 5 + 15","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 2) + 70 - 4","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"29 + ((1 - 10) - 3)","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"80 - 4 - 56","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"((15 * 1) - 3) - 36","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"49 * 3 + (2 + 2 + 10)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 7 - 5) - 74","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"10 - (10 + 6)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 5) + 3 - 96","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"23 - ((10 + 4) - 4)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 6) * 35","answer":"2590"}
{"prompt":"((89 - 6) * 10) + 55","answer":"885"}
{"prompt":"82 + 64 * 10","answer":"722"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 5) * 68 + 5","answer":"2997"}
{"prompt":"87 - 4 * 6 - 14","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"29 * (33 + 7)","answer":"1160"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 4) * (84 + 5 - 4)","answer":"595"}
{"prompt":"43 + 10 + 100","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"23 * 3 * (26 * 8) + 10","answer":"14362"}
{"prompt":"17 + 48 * 7","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"17 - 77","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"79 - (91 * 10) + 5","answer":"-826"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 6) + 70","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"40 * 8 + 42 + 5 * 10","answer":"412"}
{"prompt":"43 + 7","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"89 * 47 * 7","answer":"29281"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 1 - 8) - 68","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"76 - 31 * 2","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"34 + 50","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(44 - 4 + 4) - (57 - 10) + 9","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"36 * (14 + 6 + 4)","answer":"864"}
{"prompt":"1 - 9 * 10 + (28 + 1)","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 2) - 2 - 2","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"26 + 40 - 3","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"((89 + 10) - 6) + 7","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"69 * 76","answer":"5244"}
{"prompt":"43 + 49","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 9) + 7 + 1","answer":"692"}
{"prompt":"60 - 62","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"52 + ((94 - 7) * 6)","answer":"574"}
{"prompt":"30 - 81 * 7 - 1","answer":"-538"}
{"prompt":"16 * 27","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"95 + (5 - 1)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"11 - 8 - 25","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 1 * 6) - 15","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"((41 * 1) - 9) - 17 + 10","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"21 + 68","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"42 * ((25 + 6) * 6)","answer":"7812"}
{"prompt":"7 * 8 * 35","answer":"1960"}
{"prompt":"45 + 20","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(34 - 7) - 4","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 4) - 5","answer":"167"}
{"prompt":"29 * 26","answer":"754"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 2 - 10) - ((92 * 2) * 8)","answer":"-1456"}
{"prompt":"11 * 19 * 10 + 1","answer":"2091"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 10 * 8) + (66 + 3)","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"89 - 9 - 7 + 50 + 4","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"28 - (55 * 5)","answer":"-247"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 7) - 2) - 94","answer":"310"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 3) * 2","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"93 * 4","answer":"372"}
{"prompt":"55 - 3 * 8 - 34 + 5","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 3) - 19","answer":"254"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 9 + 9) * (59 - 7) + 2","answer":"4006"}
{"prompt":"9 - 8 * 42","answer":"-327"}
{"prompt":"33 * 82","answer":"2706"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 9) + ((96 + 2) * 8)","answer":"846"}
{"prompt":"77 - 10 * (93 - 4)","answer":"-813"}
{"prompt":"51 - 65 + 10","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 2) + (97 * 1) + 2","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"31 - 21","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 10) + 5","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"((66 + 5) * 4) - ((87 - 2) * 9)","answer":"-481"}
{"prompt":"84 * 56","answer":"4704"}
{"prompt":"68 - 95","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 3) - (61 * 8) + 2","answer":"-330"}
{"prompt":"11 + 68","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"93 + 2","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 2) * (56 * 6)","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 1) * 4 - 27","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"14 + 61 - 10","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 7) - 6 - 24","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"31 - 8 * 85 - 2","answer":"-651"}
{"prompt":"25 * 7 - 46","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"33 - 3 - (91 - 9)","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 10) - (32 * 5 - 2)","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(72 - 6) + 6 + 61 - 5 - 4","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 8) + ((91 + 8) * 4)","answer":"391"}
{"prompt":"94 * 8","answer":"752"}
{"prompt":"67 - 17","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"97 * (60 - 4 - 3)","answer":"5141"}
{"prompt":"11 + 8 * (89 - 5 + 3)","answer":"707"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 8) * 57 + 7 + 3","answer":"523"}
{"prompt":"76 - 14","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 2) - 18","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"86 - 18 + 6","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"52 + 10","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"19 + (10 - 2)","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 3) * 10","answer":"740"}
{"prompt":"6 * 37 * 4","answer":"888"}
{"prompt":"76 - 96 * 5","answer":"-404"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 5) + 45","answer":"260"}
{"prompt":"52 + 8 * 65","answer":"572"}
{"prompt":"27 - 32","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"71 - 5 * 54","answer":"-199"}
{"prompt":"63 + 8 * 29 * 5","answer":"1223"}
{"prompt":"93 * 8 - 6 * 1","answer":"738"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 3 * 9) - (46 - 6 - 2)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"10 * 27","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"88 * 7 * (73 - 2) * 3","answer":"131208"}
{"prompt":"90 * (84 + 2)","answer":"7740"}
{"prompt":"37 - 10 - 2 * 11","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"9 * ((7 + 4) + 4)","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"84 + 14","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(99 * 9) + 45 + 1","answer":"937"}
{"prompt":"82 + 59","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"76 * 96","answer":"7296"}
{"prompt":"34 - (51 * 8)","answer":"-374"}
{"prompt":"63 + 10 * 34","answer":"403"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 1 + 7) + 95","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"13 * 4","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 10) + 9 * (63 * 6 * 1)","answer":"3481"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 10 * 3) - (42 + 8) * 3","answer":"-86"}
{"prompt":"51 + 27","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 1) * (9 * 2 + 2)","answer":"520"}
{"prompt":"80 - 5 + (40 + 2)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"13 * 41 + 5 + 1","answer":"539"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 1) - 9 + 76","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"93 - 4 + 95 - 4","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 8) + 4 + 99 * 8 + 10","answer":"860"}
{"prompt":"20 * ((44 - 5) - 9)","answer":"600"}
{"prompt":"86 + 9 + 9 - ((54 * 3) + 1)","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 8 - 8) + 34 - 6 * 2","answer":"814"}
{"prompt":"37 - 31","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"40 + 4 + 78 * 3 + 9","answer":"287"}
{"prompt":"65 - (25 + 9)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"14 - (99 - 10) - 5","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"92 * 44","answer":"4048"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 8 - 10) + 62","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 5) - 4 * 1 + 4","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"46 + 6 * (27 - 8)","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"53 - 76","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 2) + 100","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"((45 - 9) - 5) * 38","answer":"1178"}
{"prompt":"60 + (74 * 2 * 5)","answer":"800"}
{"prompt":"48 - 46 * 8","answer":"-320"}
{"prompt":"31 * 2 - 31","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"1 * (52 + 6 - 6)","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"43 + 80","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"86 - 98 - 1","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"99 * 6 + 7 - (58 - 6) - 1","answer":"548"}
{"prompt":"35 - 88","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"29 + 57","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 2) * 4 - (11 + 2)","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"51 * (78 * 6 - 5)","answer":"23613"}
{"prompt":"2 + 61 - 2 * 5","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 3) - 48 + 5","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"88 * 78 - 2","answer":"6862"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 10) * 83","answer":"2490"}
{"prompt":"19 - (29 + 4 - 10)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"32 + 94 * 7","answer":"690"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 5 - 4) - (42 * 2)","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 5) + (12 + 8 + 4)","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"78 + (75 * 2)","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"41 + 2 * 59 - 10 + 2","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"38 - 21","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"69 * 75","answer":"5175"}
{"prompt":"16 * (46 + 8)","answer":"864"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 1) + (72 * 1)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 4) - (65 + 9 - 5)","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 2) * 7 * 20","answer":"7280"}
{"prompt":"70 - 36","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"59 * 83","answer":"4897"}
{"prompt":"12 + 1 * 1 + 73","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 4) * 59 - 10","answer":"639"}
{"prompt":"41 * ((93 * 1) * 4)","answer":"15252"}
{"prompt":"69 * 68 + 6","answer":"4698"}
{"prompt":"47 + 10 * (84 * 10)","answer":"8447"}
{"prompt":"((19 * 1) + 4) - (3 + 1)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"71 * 52","answer":"3692"}
{"prompt":"58 + 73 - 9","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"33 + 1 - 29","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"7 - ((11 * 7) - 2)","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"83 * 4 - 9 * 58","answer":"-190"}
{"prompt":"53 * ((22 * 6) + 8)","answer":"7420"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 8 * 1) + 90 * 5","answer":"674"}
{"prompt":"49 - 85","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 10) + 43","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 10) * 30","answer":"2100"}
{"prompt":"51 - (31 * 4 * 5)","answer":"-569"}
{"prompt":"28 - 81","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"3 * 1 * 9 - 70 * 10","answer":"-673"}
{"prompt":"93 - 91","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"2 - 79 + 2","answer":"-75"}
{"prompt":"47 * 64","answer":"3008"}
{"prompt":"99 + 24 * 8 * 10","answer":"2019"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 10) + 2 + 94 - 7","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 8 * 2) - 99","answer":"1293"}
{"prompt":"((2 * 8) - 6) - 73","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"49 * 7 + 5 - 64","answer":"284"}
{"prompt":"24 * 9 * 43","answer":"9288"}
{"prompt":"16 - 93","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"64 - 81 * 2 - 10","answer":"-108"}
{"prompt":"55 - 11","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 10) - 10) - (6 + 6)","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"65 * 44","answer":"2860"}
{"prompt":"24 - 66","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"52 * 18","answer":"936"}
{"prompt":"2 + 5","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"40 + 79 + 1","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 1) - 97 * 7","answer":"-649"}
{"prompt":"67 - 5 + 34 * 10 + 2","answer":"404"}
{"prompt":"15 - 2","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"65 + 58 + 3 - 1","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 6) * 3 - 58","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"84 * 4 + ((59 - 2) - 10)","answer":"383"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 9) * 87","answer":"2958"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 9 * 8) * 77","answer":"9548"}
{"prompt":"9 - 28 + 7 * 9","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"48 - 32 - 3","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"10 * (39 * 9)","answer":"3510"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 5) + 2 * 87 - 10","answer":"499"}
{"prompt":"93 * 83","answer":"7719"}
{"prompt":"38 - 6 * 7 - 92","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 2) + 7 + 88","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"98 - 81","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"54 - 75 + 3","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"60 - (31 + 8 - 3)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 7) - 1 + (2 + 8 * 7)","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 3) * 3 - (5 - 1 + 9)","answer":"725"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 3 + 8) - (52 + 7)","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 8) + 3 * 70","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"53 + 7 * (65 + 9) + 8","answer":"579"}
{"prompt":"67 - (93 + 8)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"((64 + 9) + 8) + 48 - 5","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"60 * 1 + 3","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"92 * 83","answer":"7636"}
{"prompt":"29 + 86 * 10","answer":"889"}
{"prompt":"41 * ((94 + 9) - 4)","answer":"4059"}
{"prompt":"6 * 38","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"18 - 1 + 97","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"24 * 66","answer":"1584"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 6) + 66","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"89 - 1","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"75 * 7 - 1 + 10","answer":"534"}
{"prompt":"13 - 1 - 9","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"89 + 16","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"((83 + 7) + 8) - (3 - 4)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"57 * 1 * (95 - 5 * 5)","answer":"3990"}
{"prompt":"72 - (41 * 4 - 6)","answer":"-86"}
{"prompt":"87 + 97","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"36 * 81","answer":"2916"}
{"prompt":"27 - 29","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"44 * 36","answer":"1584"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 1) * 5 - 60","answer":"435"}
{"prompt":"((33 * 5) + 1) + (41 * 4)","answer":"330"}
{"prompt":"8 * 9 * 57","answer":"4104"}
{"prompt":"46 + 56 * 7","answer":"438"}
{"prompt":"54 * 18","answer":"972"}
{"prompt":"25 * 2","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"21 * (19 * 5 + 9)","answer":"2184"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 5) + 4 + (94 + 2 + 1)","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"4 - 47","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 5) * (39 * 6) + 1","answer":"4447"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 8) - 91","answer":"213"}
{"prompt":"46 * 10 * 40","answer":"18400"}
{"prompt":"81 + 5","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"68 - 8 - 2 * 67 + 9 + 4","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"65 * 3","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"71 - 62","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"(77 - 5 + 3) * (23 * 5) + 4","answer":"8629"}
{"prompt":"66 + 2","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 6 * 4) - 85","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 8) + 10 * (52 + 7) + 3","answer":"654"}
{"prompt":"42 * (52 - 3)","answer":"2058"}
{"prompt":"55 * 97","answer":"5335"}
{"prompt":"65 - 11","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"59 + 95 * 3","answer":"344"}
{"prompt":"46 * 1 - (4 + 3)","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"93 * 10 * (49 - 8) + 6","answer":"38136"}
{"prompt":"29 - 6 + 96","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"94 + (68 + 3)","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"1 + (7 * 10)","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"70 + (28 - 3)","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"36 * 4 - 16","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"75 - 80","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"4 - 12","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"72 * (12 - 9)","answer":"216"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 4) * ((10 - 5) * 2)","answer":"3600"}
{"prompt":"54 * (28 + 8)","answer":"1944"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 1) + 3 + 11","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 10) * 73","answer":"39420"}
{"prompt":"52 + 96","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 7 - 1) * 38","answer":"8740"}
{"prompt":"57 + 42","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"2 + 26","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"61 + 26","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 1) - ((65 + 6) - 2)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"76 * 73 - 10","answer":"5538"}
{"prompt":"15 + 9 * 61","answer":"564"}
{"prompt":"(79 - 4) * 10","answer":"750"}
{"prompt":"44 + 8 + 5","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"93 * 2 + 7","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"6 * 88","answer":"528"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 7) - 6 + 35","answer":"477"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 4 + 3) - (81 * 6 - 3)","answer":"-398"}
{"prompt":"63 + 6 + (5 + 6)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 2) - 76 * 6","answer":"-288"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 9) * 42","answer":"1176"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 7 * 2) + 33","answer":"1181"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 6) + 7 - 46","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"28 + 10 + 41","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"16 + 92","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"((91 + 8) * 4) - (67 + 6) + 8","answer":"331"}
{"prompt":"3 + 90","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"35 * 34","answer":"1190"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 10 - 1) + 33","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"70 - ((42 * 4) + 1)","answer":"-99"}
{"prompt":"25 + 83","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"73 * 57 * 7","answer":"29127"}
{"prompt":"89 * 6 + 2 - 7 * 6","answer":"494"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 9) + (59 + 1)","answer":"942"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 1) * (72 - 3)","answer":"2898"}
{"prompt":"73 + 6 * 16","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 4) + (38 - 1)","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"40 + 97 - 1","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 10) - 5 - 95","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"19 * 31","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"71 - 4 + 61","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"33 * (40 * 10)","answer":"13200"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 5) * 6 - 53 * 10","answer":"1390"}
{"prompt":"48 - 2 - 2 - 75","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"((28 * 9) - 2) - 33 + 3","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"91 - 52","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"4 * 26 + 10","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"83 - 8 - 8 * 7","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"((58 + 9) - 8) - (98 + 9)","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"15 * 1 - 1 + 91","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 8) - 43","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"33 + (64 + 1 - 10)","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 1 - 3) * 74","answer":"518"}
{"prompt":"49 + (73 * 10 - 1)","answer":"778"}
{"prompt":"53 * (11 * 9 * 1)","answer":"5247"}
{"prompt":"34 + 76","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 2) + (55 + 10) * 4","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"69 - 10 + 6","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"21 - 20","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"8 - 48 * 1","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 2 + 6) - 95","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"57 * 60","answer":"3420"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 6) * 5 + 17 * 10","answer":"2600"}
{"prompt":"38 - 97","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"24 - 84","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"44 + 94 - 6","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"14 + 74","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 2) - 81","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 7) * (83 - 9)","answer":"-370"}
{"prompt":"29 - 10 - (3 - 8 + 10)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"74 - (31 + 6)","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"9 - 5 * 9 - 99 - 5","answer":"-140"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 10) + 22","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"53 + 10 + 7 * 56","answer":"455"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 8 - 6) * 37","answer":"1221"}
{"prompt":"56 + 62 - 6 - 3","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"59 + 8 + 47 * 10","answer":"537"}
{"prompt":"73 * 66 + 4 + 5","answer":"4827"}
{"prompt":"10 * 76","answer":"760"}
{"prompt":"77 - (76 + 7 - 7)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 4 * 5) + 69","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"31 + ((79 + 9) - 10)","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 1) * 5 * 56 - 1","answer":"4759"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 9) - (3 * 8 + 8)","answer":"517"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 5 * 8) + 67","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 7) + 6 + 21","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 7) + 9) - 58","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"71 * 3","answer":"213"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 9) + 31","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"57 + 64","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"83 + 60 + 4 * 10","answer":"183"}
{"prompt":"33 + (67 + 9) * 6","answer":"489"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 1) * 7 + 97","answer":"461"}
{"prompt":"76 - (3 * 6)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"34 + 2 - 38","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 4) - 16","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"6 + 8","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"62 - 5 + 1 + ((82 + 5) - 3)","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 1) + 67","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"96 + ((56 * 7) + 10)","answer":"498"}
{"prompt":"54 - 3 - 5 - (2 + 1) - 3","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"77 - 21 * 7","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 9) + 6 * 32","answer":"975"}
{"prompt":"((70 + 5) * 2) - (70 * 6 - 5)","answer":"-265"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 6) + (30 * 7)","answer":"280"}
{"prompt":"81 - 35","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"((40 + 1) + 7) + 66","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"12 * 4 + 2","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 7) + 98","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"54 + 98 + 1 * 4","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(44 - 6) * 3 - 100","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 3) + 6 + 74 - 1","answer":"331"}
{"prompt":"43 * 96","answer":"4128"}
{"prompt":"11 - 68","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"38 * (14 - 6)","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 10) - ((19 - 4) + 10)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"52 - (21 * 7)","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"26 - 29","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"89 * (75 + 8)","answer":"7387"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 8) * 5","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"95 + ((70 * 4) - 2)","answer":"373"}
{"prompt":"39 * 37","answer":"1443"}
{"prompt":"91 * (61 - 7)","answer":"4914"}
{"prompt":"57 - (62 - 2) - 3","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"((22 + 7) + 2) + (24 * 5)","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"54 * 43","answer":"2322"}
{"prompt":"75 - 86","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 2) * 21","answer":"1386"}
{"prompt":"63 * 91","answer":"5733"}
{"prompt":"95 + (94 * 1) + 2","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"58 - 8 - 79 + 4 - 6","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"42 * 68","answer":"2856"}
{"prompt":"45 * (62 - 9)","answer":"2385"}
{"prompt":"3 - 10 + 38","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"53 - 9","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"38 - (61 - 5 - 1)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"41 + 69","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 8 * 10) + 32","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"36 - 29","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"71 * 67","answer":"4757"}
{"prompt":"63 * 6 + 31 * 3","answer":"471"}
{"prompt":"72 - 54 + 5","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"52 + 8 + 60","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"63 + (30 + 1)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"41 + 4 + 77","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 10) * 3 * 95","answer":"30210"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 5) - 27","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"100 + 70","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"93 + (54 + 1)","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"58 + 7 * 1","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"57 + 52 + 5 - 3","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"68 + 3 * ((63 * 9) * 4)","answer":"6872"}
{"prompt":"68 + 6 + 3 * 6","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"87 - 8 * 82 * 10","answer":"-6473"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 5) * 2","answer":"980"}
{"prompt":"15 + 34","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"82 * 26 * 10 * 4","answer":"85280"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 2 - 10) + 60","answer":"178"}
{"prompt":"37 + 10 * 1 + 51 + 6 - 6","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"((46 + 5) - 10) + 53","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 5) + ((83 + 10) + 2)","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"94 - 70","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 7) + 41 + 8","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"((64 + 10) + 8) * ((23 + 7) * 3)","answer":"7380"}
{"prompt":"90 * 10 - (63 + 1) + 5","answer":"841"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 10) * 41","answer":"14350"}
{"prompt":"((83 + 7) - 3) - 97","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"26 * 99 + 1","answer":"2575"}
{"prompt":"33 - 74","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"37 - 84","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 7) - 27","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"29 - 6 + 10 - 74","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"44 - 59","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"1 - (90 + 1) + 10","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 9 + 3) * ((52 + 4) * 2)","answer":"4592"}
{"prompt":"12 * 9 - 75 * 5","answer":"-267"}
{"prompt":"85 - 8 - 6 - 39","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"58 * 9 - 6","answer":"516"}
{"prompt":"25 - 6 - 7 + (14 - 2) + 2","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"60 - 2 + ((82 + 1) - 2)","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"48 - (75 - 9) + 6","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"96 - 3 * 87","answer":"-165"}
{"prompt":"35 * 20 + 1","answer":"701"}
{"prompt":"64 - 20 - 9","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"61 + (13 * 10)","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"95 + 50","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"95 + 1 - 51","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"87 * (92 * 1)","answer":"8004"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 3) + 5 - 22 * 10","answer":"-113"}
{"prompt":"1 - 73","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 6 * 3) + 100","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"87 - (7 * 6)","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"24 + (48 + 2 + 8)","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 10) + 21","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"79 * 87","answer":"6873"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 5 * 10) + 99 + 5","answer":"2004"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 8) * 8 * (16 + 7)","answer":"10856"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 10 + 2) + 29","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"88 * 5 + 41 * 6","answer":"686"}
{"prompt":"44 - 55","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"79 * 1 + (19 + 4) * 4","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"33 + 99","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 10) + 4 * 84","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 8 + 6) + 97","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"90 * 83","answer":"7470"}
{"prompt":"64 - 27","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 9) * 7 + (35 - 10 * 9)","answer":"6245"}
{"prompt":"29 + 9 * 38","answer":"371"}
{"prompt":"80 * 15","answer":"1200"}
{"prompt":"8 + 9 * 86","answer":"782"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 9) + 9) * (2 * 2 - 2)","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"72 * 88","answer":"6336"}
{"prompt":"18 * 7 - 9 * 80 * 3 + 4","answer":"-2030"}
{"prompt":"78 * 82","answer":"6396"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 5) - (42 * 7) - 8","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"78 * 7 + 7 - 72","answer":"481"}
{"prompt":"65 + 85","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"94 * 41 - 10 * 5","answer":"3804"}
{"prompt":"71 - 97","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"67 * (93 * 6)","answer":"37386"}
{"prompt":"74 + 99","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 1) + 100","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"11 - 91","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"31 + 29","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"26 * 81 * 7 + 3","answer":"14745"}
{"prompt":"41 + 4","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"39 * (95 * 6)","answer":"22230"}
{"prompt":"92 + 5 + 84 + 7","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 8) + (81 + 10 - 6)","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"86 - (89 - 8) + 4","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"89 * 30","answer":"2670"}
{"prompt":"87 - (72 * 9)","answer":"-561"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 10 + 5) - (4 * 5 + 7)","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"79 * 9 - 6 * 54","answer":"387"}
{"prompt":"97 * 5 - 65","answer":"420"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 7) + 2 - 47","answer":"529"}
{"prompt":"37 + (36 * 10) + 9","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 2) * ((79 * 3) - 4)","answer":"28426"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 2) - 12","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"46 + 26 - 10 - 9","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"81 - 6 * 4 + (19 * 8) - 8","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"93 * 4 + 4 + 2","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"69 - 62","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"46 + 5 * 62 - 9 - 9","answer":"338"}
{"prompt":"5 + 2 - 83","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 10) - (30 - 1) - 10","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"42 + (72 * 2)","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"90 * 20","answer":"1800"}
{"prompt":"1 + 5 - (11 + 6 + 1)","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"93 + 72","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"58 - 6 + 24","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 7) * 17 - 9 - 7","answer":"579"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 5) + (97 + 8)","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 8) + 75","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"100 - ((89 * 3) - 10)","answer":"-157"}
{"prompt":"72 - (67 - 8 + 9)","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"20 + 41","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"89 * 93","answer":"8277"}
{"prompt":"97 * 39","answer":"3783"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 9) + 6","answer":"681"}
{"prompt":"7 + 100","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"59 * 14 - 5","answer":"821"}
{"prompt":"30 + ((48 * 1) + 3)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"((55 + 8) - 6) - 82","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"39 + (75 * 3) + 10","answer":"274"}
{"prompt":"40 + 11","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 6) - 7 * 39","answer":"-264"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 7) * 71","answer":"2485"}
{"prompt":"33 + 55","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"62 * 79","answer":"4898"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 1) * 1","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"2 + 7 * 2 + 1","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"100 - 2 - 69 - 1","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"48 * 4 - (74 - 9) * 10","answer":"-458"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 6) - ((76 * 6) + 10)","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 2) - 6 * ((71 * 1) + 10)","answer":"-433"}
{"prompt":"12 + 16 * 2","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"6 + 23","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"31 * 7 * ((53 + 6) * 2)","answer":"25606"}
{"prompt":"40 - (4 * 7 + 3)","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 7 - 5) * 70","answer":"1120"}
{"prompt":"21 + 4 - 9 * 38","answer":"-317"}
{"prompt":"97 + 6 * (77 + 9) * 9","answer":"4741"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 7) - 2 * 49","answer":"567"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 1) * (71 * 6 + 1)","answer":"4270"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 6) + ((98 - 2) + 8)","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"90 + 4 - 98 * 6","answer":"-494"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 6) - (89 - 3)","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"54 - 26","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"97 * (88 + 8)","answer":"9312"}
{"prompt":"75 - 33","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 7) + ((14 * 3) + 9)","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 3) * 41","answer":"2378"}
{"prompt":"11 * (80 * 6 * 1)","answer":"5280"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 4) - 5 + (27 + 2 + 9)","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"98 * 31 * 10","answer":"30380"}
{"prompt":"81 - 2 * 9 * 14","answer":"-171"}
{"prompt":"93 + (86 * 8)","answer":"781"}
{"prompt":"((47 + 5) * 4) - 80","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"33 * (98 * 6)","answer":"19404"}
{"prompt":"83 * 7 * (9 - 9 - 8)","answer":"-4648"}
{"prompt":"94 + 6 - 9 - 38","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"29 + 94","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"60 - (9 - 3)","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"25 * (53 - 1 * 2)","answer":"1275"}
{"prompt":"((33 - 6) + 7) * ((99 + 9) + 8)","answer":"3944"}
{"prompt":"99 - 80 - 4 * 9","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 3) * 17","answer":"1683"}
{"prompt":"11 + 10 - 47","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"53 * 2 * 53","answer":"5618"}
{"prompt":"53 * 51","answer":"2703"}
{"prompt":"((99 + 1) - 9) + 55","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"69 - 26","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"((8 - 5) - 4) - 17","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"((99 - 2) - 4) - (4 * 6) - 1","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"87 * 2 * 9 - 98","answer":"1468"}
{"prompt":"67 + 27","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"91 * 87 * 2 + 9","answer":"15843"}
{"prompt":"78 - 68","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"27 - 31","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 8) * 3 + (56 * 7 - 7)","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"49 + 26","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"48 + 91 + 6","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"40 + 17","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 10) - 18","answer":"462"}
{"prompt":"33 * 3 * 84","answer":"8316"}
{"prompt":"34 + 18 * 7","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"5 - 63 * 7","answer":"-436"}
{"prompt":"59 + 3 + ((15 - 2) + 10)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 6) * 4 * 10","answer":"1560"}
{"prompt":"97 * 10 - 76","answer":"894"}
{"prompt":"1 * 1","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"49 + (87 * 1) - 4","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"67 + (43 + 4) * 8","answer":"443"}
{"prompt":"11 + 7 * 91","answer":"648"}
{"prompt":"68 * 43 - 9 - 3","answer":"2912"}
{"prompt":"32 * 66","answer":"2112"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 7) * 60","answer":"2940"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 4) - 1 - (41 * 5)","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"98 * 41 * 9","answer":"36162"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 3) * 97","answer":"3298"}
{"prompt":"89 + 2 - 3","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"((78 + 5) - 5) - ((43 * 5) + 8)","answer":"-145"}
{"prompt":"75 + 8 - 3 + 6","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"35 + 89","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 2 + 4) + (94 + 5 * 6)","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 3) + (80 - 8)","answer":"183"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 2) * 72","answer":"2808"}
{"prompt":"100 * 6 + 46","answer":"646"}
{"prompt":"11 + 10 * 23 * 1 + 7","answer":"248"}
{"prompt":"62 - 7 + 27","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"36 + 32","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"83 + 58 - 2","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 3) - ((53 - 4) * 4)","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 1 * 7) + (27 - 8 - 4)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"47 * 3 - 49","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 8) * (26 - 1)","answer":"1475"}
{"prompt":"25 * 1 - 11","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"((7 + 3) - 3) - (3 * 5 - 10)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 7) * 1 - 30","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"38 - (45 * 7)","answer":"-277"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 6) - 6 - 76","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"29 - 1 * 94","answer":"-65"}
{"prompt":"20 + 2","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"87 + 5","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"6 - 7 + 8 - 96 - 1","answer":"-90"}
{"prompt":"82 * ((14 - 1) - 10)","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 1 - 9) + 9","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"65 - 2 + (32 + 5)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"44 + 6","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"80 + 3 - 3 + (36 + 9)","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"((45 - 3) * 10) - (27 * 10)","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"63 * (33 * 4)","answer":"8316"}
{"prompt":"34 - 5 - 99","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"28 * (88 + 3 - 10)","answer":"2268"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 2 * 6) - 26","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 1) * 61","answer":"3294"}
{"prompt":"(65 * 10) + 62","answer":"712"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 8 - 3) * (84 + 8)","answer":"8188"}
{"prompt":"66 - 10 + 8 * 100","answer":"856"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 3) * 39","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"80 * 36","answer":"2880"}
{"prompt":"98 - (94 - 10)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"95 + 5 - 89","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"47 + 16","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"((85 * 7) * 3) + (22 * 9)","answer":"1983"}
{"prompt":"97 * 2 * 7 + 78","answer":"1436"}
{"prompt":"75 - (70 * 5)","answer":"-275"}
{"prompt":"75 + 47 * 1","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"47 - 48","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"25 * 2 + 9 * 96","answer":"914"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 2) * 10) + 55 * 5","answer":"655"}
{"prompt":"80 * 6 * (18 * 3)","answer":"25920"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 10) - 9 * 8","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"62 * 23","answer":"1426"}
{"prompt":"((24 - 9) + 7) + 77","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 5) * 71","answer":"994"}
{"prompt":"16 * 27","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"43 - (90 - 9)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"71 + 7 - 12 - 3","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"((32 * 1) + 1) * (80 + 4) * 8","answer":"22176"}
{"prompt":"6 * (33 * 9) * 1","answer":"1782"}
{"prompt":"32 + 10 - 9 * 31","answer":"-237"}
{"prompt":"79 * 7 + 3 * 1","answer":"556"}
{"prompt":"((39 + 10) + 4) * ((10 - 5) - 6)","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"11 * 9 * 26 * 7","answer":"18018"}
{"prompt":"90 + 7","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"90 - 3 - 10 * 83","answer":"-743"}
{"prompt":"97 + 50","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"73 - 58","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"61 * 7","answer":"427"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 1 * 1) - (98 - 4)","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"51 * 80","answer":"4080"}
{"prompt":"(61 + 7) - 47","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"16 + 56","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"52 - 3 + 5 + 31 * 8 - 2","answer":"300"}
{"prompt":"62 * 21 * 8 * 8","answer":"83328"}
{"prompt":"67 - 50","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 8) * 4 - 53 + 10 + 9","answer":"2942"}
{"prompt":"73 + (45 + 2)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"23 * ((16 * 3) * 5)","answer":"5520"}
{"prompt":"11 + 68 * 10","answer":"691"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 6) + (11 * 7)","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"79 - 86","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"79 - 9 * 85","answer":"-686"}
{"prompt":"67 + 1 * ((43 + 9) * 2)","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"80 - 58 - 3 * 7","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"48 - 41","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"7 - ((39 + 2) + 10)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"((14 - 1) + 2) - 21","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"59 + (32 - 5 * 4)","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"71 - 23 - 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"100 + 47","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(10 - 2 * 8) + (97 + 6 * 10)","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"98 + 7 + 10 - 68","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"22 * (34 + 6)","answer":"880"}
{"prompt":"64 + (32 * 9 * 8)","answer":"2368"}
{"prompt":"16 * 95 + 9 * 9","answer":"1601"}
{"prompt":"66 + 95","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"60 + (92 + 4)","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"79 - (30 + 8)","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"16 + 61","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"68 + 50","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"10 + (2 * 5 * 6)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"56 * (100 * 9) - 7","answer":"50393"}
{"prompt":"83 - 32 * 10","answer":"-237"}
{"prompt":"63 - ((86 * 1) - 5)","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"78 * 3 - 4 * ((2 - 6) - 6)","answer":"274"}
{"prompt":"13 - (74 * 7) * 9","answer":"-4649"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 5) + (28 - 5 * 4)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"51 + 91","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"25 - (94 * 10)","answer":"-915"}
{"prompt":"69 + (21 + 2 - 1)","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 2 - 3) - 49","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"27 + (33 + 10 + 10)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"((96 + 6) * 6) * 2 - 8 - 6","answer":"1210"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 3) + (94 - 1)","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 6 + 8) - (91 - 3)","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"21 - ((54 * 4) - 5)","answer":"-190"}
{"prompt":"62 - 20","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(73 * 7) + (19 - 1 + 10)","answer":"539"}
{"prompt":"13 - (17 - 2 - 1)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"58 + 41 + 10","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"17 + 9 * 48","answer":"449"}
{"prompt":"68 - (93 - 7 + 9)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"15 + 8","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"18 * 14 - 4","answer":"248"}
{"prompt":"84 + (16 + 10) + 9","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"60 + (24 + 10)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(44 - 4 * 9) * 42 * 7","answer":"2352"}
{"prompt":"39 + 6 * 70","answer":"459"}
{"prompt":"72 - 72","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"18 - 91","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"23 - 6 * 2","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"88 + 66","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"13 - (71 - 9 - 5)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"89 + 96 * 6","answer":"665"}
{"prompt":"6 - 39","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"46 + 66","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"46 * (24 + 1)","answer":"1150"}
{"prompt":"40 * ((73 + 5) - 2)","answer":"3040"}
{"prompt":"70 + 2 * (6 * 4)","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"22 - (13 - 8) + 6","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"((75 * 9) * 4) + 4","answer":"2704"}
{"prompt":"95 * 1 * 47","answer":"4465"}
{"prompt":"75 + ((65 * 5) + 5)","answer":"405"}
{"prompt":"5 + (28 - 8)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"73 - (28 - 8) + 6","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"48 - 4 + 4 + 94","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"96 + 47 * 9","answer":"519"}
{"prompt":"(47 + 7) - 4 * 69","answer":"-222"}
{"prompt":"((49 * 2) + 3) * (12 + 10) - 4","answer":"2218"}
{"prompt":"19 * 53","answer":"1007"}
{"prompt":"54 + (13 + 6 * 8)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 6) * 99","answer":"9009"}
{"prompt":"32 * (84 * 2)","answer":"5376"}
{"prompt":"12 + 35","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"88 + 64 * 7","answer":"536"}
{"prompt":"83 + 10 - 81 + 4","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"95 * 26","answer":"2470"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 6) + 99","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"18 - 7 + 94 * 6","answer":"575"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 3) * 92","answer":"1564"}
{"prompt":"36 * 5 - 5","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"65 * 6 - 76","answer":"314"}
{"prompt":"52 - 86 * 4 * 5","answer":"-1668"}
{"prompt":"62 - 8 * 5","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 7) - 10 + 71 + 9 * 3","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 4) * 55","answer":"4510"}
{"prompt":"43 * 79 - 8","answer":"3389"}
{"prompt":"2 * (85 * 6)","answer":"1020"}
{"prompt":"28 + 16 * 4","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 8) * 5","answer":"425"}
{"prompt":"70 - 78","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 9 - 9) - 41","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 3) - 5 - (22 + 10 + 1)","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"40 - 8 - 66 + 10","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"23 + (3 * 8) + 5","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"78 + 9 - 18","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 6) * 9","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"80 + (28 + 3 + 5)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"((84 * 9) * 4) * 84 - 3 - 2","answer":"254011"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 9 * 1) - 70","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"46 * 81","answer":"3726"}
{"prompt":"(73 * 9) - 57","answer":"600"}
{"prompt":"69 + 37","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"34 * 9","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"81 * 14 + 4","answer":"1138"}
{"prompt":"90 * ((19 - 7) - 8)","answer":"360"}
{"prompt":"93 + (90 - 8) + 8","answer":"183"}
{"prompt":"81 - (22 * 5)","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"56 - 33","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 8) + (54 - 4) * 1","answer":"482"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 6) * 7 + 45 - 4 * 3","answer":"2595"}
{"prompt":"93 + (96 - 4)","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"76 * 67","answer":"5092"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 6) - (94 - 4 + 9)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"18 + (47 + 8 + 6)","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"78 - 66","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 9 + 2) * (35 - 3)","answer":"8704"}
{"prompt":"19 * 49","answer":"931"}
{"prompt":"18 * 1","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 1) * (72 + 1) - 10","answer":"939"}
{"prompt":"50 + 76 - 2","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"31 + 81 + 6 + 6","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"13 * 9 - 69","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((72 * 4) + 7) * ((27 - 3) + 8)","answer":"9440"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 5) + 92","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"7 - (55 + 4)","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 1) + 8 * 51","answer":"414"}
{"prompt":"83 * 74","answer":"6142"}
{"prompt":"82 * (31 + 8)","answer":"3198"}
{"prompt":"55 - 8 * 8 - 11","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"91 * 10 * 48 - 7 * 4","answer":"43652"}
{"prompt":"83 + 44 - 6 + 9","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 10) * 8 - 12","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"72 + 43 + 6","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"83 * (70 + 10 * 1)","answer":"6640"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 10) + (53 + 4 * 7)","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 8) - 5 - 79 - 3 + 6","answer":"647"}
{"prompt":"78 * 70 + 6","answer":"5466"}
{"prompt":"90 - 7 * 91","answer":"-547"}
{"prompt":"77 - 32","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"16 * 45","answer":"720"}
{"prompt":"66 * 50","answer":"3300"}
{"prompt":"61 - (26 - 1) * 3","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"((52 - 10) + 1) - 43","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 8 - 8) - 34","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"3 * 4 - (81 - 8) - 1","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"66 - 8 + (54 + 5)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"1 - 83","answer":"-82"}
{"prompt":"21 * 8","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"20 - 2 + 10","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"39 * 7 - (59 * 8)","answer":"-199"}
{"prompt":"52 + 22","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"86 - 10 * 76","answer":"-674"}
{"prompt":"70 + ((36 + 3) - 10)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"24 - (37 + 4)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 1 * 2) - 63","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"(17 + 3) * 18 * 10","answer":"3600"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 7 + 3) * (6 * 3)","answer":"11394"}
{"prompt":"3 - 48","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 10 * 6) * 30","answer":"750"}
{"prompt":"76 + 1 - 92","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 7) + 18","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 10 + 7) + ((80 - 3) * 2)","answer":"221"}
{"prompt":"13 + ((73 + 8) - 9)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"84 * 13","answer":"1092"}
{"prompt":"((38 + 5) + 4) - (85 + 9 + 7)","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"72 * 9 * 29","answer":"18792"}
{"prompt":"15 + 2 - 6 + ((73 - 1) * 7)","answer":"515"}
{"prompt":"97 * 74","answer":"7178"}
{"prompt":"20 - 84","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"14 * 61","answer":"854"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 6) - 51","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"((18 + 7) + 8) * (98 - 6 - 10)","answer":"2706"}
{"prompt":"67 + (9 - 2)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 9) + 55 + 5 + 4","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"86 - 10 - ((25 + 4) + 3)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"21 - 47","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"76 - 28","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 4) + 4) * (19 * 2)","answer":"1140"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 10 * 10) - (39 + 1)","answer":"2060"}
{"prompt":"6 + 33 * 4","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"71 + 4 - 25","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"31 + 36","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"2 + 10 - 44","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"100 * 5 - ((32 * 2) + 6)","answer":"430"}
{"prompt":"73 * (81 + 6)","answer":"6351"}
{"prompt":"(98 - 9) - (12 - 8 * 7)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"67 * (50 - 1) * 5","answer":"16415"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 6) + 8","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"68 - 60","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 4) - 8","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"60 * 9 - (56 - 10) * 6","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"15 + 24","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"93 - 43 * 6","answer":"-165"}
{"prompt":"93 * 38","answer":"3534"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 1) * 50","answer":"2700"}
{"prompt":"58 * 50 - 3","answer":"2897"}
{"prompt":"26 + 36","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"55 + 29","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"69 + (30 - 4)","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"40 + 4 - (92 + 5)","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 5 - 3) * 72","answer":"1728"}
{"prompt":"38 * 50","answer":"1900"}
{"prompt":"25 * 7 + 43","answer":"218"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 8) * 5 * (10 + 9 * 1)","answer":"34200"}
{"prompt":"((55 * 6) - 9) + (40 * 2 - 2)","answer":"399"}
{"prompt":"22 - 58","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"((1 + 8) + 4) - (47 * 6)","answer":"-269"}
{"prompt":"58 - 89","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"7 * 96 - 3 - 8","answer":"661"}
{"prompt":"2 * 98","answer":"196"}
{"prompt":"84 * 6 - 84","answer":"420"}
{"prompt":"99 * 4 + 9 - (82 * 7)","answer":"-169"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 5) - 10 * (48 * 1)","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 7) + 18 - 8","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 5) + 3 - 9","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"53 + 7 * 9 + 54","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 6) * 83 + 4","answer":"12454"}
{"prompt":"35 * 23","answer":"805"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 8) + 10 - 86","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"62 + 66","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"84 * 7 - 84","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"20 * 64","answer":"1280"}
{"prompt":"50 - 11","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"(66 * 1) * 8 - 88","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"91 - (32 - 9)","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"((17 * 4) * 5) + 97","answer":"437"}
{"prompt":"25 - 10 - (74 * 1 * 4)","answer":"-281"}
{"prompt":"43 * (45 + 4) * 7","answer":"14749"}
{"prompt":"14 * 27","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 2) * 26","answer":"936"}
{"prompt":"36 - 96 - 3 * 7","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"4 - 85","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"80 * 4 * (72 * 10 * 3)","answer":"691200"}
{"prompt":"((48 + 6) * 2) + 5 - 10 + 4","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"98 * (11 - 7)","answer":"392"}
{"prompt":"((8 * 3) + 7) * 38","answer":"1178"}
{"prompt":"43 - ((22 - 8) + 4)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"26 * 93","answer":"2418"}
{"prompt":"64 * (26 + 6) * 4","answer":"8192"}
{"prompt":"28 + ((53 - 6) - 4)","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 8) - 25","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"61 - 9 + 29 * 10 + 9","answer":"351"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 6) + 3 * 78","answer":"242"}
{"prompt":"96 * 97","answer":"9312"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 9) + 9 + 5","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"((83 + 3) + 8) * ((60 * 6) + 1)","answer":"33934"}
{"prompt":"32 + 80","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"58 + 25","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"12 + 10 + (62 * 9) * 7","answer":"3928"}
{"prompt":"71 * 4 * 50","answer":"14200"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 4) * 62","answer":"9920"}
{"prompt":"62 - 8 - 77 - 1 - 4","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"93 * 10 + 17 * 1","answer":"947"}
{"prompt":"78 * 46","answer":"3588"}
{"prompt":"53 - 91","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"((30 + 1) * 3) - 17 * 8","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"90 * 2","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"46 + 36","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 6) + 7 * (72 + 1 + 10)","answer":"911"}
{"prompt":"35 * 65","answer":"2275"}
{"prompt":"45 * 84","answer":"3780"}
{"prompt":"67 + (7 - 10 + 5)","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"((24 + 2) - 10) * (33 * 3)","answer":"1584"}
{"prompt":"50 - 6 - (77 + 3) + 2","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 3) * 3 + (19 - 7)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"24 * 29","answer":"696"}
{"prompt":"23 + (71 * 3)","answer":"236"}
{"prompt":"86 - 73","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"4 - 23 + 4 * 3","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(48 + 4) - 60","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"74 * 24","answer":"1776"}
{"prompt":"32 - (88 + 7)","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 7) - 5 + (82 * 5 * 10)","answer":"4138"}
{"prompt":"78 * 2 * 7 * ((57 + 3) + 5)","answer":"70980"}
{"prompt":"84 - 8 + 6 - 1","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"62 - 80","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"30 + 52","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"53 + 41","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 10) * 7 * ((28 * 2) - 9)","answer":"25662"}
{"prompt":"17 * 1 * (5 - 5) + 2","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 4 - 5) - (69 + 6) + 7","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 1) - (4 * 8 - 8)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"13 - 62","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"93 * (40 * 3)","answer":"11160"}
{"prompt":"((23 * 5) * 5) + 11","answer":"586"}
{"prompt":"27 - 26 - 3","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 7 + 8) - 54","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"89 * 92","answer":"8188"}
{"prompt":"91 - 35","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 1) - (16 * 1 - 4)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"50 - (12 + 6 - 3)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"34 - 15","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"((84 - 6) - 1) + 30","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 1 + 3) - 83 * 10","answer":"-822"}
{"prompt":"22 - 8 - 78","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"72 - 5 - 10 - 94","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"((87 * 3) - 5) * 20","answer":"5120"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 1) * 1","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"76 + (14 + 4 + 6)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"85 * 75","answer":"6375"}
{"prompt":"50 + 76","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"37 - ((32 + 5) - 2)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"46 * 5 + 3","answer":"233"}
{"prompt":"10 - 57","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"58 + 32","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 1) + (79 - 5) + 7","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"61 + 9 - 8 * 16","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"10 * 1 - 39","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 4) + ((51 - 6) + 5)","answer":"230"}
{"prompt":"53 - 94","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"84 - 3 - 7 - ((20 + 2) + 8)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"51 - ((82 + 5) + 8)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"43 + 18 * 2","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"97 - 83","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"((54 * 7) - 7) * 41 * 5","answer":"76055"}
{"prompt":"79 * 7 - 1 * (83 + 6) + 1","answer":"465"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 7) + 9 - (41 * 4 - 10)","answer":"-98"}
{"prompt":"46 - 83 - 10","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 1) + 5 * 5 * 2","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"42 - 4 * 8 * 57","answer":"-1782"}
{"prompt":"1 + 5 + 6","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"27 * 58 + 2 * 1","answer":"1568"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 6) + 2 * 18 - 8","answer":"568"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 5) + 8 * (9 * 9) + 3","answer":"726"}
{"prompt":"35 + 46 + 5","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"87 * 30","answer":"2610"}
{"prompt":"44 * 7 + 4","answer":"312"}
{"prompt":"7 + 27 * 9","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"71 * 3 + (81 * 8 - 2)","answer":"859"}
{"prompt":"10 - (78 + 6)","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"13 - 1 + 59","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 6 * 1) + (63 * 8 + 6)","answer":"696"}
{"prompt":"(72 - 9) + 22","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 4) + 8 + 78 - 5","answer":"309"}
{"prompt":"78 - (69 - 5)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 9) - 10 * 40 * 1 * 5","answer":"-1944"}
{"prompt":"44 - 8 - 26","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"((73 * 6) - 6) - (52 - 6)","answer":"386"}
{"prompt":"3 - 30","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"12 - 1 - 9 - 45","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"79 - 10 - 4 + 76","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"31 - 88 + 4","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"81 * 95 - 8","answer":"7687"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 4 - 3) * 74","answer":"2886"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 8) - 73","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"62 + 4 - 85 + 6","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"62 + (5 + 3)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"53 * 2 + 10 - 100","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"21 + 28","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 5) - 10 + 4","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"84 + 32 - 5","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"15 - (68 + 4)","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"58 - 10 * 3 - 22","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"85 * 20","answer":"1700"}
{"prompt":"17 + 57","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 10) * 85","answer":"56950"}
{"prompt":"49 + 5","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"17 * (47 * 4)","answer":"3196"}
{"prompt":"1 + 64","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"29 - 2 * 9 - 31","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"76 + (40 + 4 - 7)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"16 + 27","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"24 - 3 * 9 - (76 + 7) - 3","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 7 + 10) + (17 + 4)","answer":"269"}
{"prompt":"7 * ((79 + 3) * 10)","answer":"5740"}
{"prompt":"95 + 51 * 3 * 7","answer":"1166"}
{"prompt":"60 - 4 - 5 + 67","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"44 + 8 + 97","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 9) + 52 - 10 - 2","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"86 - ((100 - 3) - 5)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 3) - 12","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"60 - 1 - 5 + ((21 * 3) + 2)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"96 - 97","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"73 - 5 + 7 + 7","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 10 + 5) + (32 - 6) + 3","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"((98 * 6) * 6) * ((74 + 5) + 4)","answer":"292824"}
{"prompt":"96 + 4 * 5 * 28","answer":"656"}
{"prompt":"73 * 4 - 10 - (49 * 9 - 2)","answer":"-157"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 10 + 8) - 80","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"48 * 99 + 10","answer":"4762"}
{"prompt":"47 * 67","answer":"3149"}
{"prompt":"82 + (89 + 1 + 10)","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"62 + 64","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"23 - (23 - 7)","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 3) + 80 * 9","answer":"752"}
{"prompt":"53 - 18","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"14 + 96","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"57 + 1 * 70","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"79 - 89","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"72 * 80","answer":"5760"}
{"prompt":"59 - 1 * 93","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 3 - 9) * ((6 * 8) + 9)","answer":"3078"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 10) + 77","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"7 - 11 - 4","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"55 * (14 + 9)","answer":"1265"}
{"prompt":"19 * 9 - (78 - 1)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"((62 - 9) - 7) - 22","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 7) * 51","answer":"5151"}
{"prompt":"30 * 10 * 6 * (92 * 6)","answer":"993600"}
{"prompt":"((99 - 2) + 5) * (5 * 3)","answer":"1530"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 2) - 5 - 46","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"27 + 4 - (58 - 1)","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"((28 * 7) + 1) + ((11 - 10) + 9)","answer":"207"}
{"prompt":"((21 + 2) - 5) + (72 + 2) + 7","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"43 * (88 - 4)","answer":"3612"}
{"prompt":"28 * 92 - 6","answer":"2570"}
{"prompt":"3 - 4 - 11","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"60 * (55 + 9) * 5","answer":"19200"}
{"prompt":"91 + 74","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"21 - 9 * 100 * 1","answer":"-879"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 2) - 67 * 9","answer":"-590"}
{"prompt":"10 - 89 * 9","answer":"-791"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 8 + 2) - 9","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"77 * 4 + 40","answer":"348"}
{"prompt":"((20 + 3) - 5) + 9","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 3) - (39 + 1)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"58 - 10 + (5 - 4 * 8)","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 9) * 73","answer":"5986"}
{"prompt":"7 + (77 + 10)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"72 - 84","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"35 + (97 * 3)","answer":"326"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 5) + 86 + 7 + 8","answer":"506"}
{"prompt":"17 * 93 + 3","answer":"1584"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 8 * 10) - 89","answer":"4391"}
{"prompt":"((47 + 6) + 7) - (50 + 3 * 4)","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"52 * 45","answer":"2340"}
{"prompt":"81 * 23","answer":"1863"}
{"prompt":"80 * 81 * 1","answer":"6480"}
{"prompt":"67 * 20","answer":"1340"}
{"prompt":"93 + (93 * 3) - 5","answer":"367"}
{"prompt":"26 + 15 * 6","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 9) + 16","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 5 + 2) + (7 - 9) + 2","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"83 * 66","answer":"5478"}
{"prompt":"18 * 66 + 7 * 8","answer":"1244"}
{"prompt":"60 * 63 - 2","answer":"3778"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 3) + 60 + 5","answer":"281"}
{"prompt":"29 - (94 * 5)","answer":"-441"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 2) + 6 - 81","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 9 - 4) + (98 - 10 - 2)","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"62 * 51","answer":"3162"}
{"prompt":"44 - 7 + 86 - 9","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"72 + 24","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"96 * 1 * 4 + 9","answer":"393"}
{"prompt":"5 - 1 - 5 * 17","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"54 - 4 - 25","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 4 - 5) + 47","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 4) - 1 - (93 * 9)","answer":"-742"}
{"prompt":"64 + 3","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"14 + (82 - 2)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"20 * 6","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"46 * 48","answer":"2208"}
{"prompt":"18 * 86","answer":"1548"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 4) - (43 - 7)","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"55 * ((9 - 9) + 7)","answer":"385"}
{"prompt":"96 - 9 + 90","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"99 - 1 - 6 + (73 * 3 - 9)","answer":"302"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 10) - 27 * 8 - 2","answer":"-159"}
{"prompt":"82 - 49","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"24 + 20","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"63 - 10 + (58 * 10) - 1","answer":"632"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 9) + 8 - 96 * 4","answer":"-345"}
{"prompt":"11 * ((38 + 1) + 4)","answer":"473"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 9) - 9","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"81 - 64","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 8) + 3 + 5 - 5","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 10) * 8 + 22 - 2 - 3","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"26 - 9 - (87 * 2 - 3)","answer":"-154"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 6) * 60","answer":"3780"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 2) * 24","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"33 - 39","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 5) - 2 * 77","answer":"256"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 1) + 62 + 9 * 10","answer":"203"}
{"prompt":"83 - 51 - 9 * 9","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"91 - 59","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 10) * 8 * 22 + 10","answer":"13210"}
{"prompt":"45 + 7","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 7) + 32","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"83 * (91 * 9) + 6","answer":"67983"}
{"prompt":"69 - 60","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 1) + 17","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"((42 + 3) + 2) - 51","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"47 - 89","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"68 * 89","answer":"6052"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 1) + 8 - (88 * 1 + 8)","answer":"-75"}
{"prompt":"42 + 2 - 99","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"23 * 85","answer":"1955"}
{"prompt":"79 + 21","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"61 - 84","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 10) + (55 - 3) + 10","answer":"1042"}
{"prompt":"5 - 54","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"((8 + 8) * 6) + (91 + 2 * 6)","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"58 - 6 * 26","answer":"-98"}
{"prompt":"64 - 1 + 2 + 95","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"64 * 12 + 7 - 9","answer":"766"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 1) * 10","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"((99 * 3) - 9) - 46","answer":"242"}
{"prompt":"91 * 67","answer":"6097"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 2 * 10) - (99 * 1)","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 6) + 3 - 58 + 10","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 3) + ((60 - 5) * 3)","answer":"217"}
{"prompt":"65 + 40","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"33 - 18","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"6 * 7","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 4) * (94 - 4)","answer":"32040"}
{"prompt":"62 + 20 - 4","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"85 * 49","answer":"4165"}
{"prompt":"31 + 87","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"66 * 6 + 6 + 4","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 4) * 94","answer":"6580"}
{"prompt":"1 * ((23 * 10) * 8)","answer":"1840"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 10 - 5) + 40","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 9) + 11 + 7","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"23 * (79 * 2) - 1","answer":"3633"}
{"prompt":"88 + 7 - 51","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"20 - 3 * 1 - (5 * 10) + 9","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"8 - 58","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 5) + 60 + 4","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"77 + 3 + (48 * 8)","answer":"464"}
{"prompt":"71 - (81 + 7)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 5) + 2 + 25","answer":"492"}
{"prompt":"18 - 8 - 9 * 21","answer":"-179"}
{"prompt":"((92 + 10) - 9) + 64 - 10","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 5) + 2 - (99 - 10 - 1)","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"((72 + 1) + 10) - 70 + 7 * 2","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"86 * 2 + 62","answer":"234"}
{"prompt":"83 - 8 * 82","answer":"-573"}
{"prompt":"18 - 26 - 8 + 2","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"37 + 9","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"5 - 45","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 7) + 53","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"17 - 57 * 2","answer":"-97"}
{"prompt":"81 - 9 + 52","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 4 - 5) * 55","answer":"5445"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 3) * ((22 * 10) + 9)","answer":"2061"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 1) * 4 + 93","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"65 + (23 - 1)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 6) - (23 * 4)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 1) + (73 * 10)","answer":"778"}
{"prompt":"54 * 48","answer":"2592"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 5) + 4 + 74","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(69 * 3) + 9 * 59","answer":"738"}
{"prompt":"85 - 82","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"21 - 82 + 2","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"7 - 98","answer":"-91"}
{"prompt":"38 + (58 + 7 - 10)","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"10 + ((96 + 9) * 1)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"79 * 7 * 1","answer":"553"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 7) * 6 - 79","answer":"221"}
{"prompt":"65 * 52 + 2 * 10","answer":"3400"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 3 - 8) - 33","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"88 * 9 + 70 * 8 * 5","answer":"3592"}
{"prompt":"59 * 10 + 1 * 13","answer":"603"}
{"prompt":"12 + 2 + 7","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"44 - 5","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"42 - 16","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"84 + (38 - 9)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"65 + (4 - 6)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"59 - 91 * 5","answer":"-396"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 9) - 28","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"19 - 78","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"87 * (89 - 8) + 7","answer":"7054"}
{"prompt":"((38 + 1) - 4) * 31 + 6","answer":"1091"}
{"prompt":"1 + 40","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"45 - 79","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 1 - 4) + ((98 * 10) + 2)","answer":"989"}
{"prompt":"67 + 59","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"((41 * 2) * 3) - ((40 + 9) + 9)","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"90 - 9 + 14","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"45 - 84","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"34 + 51 + 10","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"61 - 9 + 72","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"51 - 68 - 6","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"84 + (23 - 7)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"38 + 1 + ((31 + 9) + 2)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"51 - 11","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"41 - ((71 + 2) * 1)","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"64 * (69 - 7)","answer":"3968"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 2 + 4) - 40","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"98 - 4 * 8","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 10 * 7) - 5","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"73 - 68","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"9 - 71","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"32 - 26","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 9) * (72 + 7) * 5","answer":"302175"}
{"prompt":"97 + 6 + 82 + 4","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"63 + 22","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"25 * 3 + 7 + 8","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"23 - (26 + 10)","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(58 * 6 - 5) - 54 * 2","answer":"235"}
{"prompt":"((2 - 8) + 3) + 33 - 9","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"36 - (54 * 4)","answer":"-180"}
{"prompt":"((3 - 8) - 7) * 83 - 1","answer":"-997"}
{"prompt":"54 - 9 + 7 * 78 - 10","answer":"581"}
{"prompt":"9 - 10 + 19","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"27 + 7 + 43","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"24 - 9 + 4 * 17 + 5","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"32 + 2 * (41 + 8) - 8","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"31 * 6 + 5 - 28 * 7","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"51 + 29","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"60 * (36 + 8)","answer":"2640"}
{"prompt":"11 - 3 * 96","answer":"-277"}
{"prompt":"29 - 1 + (68 * 8)","answer":"572"}
{"prompt":"94 * 30","answer":"2820"}
{"prompt":"85 - 6 - (99 - 2) - 4","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 2) - 7 + 86 + 10","answer":"267"}
{"prompt":"((93 + 10) * 9) * 70 * 8","answer":"519120"}
{"prompt":"12 + (16 + 2)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"66 + 3 * 66","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"20 + 74","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"22 + ((56 - 8) + 4)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"68 - 29","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 2) * 16","answer":"928"}
{"prompt":"93 + (2 * 7)","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 5) * 4 + 65 + 3","answer":"332"}
{"prompt":"96 - 92","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 2) - (46 * 9)","answer":"-408"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 9) + 9 + 10","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"15 - 43","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 3) * 9 * (56 - 6) * 7","answer":"463050"}
{"prompt":"40 * 68","answer":"2720"}
{"prompt":"((85 - 3) * 4) - 9 * 7","answer":"265"}
{"prompt":"72 - 1 + 3 - (8 - 4) - 3","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"13 + 29","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"97 + 10 + (97 - 2 * 10)","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 10 - 5) * 17","answer":"15895"}
{"prompt":"((10 - 6) - 8) + 83 - 7","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"((15 - 4) - 4) - 24","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"95 + ((35 + 10) + 5)","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 8) - 39","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"17 + 86","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"84 * (82 * 1 * 1)","answer":"6888"}
{"prompt":"((4 + 7) * 2) * 75","answer":"1650"}
{"prompt":"((86 + 6) * 4) * (35 + 4) + 8","answer":"14360"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 5) + 1 + 74 + 4 * 6","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 3) * 7 * 28","answer":"6468"}
{"prompt":"38 * (12 * 8) - 3","answer":"3645"}
{"prompt":"56 * 98","answer":"5488"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 8) + 27 * 5","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"50 - 17","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"92 + 68","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 10 + 2) + 25","answer":"807"}
{"prompt":"52 * 100","answer":"5200"}
{"prompt":"64 * 10 + 6 - 66 + 1","answer":"581"}
{"prompt":"70 + ((75 + 1) + 8)","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"55 + 6 - 4 * 72","answer":"-227"}
{"prompt":"96 * 7 + (25 + 6 * 3)","answer":"715"}
{"prompt":"11 * 23","answer":"253"}
{"prompt":"22 * 63","answer":"1386"}
{"prompt":"22 * 5","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 3) * 5 * 14","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"71 - 10 + 3 - (19 * 7)","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"34 + 5 * 31","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"36 - 8 + 53 - 5","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"83 + (37 * 1 - 6)","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"27 - 70 + 1 * 10","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"55 - 95","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"34 * 56","answer":"1904"}
{"prompt":"43 - 7","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 8) - 1 * 37","answer":"595"}
{"prompt":"32 * ((82 + 6) * 2)","answer":"5632"}
{"prompt":"77 - ((3 * 2) * 7)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"(66 - 2) - (60 * 8 * 7)","answer":"-3296"}
{"prompt":"4 - 42","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 6) * 5 * 25","answer":"26250"}
{"prompt":"47 * 77","answer":"3619"}
{"prompt":"17 * (23 + 7)","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"26 * 85 * 3","answer":"6630"}
{"prompt":"46 - 10 * 39 - 3","answer":"-347"}
{"prompt":"56 - 10 + (33 * 7)","answer":"277"}
{"prompt":"80 + 53","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 6) - 65","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"64 - 12 - 9 + 1","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"68 - 63","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"13 + 33","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 2) * 8 * 40","answer":"10560"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 8) + (98 - 4)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 2) + 2 - (77 * 1)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"34 * 3 * 90","answer":"9180"}
{"prompt":"53 - 85","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"23 - 71","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"89 - 10 * (84 + 4) * 2","answer":"-1671"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 6) * 10 + (39 - 9)","answer":"700"}
{"prompt":"96 + 6","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"((98 - 10) + 3) * 76","answer":"6916"}
{"prompt":"40 * 58 + 7 - 2","answer":"2325"}
{"prompt":"74 + 7 * 9 + (1 + 10)","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"86 * (80 * 9)","answer":"61920"}
{"prompt":"67 + 8 + (14 - 9)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"33 * 35","answer":"1155"}
{"prompt":"32 * 8 + 66 + 5","answer":"327"}
{"prompt":"49 * 53 - 9","answer":"2588"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 10) - 75","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 1) - 4) - 77","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"69 + 76","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"30 * (66 + 6 + 8)","answer":"2400"}
{"prompt":"9 - 7","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"99 * 15","answer":"1485"}
{"prompt":"((19 * 2) * 3) * 1 * 4 * 3","answer":"1368"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 7) + 1","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 3 + 2) + 39","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"21 - 8 - (43 + 4)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 9) * 88 * 8","answer":"532224"}
{"prompt":"95 + 63","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"22 - 1 - 93","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"56 + (39 * 9) + 3","answer":"410"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 3) + 6) - 18","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"48 * 7 + 100","answer":"436"}
{"prompt":"42 + 16","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"38 - 5 - (74 * 7)","answer":"-485"}
{"prompt":"93 - 5 - 6 + (49 - 1)","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"20 * (90 * 5)","answer":"9000"}
{"prompt":"8 + 37","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"83 + 91","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 5) + 3 * 79","answer":"502"}
{"prompt":"41 - 69","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"1 * 7 - ((60 * 4) + 10)","answer":"-243"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 3 + 7) + 55 * 5 * 8","answer":"2495"}
{"prompt":"38 - 64","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"12 - 96","answer":"-84"}
{"prompt":"14 - 76","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"75 + (8 + 2 * 9)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"28 - 2 * (44 - 2)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 8 + 1) * 53 + 3","answer":"12776"}
{"prompt":"((22 + 10) * 6) * ((61 * 5) * 9)","answer":"527040"}
{"prompt":"99 * (26 * 8)","answer":"20592"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 1) * (53 + 8) * 9","answer":"36783"}
{"prompt":"60 - (8 * 6 * 2)","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"100 * 7 + 3 + 20 * 7","answer":"843"}
{"prompt":"((90 + 3) * 5) - 100 * 9","answer":"-435"}
{"prompt":"46 * ((58 + 4) + 7)","answer":"3174"}
{"prompt":"57 - 42","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 5) + 99","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"7 * 7 * 93","answer":"4557"}
{"prompt":"56 * 2 * 7 + 74","answer":"858"}
{"prompt":"((28 + 8) + 5) + 12","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"11 + 2 + ((91 + 9) - 7)","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"43 + 42","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"98 + (61 * 5)","answer":"403"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 7) * 43","answer":"2580"}
{"prompt":"53 * (54 + 8 * 1)","answer":"3286"}
{"prompt":"65 + 3 - (87 - 8 * 7)","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"30 * 40 * 5 * 1","answer":"6000"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 6) * ((69 + 10) - 1)","answer":"1950"}
{"prompt":"3 - 53 - 4","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 6) + 6 + 93","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"(81 + 3) - ((82 - 3) + 4)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"37 - (57 - 5 + 1)","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"62 - 10 * (30 + 9) + 3","answer":"-325"}
{"prompt":"68 - 1 - 7 - 63","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"88 - 6 * 1 - 5 + 4","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 9) - 8 + 28","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"2 * 56","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 10) * (91 - 3 * 2)","answer":"53550"}
{"prompt":"64 + 69","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"93 * (77 * 8) * 4","answer":"229152"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 2) * 5 - (28 + 1 - 5)","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"57 * 8 * 3","answer":"1368"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 1) + 73 * 10","answer":"744"}
{"prompt":"40 + 26","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"60 - 45","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"((80 + 4) - 5) - ((36 - 10) - 6)","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"81 + 2 * 48","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"92 * 34 + 6 * 5","answer":"3158"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 3 - 7) - (30 + 5) - 7","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"33 * 94 - 6 - 6","answer":"3090"}
{"prompt":"(86 + 1 * 7) * 38","answer":"3534"}
{"prompt":"((98 - 10) + 9) - (14 - 3)","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"34 + 65","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 9 * 2) - 31","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 8 * 8) - ((42 - 6) + 3)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 7) + 62","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"40 + 5 + 6 + (53 * 10) + 2","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 2 * 7) + (20 * 8)","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"84 - 99","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"69 + 15","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 6) + 45","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 2) - 1 * 21 * 4","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 6 + 10) - (95 + 7 - 7)","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 8) - 3 * 60","answer":"-98"}
{"prompt":"23 - 79","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 9 - 1) + 93","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"57 * 65","answer":"3705"}
{"prompt":"50 * (55 + 6) * 3","answer":"9150"}
{"prompt":"75 - 49","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 9 * 2) - 46 - 8","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"28 * 42","answer":"1176"}
{"prompt":"68 * 79 - 8","answer":"5364"}
{"prompt":"78 - 26 * 6 - 6","answer":"-84"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 10 * 10) * ((19 * 6) - 6)","answer":"17496"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 2 - 7) + 88 * 5","answer":"458"}
{"prompt":"96 + 6 * 35 + 9 + 8","answer":"323"}
{"prompt":"(79 + 7 + 5) * 15","answer":"1365"}
{"prompt":"85 * 10 + (16 * 3) - 3","answer":"895"}
{"prompt":"13 + 38","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"88 * 82","answer":"7216"}
{"prompt":"72 - 3 + 70 - 6","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"16 + 3 + 6","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 9) + 67","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 3 - 6) + 28 - 8","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"54 * 4 - 32","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"14 * 65","answer":"910"}
{"prompt":"95 * 80","answer":"7600"}
{"prompt":"20 + (52 - 10)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"11 - (16 * 8) + 4","answer":"-113"}
{"prompt":"47 * 17 * 4","answer":"3196"}
{"prompt":"7 * 7 - 85","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"85 + 32","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 9 + 6) - (1 - 1) + 3","answer":"747"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 4) + (13 + 6 - 8)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"47 - 6 - 45 - 8","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"7 - 15","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"33 + 92","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"29 + 4 * 7 - (13 - 10) - 7","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"57 * 48 + 8","answer":"2744"}
{"prompt":"((69 * 5) - 5) * 82","answer":"27880"}
{"prompt":"47 + 3 + (61 + 10) * 8","answer":"618"}
{"prompt":"94 * 31","answer":"2914"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 6) + 29","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 5) + ((97 + 7) - 9)","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"75 + 60 - 1 - 1","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"19 * 6 - 89","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"94 * 5 + (26 + 7)","answer":"503"}
{"prompt":"43 * 10 - ((33 - 7) + 6)","answer":"398"}
{"prompt":"58 + 9 + 9 * ((75 - 7) * 10)","answer":"6187"}
{"prompt":"30 * 58 - 1 + 5","answer":"1744"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 5 - 4) * (68 - 3)","answer":"4160"}
{"prompt":"70 - 2 + 79 + 6","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"89 - (46 * 4)","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"24 * (100 * 2) + 6","answer":"4806"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 3) * 79","answer":"7110"}
{"prompt":"77 * 7 + (30 - 9 * 5)","answer":"524"}
{"prompt":"29 + 9 - 4 * 24","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"53 * 5 - 1 - (35 + 6 + 3)","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 3) + 86","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"47 - 83","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"12 - (9 - 5)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 6) * 1 - 63 - 5","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 7) * ((86 * 9) * 5)","answer":"158670"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 2 + 8) - 21","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"71 + 64 - 3 + 1","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"91 - 10 - 10 * 74 - 3","answer":"-662"}
{"prompt":"36 + 3 - 39","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"35 + 7 - 65","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 3 - 7) - 99 * 10","answer":"-929"}
{"prompt":"58 + 4","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"69 - 5 * 47","answer":"-166"}
{"prompt":"41 - 76","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"((95 * 1) + 8) + (14 - 8 * 4)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"16 - 86 + 1","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"45 * 32","answer":"1440"}
{"prompt":"25 + 2 + 8 * (23 * 6)","answer":"1131"}
{"prompt":"43 * (59 + 8)","answer":"2881"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 6) * 3 - 88 - 4 + 5","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"60 * 42","answer":"2520"}
{"prompt":"66 + 7 - 3 - 5","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(48 + 9) - ((30 + 6) + 1)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"85 + 6 - 7 - 3 - 8 + 5","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"92 + 49","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"86 - 71","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 8) * 24","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"51 * 80","answer":"4080"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 8 + 5) - 68","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"98 + 1 + 80","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"13 + 10 * 36","answer":"373"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 9) - 41","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"70 + 5 - (21 * 9)","answer":"-114"}
{"prompt":"97 * 16","answer":"1552"}
{"prompt":"((31 - 8) + 8) * 86","answer":"2666"}
{"prompt":"6 + 59","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"21 - 58 * 10","answer":"-559"}
{"prompt":"47 * 4 * 83","answer":"15604"}
{"prompt":"6 - 9 * 26","answer":"-228"}
{"prompt":"77 + 78 * 2 + 4","answer":"237"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 9) - (73 + 5) * 7","answer":"-482"}
{"prompt":"31 + 12","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"12 + 22","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"26 + ((29 + 6) * 10)","answer":"376"}
{"prompt":"88 * 87 - 5","answer":"7651"}
{"prompt":"52 - 3 * 53","answer":"-107"}
{"prompt":"58 - 64 + 1 + 8","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"74 - 14","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"23 * 48","answer":"1104"}
{"prompt":"6 - (92 * 4 + 4)","answer":"-366"}
{"prompt":"5 + 6","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"36 - (56 * 1) + 5","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"78 + 22","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"6 - (25 + 4) * 10","answer":"-284"}
{"prompt":"97 + (93 - 2)","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"((7 * 7) * 9) * (33 * 7)","answer":"101871"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 5) - ((91 + 2) * 3)","answer":"-224"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 7) + ((96 * 7) + 3)","answer":"1221"}
{"prompt":"32 * 94","answer":"3008"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 2) * 49","answer":"1470"}
{"prompt":"((90 * 9) - 9) + 18","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"((64 + 1) * 1) + (70 + 2) - 5","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 8) * 67","answer":"10184"}
{"prompt":"50 - (56 - 2) * 10","answer":"-490"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 4) - 2 - (77 - 8)","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"41 * 8","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 6) * 2) + 67","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"48 * 7 * 6 - 17","answer":"1999"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 1 + 7) * (9 - 3 + 2)","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"67 + 6","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"28 * 8 * 7 - 31","answer":"1537"}
{"prompt":"81 - 19 + 4 * 3","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 1) * ((20 - 1) - 6)","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 6 - 1) + 4","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"96 - 63","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 8 * 6) * ((57 - 6) + 6)","answer":"-2394"}
{"prompt":"70 - (30 * 5)","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 2) * 4 - 79","answer":"313"}
{"prompt":"40 - 47","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"6 + (40 - 1 - 5)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"96 - 48","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"78 + (87 * 9)","answer":"861"}
{"prompt":"(16 - 7) - 1 - 15","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 9) * 8 - 41","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"5 - 39","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 4) - 80","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"80 - 8","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"13 * (4 * 6) * 4","answer":"1248"}
{"prompt":"96 * 6 - (46 + 4)","answer":"526"}
{"prompt":"49 - 7 - 3 - 59","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"13 - 14","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"17 + (69 + 2 - 7)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"99 - 51","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((84 * 4) + 1) - 74","answer":"263"}
{"prompt":"70 - 56","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(69 * 5) + 49 * 4 * 10","answer":"2305"}
{"prompt":"38 - (2 + 3) - 10","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"11 - 56","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"23 * 6 * 52","answer":"7176"}
{"prompt":"70 * 3 + 23 + 6","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"99 + 32","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 1) * 6 + 18 * 3","answer":"276"}
{"prompt":"45 * 73 - 5","answer":"3280"}
{"prompt":"((38 - 1) - 10) - 42","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"((82 - 10) - 8) + (16 + 2) - 2","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"9 - 96","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 8) - 4 - (91 + 2)","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 4 * 5) * 60","answer":"2700"}
{"prompt":"87 * 72","answer":"6264"}
{"prompt":"11 - 3 - (25 * 6) * 1","answer":"-142"}
{"prompt":"((53 + 7) * 8) * 4","answer":"1920"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 5) * 17 * 6","answer":"6120"}
{"prompt":"65 + 70","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"21 * 9 + (56 * 2) * 6","answer":"861"}
{"prompt":"86 - 8 - 70 * 4 + 10","answer":"-192"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 7) + (12 - 1 - 10)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"27 + (34 - 4)","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"73 - 49","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"65 - 100","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"24 - 79","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"43 + 41 - 10 + 9","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"22 - 24","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"59 + 98","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"80 + 1 * 3 - 30","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 10) + 8 * 12","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"36 - 84","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"29 - 86","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"92 + 74","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"80 * 1 + 45","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"17 * 2 + ((68 + 7) + 9)","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"40 + 7 + 4 - (89 + 7 + 6)","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"46 * (68 - 8)","answer":"2760"}
{"prompt":"53 + 5 - 10 - 98","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"83 + 7 + 67 + 6","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"77 + (5 - 4)","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"81 + 9","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"87 * (84 + 3)","answer":"7569"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 1) + 5 + 51 - 8","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"37 - 47","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"43 * 6","answer":"258"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 6) - 77 + 2","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 3 - 3) - 82","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"46 + 5 - 5 * (12 + 9)","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"39 * 71 - 8 - 8","answer":"2753"}
{"prompt":"65 + (78 * 6 - 1)","answer":"532"}
{"prompt":"80 + 37","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 8) - 8 * 54","answer":"-405"}
{"prompt":"51 * 3 * 32 + 8","answer":"4904"}
{"prompt":"10 * 66","answer":"660"}
{"prompt":"100 + 25","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"17 * 7 + 65","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"34 * 75 + 8 - 4","answer":"2554"}
{"prompt":"54 + 6 * 1 - 10","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 8 - 2) * 96","answer":"3264"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 10) - 51 * 1","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"72 * 86 - 7","answer":"6185"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 3) - (88 - 9)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"62 + 30","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 1 * 5) * 33","answer":"15675"}
{"prompt":"40 + (32 - 10)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"19 * 33","answer":"627"}
{"prompt":"79 * 56","answer":"4424"}
{"prompt":"80 - 24 * 9","answer":"-136"}
{"prompt":"73 - (70 * 10)","answer":"-627"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 2) * 9 + 6 + 3","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 7) * (95 + 7)","answer":"22134"}
{"prompt":"10 - 3 - 9 - 82 + 3 - 2","answer":"-83"}
{"prompt":"72 - 3 + 2 - 83","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"6 + (25 + 8)","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"34 + (26 + 6 - 1)","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 3) + 92","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"26 * 94","answer":"2444"}
{"prompt":"(22 * 8 - 5) + 80","answer":"251"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 1) + 22 * 7","answer":"236"}
{"prompt":"76 + 10 * 7","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"81 + 69","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"81 - 58","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"76 - 34","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 1) + ((72 - 8) * 8)","answer":"577"}
{"prompt":"11 - 4 - (78 * 6)","answer":"-461"}
{"prompt":"53 * 39 * 10 + 9","answer":"20679"}
{"prompt":"73 - (31 * 5) + 10","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 2) + 7) * 30","answer":"1350"}
{"prompt":"25 - 2 + 10 - 88","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"58 + 48 - 8 - 1","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"47 + 3 * (64 - 9)","answer":"212"}
{"prompt":"((65 * 3) - 4) * 9","answer":"1719"}
{"prompt":"89 * 5 - (75 + 8 - 9)","answer":"371"}
{"prompt":"38 - 4 - 15","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 3) - 5 * (62 - 8)","answer":"-266"}
{"prompt":"8 + 69","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"52 + 50","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"69 + 70","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"11 + 9","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"65 - 38","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"64 + 83","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 6) + 73","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"((17 - 4) * 1) * 13","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"36 - 8 * 99","answer":"-756"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 8 + 6) + 50 * 8 - 6","answer":"473"}
{"prompt":"4 - 14","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"((61 - 5) - 5) + 58","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"25 - ((6 + 9) - 7)","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"94 + 98 - 7","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"22 * 72","answer":"1584"}
{"prompt":"76 + 3 - 68 + 5","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"92 - 89","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"46 + 57","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"92 - (9 * 5)","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 5) + 3 - 29","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"15 + 9 - 5 - (53 * 4)","answer":"-193"}
{"prompt":"65 * 1 + 11","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"97 * ((23 - 9) - 5)","answer":"873"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 4) + 47","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"54 * 47","answer":"2538"}
{"prompt":"2 + 52","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 5 * 4) - 54","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 2) - 77","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"72 - 7 + 30","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"55 * (38 - 4) * 3","answer":"5610"}
{"prompt":"27 + 30 + 2 * 3","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"60 - 17","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"9 + 10 + 3 + 33 - 9","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"97 - (2 * 3)","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"61 - 4 * (65 + 5) - 3","answer":"-222"}
{"prompt":"27 * (64 + 7 + 5)","answer":"2052"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 7) - 42 * 2","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 3) - 4 - (78 * 5) - 8","answer":"-312"}
{"prompt":"12 * (9 - 7 * 3)","answer":"-144"}
{"prompt":"92 - (25 - 2)","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"36 + (51 + 7) * 6","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"77 + 4","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 10 + 6) * 31","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"67 + 3 - 61 + 9","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"42 + (60 - 5) * 2","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"39 - ((77 * 8) - 10)","answer":"-567"}
{"prompt":"19 - 68 - 10","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 3) - ((24 * 8) * 5)","answer":"-891"}
{"prompt":"14 * 10 + 66 - 2","answer":"204"}
{"prompt":"43 * 10 - 8 + 5","answer":"427"}
{"prompt":"55 * 73 - 8 - 5","answer":"4002"}
{"prompt":"((7 + 1) - 4) * 65","answer":"260"}
{"prompt":"70 - 71","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 7 + 9) - 73","answer":"461"}
{"prompt":"17 * 9","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"6 * 34","answer":"204"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 4) - 81","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"(22 * 6 - 4) + 35","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"60 - ((53 - 1) + 4)","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(69 * 6) - ((49 + 2) - 10)","answer":"373"}
{"prompt":"56 * 83","answer":"4648"}
{"prompt":"44 - (34 * 10 - 8)","answer":"-288"}
{"prompt":"2 + 3 - 21 * 7","answer":"-142"}
{"prompt":"85 + 30","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"((85 - 3) - 6) - 31","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"((86 + 7) + 10) - 66","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"24 - (67 - 8)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"54 + 12","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"58 * 99","answer":"5742"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 10 + 8) - 60","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"54 * 26","answer":"1404"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 2) * 1 + 80","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 8) - 40","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"61 + ((29 - 4) + 10)","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"87 + 7 * 3 + 33","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 6) - (14 - 2 + 1)","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 2) - 4 + 89","answer":"211"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 1) + 25","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"52 - 72","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 9) + 8 * (25 + 1)","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"62 - 2 - 10 * (81 + 10)","answer":"-850"}
{"prompt":"((73 - 6) + 9) + 33 + 4","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"47 + 8 * 10 + (66 - 4)","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 5 + 3) * 25","answer":"1175"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 10 + 4) - 77","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"100 - 29 - 1 - 4","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"39 + 33 + 10","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"90 - 8 * (86 + 9)","answer":"-670"}
{"prompt":"71 - 48 - 5","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 5 + 2) * 1","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"86 + ((85 * 5) - 9)","answer":"502"}
{"prompt":"67 + 7 + (63 + 9 + 1)","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 8) * 9 - 89","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"41 + (52 + 4 + 6)","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"6 + ((99 - 10) + 10)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"51 - 3 + 57","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"91 - 70","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 8) - 10 * 25","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"76 * 1 + ((9 - 7) - 7)","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"78 * 95","answer":"7410"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 1) * 8 + 39","answer":"735"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 1) + 9 + (9 * 9)","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"((44 * 10) - 9) - 87","answer":"344"}
{"prompt":"93 - (60 * 3 + 3)","answer":"-90"}
{"prompt":"2 + 37","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"12 - 34","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"88 * 1 - 5","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 3) * (96 * 5) + 7","answer":"24007"}
{"prompt":"74 * (25 + 4)","answer":"2146"}
{"prompt":"10 - 3 * 5","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"60 * (72 - 5)","answer":"4020"}
{"prompt":"14 - 92","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"5 + 9 - 7","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"41 + 32","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"84 + 91 - 9","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"34 * 8 - 49","answer":"223"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 1) - 41 - 5","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"21 + (46 + 10 - 3)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"19 * 7 - 10 - (93 - 8) * 4","answer":"-217"}
{"prompt":"19 + ((100 - 2) + 4)","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"71 * 3","answer":"213"}
{"prompt":"75 * 77","answer":"5775"}
{"prompt":"62 - (46 - 5) - 7","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"93 * 58","answer":"5394"}
{"prompt":"48 * 9 * ((41 * 1) + 5)","answer":"19872"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 6) - 61","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"47 * (74 - 3 + 2)","answer":"3431"}
{"prompt":"97 * 54","answer":"5238"}
{"prompt":"70 * (52 - 4) + 3","answer":"3363"}
{"prompt":"(88 - 4 * 1) + 40","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"70 * 77","answer":"5390"}
{"prompt":"5 - 45","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"((83 * 10) - 1) * (70 - 2)","answer":"56372"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 6 + 8) + 97","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"38 * (76 + 2) + 7","answer":"2971"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 7) + 9 - (65 * 3)","answer":"-152"}
{"prompt":"24 * (28 - 3) - 3","answer":"597"}
{"prompt":"78 + 1 * (23 - 1)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 2) + 2 - 69","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"41 - (51 + 5)","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 2) - 54","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(13 - 4) - 6 * 55 * 6","answer":"-1971"}
{"prompt":"53 - 8 - 1 + (26 + 8)","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 3) + 82 * 8","answer":"722"}
{"prompt":"17 - 10 - (11 + 1)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 3) + 45","answer":"333"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 4 + 2) * 19","answer":"5814"}
{"prompt":"21 - 2 * (34 * 5) + 10","answer":"-309"}
{"prompt":"51 + 64","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 10) + 2","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"45 - (51 * 10)","answer":"-465"}
{"prompt":"72 + 6 - 3 + 23","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"37 * 3 - 17","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"11 + 3","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"7 - 81","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"4 * 10 + 24","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"80 + 1 - 36","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"71 + 3 + 48","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"2 + (59 - 9)","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"44 * 21 * 9","answer":"8316"}
{"prompt":"71 + (18 - 3)","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"36 * 8 - (48 + 8) + 4","answer":"236"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 4) * 57 - 1","answer":"284"}
{"prompt":"93 * 3 * 8 - 74","answer":"2158"}
{"prompt":"11 + 3 - 7 + (97 + 9)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"100 - 90 * 2","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"98 + 4 * 6 * 58","answer":"1490"}
{"prompt":"80 - 6 * 37 - 8","answer":"-150"}
{"prompt":"59 * 44","answer":"2596"}
{"prompt":"86 - 21","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 7) - 10) - (79 * 2)","answer":"238"}
{"prompt":"85 + 29 * 7","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"95 * (96 + 3)","answer":"9405"}
{"prompt":"83 * 40 + 6","answer":"3326"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 4) * 22","answer":"1056"}
{"prompt":"41 * 74","answer":"3034"}
{"prompt":"80 * 44 - 10 * 4","answer":"3480"}
{"prompt":"61 + (57 - 2)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"9 + 89","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"24 * 4 - 34 + 6","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"40 * 37","answer":"1480"}
{"prompt":"77 + 7 + ((49 * 10) + 9)","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"19 + (85 - 2)","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"75 - 84 - 2","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"71 + 6","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"33 + (90 - 4 - 4)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"85 - 58","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"11 * 94","answer":"1034"}
{"prompt":"77 * 64","answer":"4928"}
{"prompt":"96 - 10 - 8 - 74 + 6 - 2","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"78 + 88","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"11 - 8 - 94","answer":"-91"}
{"prompt":"15 * 79","answer":"1185"}
{"prompt":"95 * 59","answer":"5605"}
{"prompt":"79 - (10 - 5 + 10)","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"84 * 7 + 59","answer":"647"}
{"prompt":"16 * 100","answer":"1600"}
{"prompt":"((87 - 8) - 3) - 72 * 4","answer":"-212"}
{"prompt":"11 - 27 + 2 + 3","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"67 * 6 + 23","answer":"425"}
{"prompt":"67 * 37 - 10","answer":"2469"}
{"prompt":"68 - 16","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"11 + 8 + 87 - 3","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"23 * 32","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"49 + 95","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 6) + ((60 * 9) * 3)","answer":"2220"}
{"prompt":"((17 - 5) * 4) + (80 + 10)","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"12 - 48","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 10 + 10) + 29 + 9","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 7 * 8) + 35","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"28 + 55","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"61 * (30 - 7)","answer":"1403"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 7) - 8 - 32 * 9 + 9","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"75 + (75 - 7 - 5)","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"96 * 8 * (37 - 1) * 3","answer":"82944"}
{"prompt":"28 + 7 * 5 - 62","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"74 - 19","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 7) + 26","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"66 - 78","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"((74 + 4) * 4) * 8","answer":"2496"}
{"prompt":"69 + ((19 * 2) * 9)","answer":"411"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 7) - 10 + 35 * 9","answer":"325"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 1) * 9 * 20","answer":"12960"}
{"prompt":"80 - 3 + 3 + (37 - 2)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"53 - 8","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"60 * 33","answer":"1980"}
{"prompt":"12 - 75","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"60 - 88 - 5 + 2","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"38 + 6","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"1 - 16 * 7","answer":"-111"}
{"prompt":"26 * 20","answer":"520"}
{"prompt":"9 - 49 + 6 * 10","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"((8 * 3) * 4) * (69 - 2)","answer":"6432"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 5) - (89 * 10)","answer":"-894"}
{"prompt":"79 - 49 + 10","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"((10 * 9) + 10) - (59 + 5)","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"68 * 31","answer":"2108"}
{"prompt":"75 * 85","answer":"6375"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 7) + 36","answer":"694"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 1 + 6) * 23 + 8","answer":"1457"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 7 * 2) + (86 - 10)","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"21 + (88 + 6)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"82 - (98 * 10) * 8","answer":"-7758"}
{"prompt":"25 + (41 - 5) - 3","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 7) * 5 - 14 - 9 - 7","answer":"425"}
{"prompt":"10 - 3","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 6) * 35 + 6","answer":"1826"}
{"prompt":"61 * 6 - 9","answer":"357"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 2 * 8) - 37","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"((68 - 4) + 10) + 19","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"85 * 93","answer":"7905"}
{"prompt":"66 - 15","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((73 + 10) + 6) * 37","answer":"3293"}
{"prompt":"73 - (49 - 3)","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 2) * 1 - 73 - 6","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"72 * 59","answer":"4248"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 9 * 6) - 28","answer":"2888"}
{"prompt":"69 + 3 - 81 * 10","answer":"-738"}
{"prompt":"7 - 8 + 60","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"45 - 2 - 4 + ((90 + 4) * 1)","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"63 + (13 - 4)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"87 - 9","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"21 + 96","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"((74 - 8) - 5) - 13","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 10 + 9) + 69 * 3","answer":"224"}
{"prompt":"73 + (15 * 4) * 3","answer":"253"}
{"prompt":"51 - 5 * (54 + 2) - 2","answer":"-231"}
{"prompt":"15 - 10 * 27 * 8","answer":"-2145"}
{"prompt":"66 - 65 * 8 + 6","answer":"-448"}
{"prompt":"100 + 3","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 10) - 91","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 10) + (80 * 9)","answer":"806"}
{"prompt":"51 * (47 - 10)","answer":"1887"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 6) + 39","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"68 - 93","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"87 - 5 - 67","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"17 * 1","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 9 - 9) + (71 * 5) * 9","answer":"3197"}
{"prompt":"32 - (79 + 7 * 6)","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 3) + 78","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 9) * ((35 - 10) - 5)","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"4 * 6 - 2 + 40","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"20 - (90 - 2)","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"72 + 47","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"97 - 1 - 52","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"73 + (89 + 7)","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"58 * 35","answer":"2030"}
{"prompt":"75 + 45","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"95 * 12","answer":"1140"}
{"prompt":"95 - 1 - 5 + 1 - 10","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"57 + 72","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"28 * 14","answer":"392"}
{"prompt":"1 - 1 * 2 * 4 - 6","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"81 * (4 + 7)","answer":"891"}
{"prompt":"81 - 4 - 84","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 10) + (95 + 1)","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 1) - ((72 * 4) - 1)","answer":"-212"}
{"prompt":"9 - (53 * 10) + 7","answer":"-514"}
{"prompt":"37 + 7","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"73 * 2 - 64 - 9","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"96 - 62 - 9 + 2","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"12 * 8 * 66 - 1 * 9","answer":"6327"}
{"prompt":"98 * 27","answer":"2646"}
{"prompt":"((57 - 3) * 5) - 17","answer":"253"}
{"prompt":"92 + (67 * 8)","answer":"628"}
{"prompt":"6 - 23 + 7","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"87 * 8 + 10 * (37 - 3) + 5","answer":"1041"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 8) * 19 + 2","answer":"325"}
{"prompt":"70 + 9 + 65 - 9","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"34 + 3 * 76","answer":"262"}
{"prompt":"41 - 50","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"6 * 26","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"1 + ((56 * 7) - 10)","answer":"383"}
{"prompt":"80 - 94","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"86 * 38","answer":"3268"}
{"prompt":"55 * 82","answer":"4510"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 2) - (54 * 6 + 8)","answer":"-293"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 9) - 2 + (83 + 10 * 4)","answer":"841"}
{"prompt":"11 - 89 + 6","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 8 + 6) - 46 + 5","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"98 + (83 + 2 + 6)","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"66 - (68 - 5)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 8) * 4 + ((40 - 5) + 1)","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"22 * 1 - 1 * (63 + 1) + 10","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"76 - (98 * 8) + 5","answer":"-703"}
{"prompt":"55 * 3 + 31 + 7","answer":"203"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 8 - 3) * (1 - 10)","answer":"-306"}
{"prompt":"((68 - 8) - 1) - 31","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"41 * 1","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"10 * 6 + (4 - 3 + 5)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"14 + 78","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"47 * 2 + 3 + 9","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"16 * (73 - 2)","answer":"1136"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 5) * 35","answer":"13650"}
{"prompt":"65 + ((80 - 3) * 6)","answer":"527"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 1) * 45","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"68 - (70 - 9)","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 6) - 1 + ((45 - 4) - 2)","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 7) - 83","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"23 - 2 + 94","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"21 * 6 * (62 + 7)","answer":"8694"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 2) * 3 - (98 * 3 - 4)","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"22 + 1 * 6 + 10","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 2 + 1) * 19","answer":"3819"}
{"prompt":"42 - (41 + 7)","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 4) * 9 * 26","answer":"11232"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 4) * 99","answer":"4455"}
{"prompt":"50 - 91","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 1 - 5) * 16 * 10 - 3","answer":"11037"}
{"prompt":"81 * 24","answer":"1944"}
{"prompt":"86 - (75 - 10) - 2","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"51 + 19","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 5) * 40","answer":"1600"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 1 - 1) * 89","answer":"8188"}
{"prompt":"33 - 27","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"32 - (98 - 6)","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"19 * 26","answer":"494"}
{"prompt":"94 * (87 + 6)","answer":"8742"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 7) + 84","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 4 - 2) - 50","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(62 + 9 + 4) - 76 - 10","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"34 - ((61 - 5) + 5)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 6) - 10","answer":"548"}
{"prompt":"35 * 33","answer":"1155"}
{"prompt":"27 + 2 * 4 - 74","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"61 * 6 - 56","answer":"310"}
{"prompt":"((89 + 10) - 8) + 21","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"((100 - 2) + 5) - 3 * 3","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 6) * 81","answer":"37908"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 7) + 41","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(34 - 6) - 65","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"3 - 49 * 10","answer":"-487"}
{"prompt":"23 + (7 + 8 * 2)","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"48 - 4 * 3 * (67 * 2) * 3","answer":"-4776"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 5) + 30","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"77 + 5 * 9 * 87","answer":"3992"}
{"prompt":"((47 - 7) * 3) - ((76 * 6) * 6)","answer":"-2616"}
{"prompt":"((43 * 5) - 10) + 15","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"22 - 36","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"72 * 73","answer":"5256"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 1) * 99","answer":"792"}
{"prompt":"34 - 7","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"36 - (65 - 4) - 10","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"23 + 2 - 2 + 38","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"((76 + 8) + 10) * 72 - 6","answer":"6762"}
{"prompt":"41 - (80 + 9) + 3","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"88 * (1 - 1)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"28 - 66","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 7 - 5) + 67 + 2 - 5","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 8) - 8","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"26 - 72","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"22 * ((11 * 1) + 3)","answer":"308"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 1) + 2 + 94","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 5 * 3) - 41","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"49 + 73 + 7 + 7","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"85 - (91 + 4) * 2","answer":"-105"}
{"prompt":"13 + 40","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"66 + 6","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"33 - 2 - 10 + 89 * 2 + 1","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 9) - 1 * ((17 * 5) + 10)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"9 - 57 + 4","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"33 + ((3 - 2) - 5)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"((3 + 2) * 10) - 89 + 3","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 7) - 33 + 4","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"95 + 61","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"18 * 70","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"45 * 6 - 95","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"13 + 6","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"26 - 85","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"25 + 10 - 12","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 4) * 61","answer":"3721"}
{"prompt":"32 * 68","answer":"2176"}
{"prompt":"37 + 46","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"((44 + 5) - 3) + 98","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"70 - 5 * 2 - 7","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"90 * (74 + 10 * 8)","answer":"13860"}
{"prompt":"55 - 73 * 6","answer":"-383"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 9) + 8 * (96 * 3 - 8)","answer":"2645"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 8) - 9 - 86 * 6","answer":"-466"}
{"prompt":"33 * 87","answer":"2871"}
{"prompt":"99 + 10 * 9 - 4","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"83 * 10 * 8 * 50 * 6","answer":"1992000"}
{"prompt":"20 - 4 - 65","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"21 - 7 + ((31 * 4) * 3)","answer":"386"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 8) - 6 * (14 * 10 + 10)","answer":"-188"}
{"prompt":"62 * 3","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"64 - 5 + 6 - 84","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"51 - 55 * 4 + 6","answer":"-163"}
{"prompt":"68 * 93","answer":"6324"}
{"prompt":"15 - 11","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"37 * 87 * 3 + 10","answer":"9667"}
{"prompt":"24 + 5 - 3 * 88","answer":"-235"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 2) + 6 - 84","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 8) + (54 * 1) * 1","answer":"526"}
{"prompt":"56 * 6 - 7 + 68 * 9","answer":"941"}
{"prompt":"(86 * 8 * 3) * (18 + 5 + 9)","answer":"66048"}
{"prompt":"76 + (86 + 7) + 7","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"18 * 4","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"((19 + 2) + 7) - 40 * 5","answer":"-172"}
{"prompt":"99 + 42","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"1 * 13 + 8","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 2) + (83 - 6)","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"17 - 35","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"4 - ((69 + 2) + 4)","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 6) * 83","answer":"8715"}
{"prompt":"50 * 8 + 30","answer":"430"}
{"prompt":"89 + 8","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"56 + 54","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 7) * 9 - 85","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 9) * 5 * ((24 + 5) - 7)","answer":"6710"}
{"prompt":"63 * 20 - 3","answer":"1257"}
{"prompt":"22 * 50","answer":"1100"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 1 - 6) - (72 - 7)","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"85 - 68","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"((55 + 5) * 1) + (47 * 2) - 10","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"7 - (1 - 2)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"73 + 9 * 8 + (24 + 10 * 5)","answer":"219"}
{"prompt":"(57 - 1) + (80 - 8 * 1)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"(3 + 9) - 9 * 12","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 10) - 1 - 64","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"5 - 4 * 8 * (22 * 3) * 9","answer":"-19003"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 8) + 43","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"16 + (11 + 8)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"45 + 49","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"42 - 3 - 96 - 6","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"7 + 39 - 5 + 8","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"84 - 1 * 10 + 34","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"99 * 5 + 75 + 7","answer":"577"}
{"prompt":"90 * 4 - 79","answer":"281"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 3) * 72","answer":"21600"}
{"prompt":"71 + (51 + 1) - 3","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"31 - 4 - 48","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 4) * 10 - 40","answer":"2920"}
{"prompt":"77 - 93","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"65 - 5 - (63 + 2)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"17 * 32","answer":"544"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 3 * 3) * 30 * 6","answer":"32400"}
{"prompt":"33 * 9 - 10 + 35","answer":"322"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 4) * (77 + 9 * 3)","answer":"31200"}
{"prompt":"95 - 59","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"5 * 78","answer":"390"}
{"prompt":"(16 - 9) * 9 - 70 * 1","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 4) * 10 + 61","answer":"731"}
{"prompt":"(88 + 8) + 1","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"72 - 27 - 9 + 8","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"55 - (40 * 5 - 1)","answer":"-144"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 2 * 3) + 84","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"61 * 19 + 5 + 10","answer":"1174"}
{"prompt":"5 * 3 * 4 - 3","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"81 * 2 - 92 - 2","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"87 + 38","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 9) + 52","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"1 * (81 * 7 + 9)","answer":"576"}
{"prompt":"80 * 4 + 2","answer":"322"}
{"prompt":"79 - 10 * 7 + 71","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"54 + 5 - (82 * 4 + 4)","answer":"-273"}
{"prompt":"(15 - 6 - 7) + (73 * 7)","answer":"513"}
{"prompt":"65 * (67 * 7 - 6)","answer":"30095"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 3) * 4 + 33","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(58 - 7) * 6 + 62","answer":"368"}
{"prompt":"19 * 6 - 3 - 15","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"((52 * 6) * 8) - (20 - 1)","answer":"2477"}
{"prompt":"96 + (32 * 7)","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"72 + (36 - 7) + 3","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 5) * 10 * 79","answer":"98750"}
{"prompt":"23 + 47","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 10) * 8 - 67","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"((96 - 4) + 4) * 29","answer":"2784"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 4) * 60 * 3 - 5","answer":"51115"}
{"prompt":"14 * 9 * (83 - 1)","answer":"10332"}
{"prompt":"67 + (11 - 5 * 8)","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(76 - 8) * ((3 + 10) + 8)","answer":"1428"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 4) - 25","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"9 - 89","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 2) - 26","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"71 - 8 - 59","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 8) + 48","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"52 * 97","answer":"5044"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 8) - 85","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 5) * 3 * 63","answer":"9450"}
{"prompt":"26 - 12","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"62 * 88","answer":"5456"}
{"prompt":"((68 - 2) - 5) * 68","answer":"4148"}
{"prompt":"50 * 80 - 6","answer":"3994"}
{"prompt":"100 + 6","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 8) * 47","answer":"4559"}
{"prompt":"96 + 83","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"56 - 5","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"43 + 10 - 55 - 4","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"94 * 1 + 6 - 5","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"87 - 38","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"88 - 10 - 56","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"97 * 5 - 79 + 2","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"48 - 6 + (57 + 8)","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"41 - (22 * 10 * 8)","answer":"-1719"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 2) + 73","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"60 * (100 + 6)","answer":"6360"}
{"prompt":"3 - 47","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 4) * 4","answer":"1344"}
{"prompt":"99 - 3 * (36 - 9)","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"24 - 10 * 5 * 26","answer":"-1276"}
{"prompt":"88 * (71 * 2)","answer":"12496"}
{"prompt":"83 - ((74 * 6) - 3)","answer":"-358"}
{"prompt":"47 - (17 + 6)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"28 - ((58 - 4) * 2)","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"38 + (99 * 1) + 2","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"30 * 88","answer":"2640"}
{"prompt":"89 + 83","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"62 + 1 * 5 + (7 - 4 - 6)","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"33 + 8 * 1 * 61","answer":"521"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 1 * 9) - 76 + 3","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"44 - 4 - 7 - (20 * 6 * 1)","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 1) - 86 + 3","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"20 * 100","answer":"2000"}
{"prompt":"67 + 10","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 5) + 5 * 39","answer":"224"}
{"prompt":"73 - 1 + 18 + 6","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"38 - 5 - ((26 * 2) - 6)","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 9 - 6) - 79 - 5 * 6","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"86 - 38","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"95 - 10 + (36 * 5)","answer":"265"}
{"prompt":"(79 - 3) * 78","answer":"5928"}
{"prompt":"47 + 9 * 3 - (46 - 7)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 1) * 3 * 45","answer":"9585"}
{"prompt":"((55 - 2) + 4) - 80 - 8 - 6","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"51 - 1 + ((65 + 3) + 9)","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"37 - 58","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 6 - 6) - 25","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"60 - 1 + 44 + 2","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 8) + 25 - 2 - 5","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"31 + 71 * 7","answer":"528"}
{"prompt":"((64 * 9) - 8) - 61 - 8","answer":"499"}
{"prompt":"3 + 11","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 4) * 29","answer":"3828"}
{"prompt":"48 - 85","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"70 * 9","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"19 - (93 * 10)","answer":"-911"}
{"prompt":"27 - 1 + 4","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 5 * 7) - 47 + 3 - 3","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 5) - 8 - 57","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"2 - 3 + 3 - 93","answer":"-91"}
{"prompt":"84 * (63 + 6 + 8)","answer":"6468"}
{"prompt":"61 + 5 * 76","answer":"441"}
{"prompt":"36 - 59","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 10 * 6) + 55","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 4) + 2 + (73 + 7) - 5","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"12 + (83 - 3)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"52 * 72","answer":"3744"}
{"prompt":"69 - (74 - 9 * 9)","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 9) * 59","answer":"2596"}
{"prompt":"7 + 65","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 6 - 8) + 57","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 1) * 54","answer":"1944"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 1) + 4 + 52","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 2 + 7) - 96","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"62 + 4","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"35 - (4 - 7) * 4","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"63 - (50 + 2)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"20 * 88 - 6","answer":"1754"}
{"prompt":"((44 * 1) * 4) * 66","answer":"11616"}
{"prompt":"51 * 8 * 89","answer":"36312"}
{"prompt":"94 * 7 + 9 - (31 * 6) - 2","answer":"479"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 9) + 6","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"72 - 45","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 4) - 68","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"63 + (2 - 5)","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"49 * 10 - (74 + 2) - 4","answer":"410"}
{"prompt":"79 + 5 - (69 * 4) + 1","answer":"-191"}
{"prompt":"24 + 81 - 6","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"32 - 25","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"2 + 4 * 1 + 7","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 1) - 7 - 32","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"92 - ((53 - 9) - 3)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"12 + 2 - 3","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"23 + (66 * 1 + 5)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"65 + 8 * 10 - 1","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"89 - 10 * (78 * 1 + 2)","answer":"-711"}
{"prompt":"82 * 68","answer":"5576"}
{"prompt":"((78 * 4) - 5) + 39","answer":"346"}
{"prompt":"1 - 8 * 16","answer":"-127"}
{"prompt":"18 + 2 - 81","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"((33 * 9) - 5) - ((72 + 5) * 5)","answer":"-93"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 5) - 40","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"53 * ((91 - 6) * 6)","answer":"27030"}
{"prompt":"58 * 69 - 5","answer":"3997"}
{"prompt":"100 + (100 + 8)","answer":"208"}
{"prompt":"84 + 34","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 6 - 9) - 24 + 6 * 1","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 8) - ((12 - 10) + 7)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"23 * 6 * (30 + 5 * 6)","answer":"8280"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 6) + 8 + ((61 + 10) * 8)","answer":"1080"}
{"prompt":"32 - 2 + 32","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"51 + 78","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"89 - 10 + (76 - 2 + 7)","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"47 + 20 * 7","answer":"187"}
{"prompt":"(88 + 10) - 17","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 8) + 5 + 59 * 8","answer":"757"}
{"prompt":"89 * 1 - 5 + 99","answer":"183"}
{"prompt":"49 * 96","answer":"4704"}
{"prompt":"82 + (25 * 1) + 4","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"59 - 10 - (44 + 1)","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 8) + (30 * 8)","answer":"448"}
{"prompt":"97 * 1","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"49 + 2 * 7 + 7","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"74 + 28","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"72 - (34 - 2 * 10)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"48 - 58","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"29 + 40","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"((83 - 5) + 6) + 50","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"((100 * 8) * 8) + 48","answer":"6448"}
{"prompt":"((76 - 8) + 5) * 95 + 1 + 4","answer":"6940"}
{"prompt":"16 + 51 - 3","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"((8 * 2) + 1) + ((87 + 1) - 5)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"28 + 8 * 6 * 22","answer":"1084"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1 * 3) - 19","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 2 * 5) - 75","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 5) * 8 + 7 - 6 + 1","answer":"562"}
{"prompt":"(34 - 8 * 2) + 27","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"86 - 70","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"30 - ((29 * 9) * 3)","answer":"-753"}
{"prompt":"19 + 88","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"100 * 9","answer":"900"}
{"prompt":"4 - 3 - 98 - 6 + 8","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"75 - 9 * (45 - 7)","answer":"-267"}
{"prompt":"(61 + 7) - (47 + 2 * 10)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"39 + 45","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"17 * 37","answer":"629"}
{"prompt":"((44 + 5) * 8) + (61 - 9) + 9","answer":"453"}
{"prompt":"90 - 33","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"95 - 6 * 52","answer":"-217"}
{"prompt":"89 + 1 + ((46 * 6) + 8)","answer":"374"}
{"prompt":"48 - 8 * 41","answer":"-280"}
{"prompt":"92 + 34 - 9 - 5","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"((44 * 4) + 7) - 7","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"56 + 6 + (99 + 10) - 10","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 2) + 7 - 95 - 1","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 8) * ((75 * 5) - 4)","answer":"264152"}
{"prompt":"83 - (45 + 10) - 2","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 1) + 13","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"28 + 2 * 10 * 6","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"40 - 5 * (88 - 7)","answer":"-365"}
{"prompt":"40 - 2 * 5 + 80","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"55 * 85","answer":"4675"}
{"prompt":"100 + 54","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"21 + ((88 - 7) * 10)","answer":"831"}
{"prompt":"83 - 78","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"62 + 7 - 4 + 70","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"25 + 8 - 8","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 1) - (79 + 2 + 10)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 7 * 10) + 95","answer":"6535"}
{"prompt":"88 - 35","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 10) + 8 * 18","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"43 - (12 + 5)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 9) + 9 - 15","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"4 * 3 - 4 * 61","answer":"-232"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 8) - 66","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 10) * (49 + 4)","answer":"530"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 1) - 9 * (11 * 3)","answer":"-223"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 3) * 16","answer":"2160"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 2) - 64","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"51 - 6 - 9 + 5","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"47 - 8 - 6 * (35 + 7)","answer":"-213"}
{"prompt":"8 * 1 + 5 + (82 * 2) * 5","answer":"833"}
{"prompt":"6 * 87","answer":"522"}
{"prompt":"40 - 65 + 1","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"(3 + 4) - 3 + 39 * 7 * 7","answer":"1915"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 5) - 100","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"44 + 80","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 4) + 2 * 2","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 9) - 71","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"46 * (70 + 3) * 3","answer":"10074"}
{"prompt":"8 - (96 - 6) * 2","answer":"-172"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 4 - 4) + 47 - 5","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"36 * ((33 * 8) * 8)","answer":"76032"}
{"prompt":"4 - 78","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"17 - 76","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"33 - ((81 * 7) + 7)","answer":"-541"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 9 * 10) + 87 - 2 + 6","answer":"233"}
{"prompt":"57 * 67","answer":"3819"}
{"prompt":"81 + 33 * 1","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"88 - 2 * 2 - 4 * 5","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 3) * 4 * 26","answer":"3536"}
{"prompt":"81 * 2 + ((54 - 1) + 4)","answer":"219"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 4) + 67","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"94 - 4 * 16 * 3 + 5","answer":"-93"}
{"prompt":"66 * 10 * 6 * ((69 + 6) + 8)","answer":"328680"}
{"prompt":"47 + 5 - 80","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"44 - 26","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"69 * 4 * 3 + 19","answer":"847"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 2) - 4 + 69","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"65 * 83","answer":"5395"}
{"prompt":"91 - 69","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"30 * 5 - 19","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"((91 * 1) - 7) + (33 + 1) - 7","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"(22 - 2) * 7 + (87 + 9)","answer":"236"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 7) - ((51 - 1) + 7)","answer":"482"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 8 - 7) - 18","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"90 * 15","answer":"1350"}
{"prompt":"81 + 8","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"95 + (90 - 2) * 9","answer":"887"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 3) * 4 * 53","answer":"8904"}
{"prompt":"11 + 40","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"67 * 99 * 6 + 8","answer":"39806"}
{"prompt":"((24 - 2) * 1) * ((1 - 4) + 10)","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"((49 - 7) + 4) + 74","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"((3 - 7) * 2) + (21 - 7) - 2","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 2) * 44","answer":"3432"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 6) - 7 + 22","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"95 - (19 * 10)","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"18 * 16","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"60 - 28","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"16 + ((15 * 1) * 10)","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"80 + 8 + 3 * 96 + 2","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"((53 - 2) * 1) - 78 - 3","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"44 * (69 - 2 - 5)","answer":"2728"}
{"prompt":"41 + 91","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"71 - (99 + 1 - 4)","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 10) - 68","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"23 - (50 + 7)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"57 * ((30 * 9) - 5)","answer":"15105"}
{"prompt":"74 - 3 + 35","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"((64 * 1) - 4) * 85","answer":"5100"}
{"prompt":"69 * 83","answer":"5727"}
{"prompt":"53 + 72","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"73 + 66","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"31 + 7 - 5 - 69","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"7 * 3 + (18 - 5)","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"55 + 78","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"(40 - 7) * 2 - (29 + 10)","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(33 - 1) - 2 + 49","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"76 * ((31 - 4) + 4)","answer":"2356"}
{"prompt":"68 + 78","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 7) - 59 - 1","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"52 + 36","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"56 + 6 - (22 * 10 * 9)","answer":"-1918"}
{"prompt":"74 + 73 * 5 - 1","answer":"438"}
{"prompt":"54 + 59 * 9","answer":"585"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 1 * 5) + (50 - 5) - 6","answer":"474"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 10) * 3 * 70","answer":"-840"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 10) * 6 + 58 * 3 * 3","answer":"756"}
{"prompt":"55 * 51 * 6","answer":"16830"}
{"prompt":"67 * 1 - 7 * (50 * 2 - 8)","answer":"-577"}
{"prompt":"59 + 61","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 4) - 19","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"94 * 4 - ((89 - 4) - 1)","answer":"292"}
{"prompt":"16 + 4 + 70","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"40 + 10 - (14 * 6)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"100 - 8 - 2 - ((2 - 3) - 10)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"19 * 15 * 10","answer":"2850"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 6 - 3) + 75","answer":"546"}
{"prompt":"34 + 5 - 60","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"51 - 7 + 8 - (82 * 10) + 10","answer":"-758"}
{"prompt":"((49 + 8) * 6) * 2 * 3 + 6","answer":"2058"}
{"prompt":"((17 - 5) + 2) - (47 * 3)","answer":"-127"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 3) - 4 - ((40 * 3) - 4)","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"64 * 50 - 8 + 4","answer":"3196"}
{"prompt":"38 * 85","answer":"3230"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 6) - (24 * 8 - 2)","answer":"-153"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 2) + 49","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"((35 * 5) + 6) * 63 - 1","answer":"11402"}
{"prompt":"71 + 59","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"40 * (65 + 8)","answer":"2920"}
{"prompt":"45 * 96","answer":"4320"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 8) + 58","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"94 - 45 + 5","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"9 * (17 - 1) - 9","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"99 * 8 * (86 - 1)","answer":"67320"}
{"prompt":"60 * 2 - 45","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"27 + 92","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"62 + 6 * (1 * 10)","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"64 + 5 + 60","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"90 * 33 + 3","answer":"2973"}
{"prompt":"29 - 53","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"45 - 27","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"22 * 2 - 67","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 6) - 8 + 1","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"59 + 13","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"75 + 44","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"36 * 67","answer":"2412"}
{"prompt":"48 * 3 + 90","answer":"234"}
{"prompt":"(65 * 10) * 9 + 64","answer":"5914"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 8 * 6) - 1","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"85 + (83 + 7)","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"99 + (61 - 1)","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"74 * 24","answer":"1776"}
{"prompt":"55 * ((72 + 5) + 2)","answer":"4345"}
{"prompt":"5 + 88","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"44 + 41","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 2 - 8) + 12 - 2","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"40 * 46","answer":"1840"}
{"prompt":"96 * 61 - 6","answer":"5850"}
{"prompt":"86 + 47","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"8 * 4 * (33 * 3 + 1)","answer":"3200"}
{"prompt":"25 - (46 + 4 - 9)","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"79 * 52","answer":"4108"}
{"prompt":"71 - (81 + 9) * 6","answer":"-469"}
{"prompt":"62 + 20 - 5","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"22 + (29 + 5)","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"((9 - 1) - 10) + 92","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"59 * 46","answer":"2714"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 9) * (28 - 1)","answer":"972"}
{"prompt":"35 + 4","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 7) - 81","answer":"605"}
{"prompt":"43 + 1 + 54 * 5 + 10","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"23 * 90","answer":"2070"}
{"prompt":"22 - 7 - 6 * 20","answer":"-105"}
{"prompt":"81 + 64 * 2","answer":"209"}
{"prompt":"20 * 100","answer":"2000"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 1) * 9 - ((88 + 8) * 7)","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"85 + 88","answer":"173"}
{"prompt":"82 + 36 * 6","answer":"298"}
{"prompt":"53 - (99 + 10)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 10) * 11 - 10 + 1","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"61 + 88 + 2","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 10) + (36 - 2) * 5","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"100 - 92","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"99 * 77","answer":"7623"}
{"prompt":"28 + ((7 - 4) + 6)","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"((86 * 4) + 7) - (58 + 9)","answer":"284"}
{"prompt":"55 - 3 + 92 * 3","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"9 - 75","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"92 + (100 - 1) * 4","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 7 * 3) - (23 + 6)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"96 + 49","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 8 + 7) * (87 * 5 * 8)","answer":"233160"}
{"prompt":"25 - 8 * 44","answer":"-327"}
{"prompt":"34 + 84","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"15 - 6 - (16 - 1) + 9","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"9 - 94","answer":"-85"}
{"prompt":"87 * 28","answer":"2436"}
{"prompt":"7 * 27 * 9 + 10","answer":"1711"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 5) - (94 - 3)","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"64 + 1","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"23 - 9 + 4","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"50 - 27","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"87 - 7 - 66","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 6 - 3) * 71","answer":"-213"}
{"prompt":"37 + (55 * 9) * 5","answer":"2512"}
{"prompt":"54 - 56","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"55 - 14","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 2) + 12","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"92 + 90","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 7) - 6 - 94","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"86 - 83","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"54 * 8","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 8) + ((69 * 2) + 3)","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"68 + 8 - 10 - 96","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"88 - 89 - 3","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"77 + 26","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"(99 - 7) - 19","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 2) * 54 * 7","answer":"23814"}
{"prompt":"96 - 7 - 94","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(32 + 8) * 77","answer":"3080"}
{"prompt":"47 * (59 + 10 + 1)","answer":"3290"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 9) * 83 + 9","answer":"44082"}
{"prompt":"(54 - 2) + 6 * 32 + 3","answer":"247"}
{"prompt":"58 - 48 - 9","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 3) - 52","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"92 + 94 - 1","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"(62 - 10 - 10) + 50","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"44 - ((6 * 8) + 9)","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 2) * 1 + ((20 - 6) * 1)","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"10 - 1 - ((97 - 10) * 1)","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"81 * 38","answer":"3078"}
{"prompt":"76 - (20 * 7 * 10)","answer":"-1324"}
{"prompt":"16 + 26 - 7","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"89 * 48 - 1","answer":"4271"}
{"prompt":"4 + 6 * (17 - 6) + 1","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"81 + (73 * 2) * 3","answer":"519"}
{"prompt":"81 + 65 - 7","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"66 + 39 - 2","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 7 + 3) - 4","answer":"643"}
{"prompt":"80 + 70","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"95 - ((36 * 6) - 6)","answer":"-115"}
{"prompt":"30 - 28 * 2 + 9","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"69 * 73 - 3 + 6","answer":"5040"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 6) + (77 * 6)","answer":"546"}
{"prompt":"51 - (61 * 5) - 8","answer":"-262"}
{"prompt":"((73 - 1) + 3) * 70","answer":"5250"}
{"prompt":"31 + 6 * (48 + 9)","answer":"373"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 3) + 90 * 8 * 3","answer":"2207"}
{"prompt":"48 + 1 * ((57 - 7) - 6)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"17 * 10","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"6 * 48","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 9) - 41","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"82 * (70 * 6)","answer":"34440"}
{"prompt":"22 + 9 - 9 - (54 * 2 + 6)","answer":"-92"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 1) - 14","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"90 - 56","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"33 - 70","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 2) - (84 - 8 + 10)","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"74 - 37","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"58 * (92 + 5)","answer":"5626"}
{"prompt":"1 - 63","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"64 + (47 + 5)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 7 + 8) + 39","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"18 + 8 + (7 - 7)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"((25 * 7) * 6) - (26 - 9) * 2","answer":"1016"}
{"prompt":"20 - 29","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"(45 - 8 + 8) - (33 - 5 - 3)","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"45 * 10 - (24 - 7 * 10)","answer":"496"}
{"prompt":"66 * 7 * 1 - (27 - 1 * 1)","answer":"436"}
{"prompt":"19 + ((18 * 10) + 8)","answer":"207"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 4) + 9 * (60 + 4) - 4","answer":"574"}
{"prompt":"86 + (26 * 6) - 2","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"92 * (11 - 2 * 9)","answer":"-644"}
{"prompt":"(62 * 3) + (66 * 6 + 4)","answer":"586"}
{"prompt":"63 * 89","answer":"5607"}
{"prompt":"21 * 47 - 10 * 8","answer":"907"}
{"prompt":"46 + 64 - 2 * 3","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"37 - (91 + 4)","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"46 - ((68 - 1) * 1)","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"45 + 4 * 42 - 1 + 8","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"49 + 36 + 4","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"26 * 74 * 7","answer":"13468"}
{"prompt":"((7 * 3) + 4) - 47","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"56 + 79","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"52 + 2 + 5 + (72 + 7)","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"74 - 95","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"17 * (55 + 4)","answer":"1003"}
{"prompt":"47 * (20 + 7)","answer":"1269"}
{"prompt":"72 - 42","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"44 + 10","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"80 * 47 * 8","answer":"30080"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 10) * 77","answer":"-693"}
{"prompt":"51 + 41","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"88 - 31 + 7","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"11 * ((40 - 1) * 1)","answer":"429"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 8) - 25","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"20 * 4 - 79","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"78 - 24","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 5) * 5 * 11","answer":"5665"}
{"prompt":"57 + ((30 - 1) - 1)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 8 * 3) + 42","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"74 - 90 * 4 - 8","answer":"-294"}
{"prompt":"47 * ((31 * 1) + 9)","answer":"1880"}
{"prompt":"97 - 17","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"((38 + 8) - 8) * 42","answer":"1596"}
{"prompt":"80 * 3 + 31","answer":"271"}
{"prompt":"64 * 6 * 7 - 78 * 4","answer":"2376"}
{"prompt":"((42 + 8) - 6) + ((63 - 1) + 8)","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"65 - 8 - (29 + 5)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"25 - 31 * 9","answer":"-254"}
{"prompt":"31 * (65 * 10)","answer":"20150"}
{"prompt":"8 * 36","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"21 - 38","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 8) + (49 + 3)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"52 * 86 + 8 * 6","answer":"4520"}
{"prompt":"13 + (15 + 8 * 7)","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"((49 * 9) - 2) - (49 * 6 + 1)","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"31 - 3 * 74","answer":"-191"}
{"prompt":"((43 + 1) - 1) * 10","answer":"430"}
{"prompt":"28 * 21","answer":"588"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 4 + 7) * 78","answer":"7488"}
{"prompt":"48 * (3 + 3)","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"((79 - 8) + 5) + 12","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"50 + (59 - 9 + 7)","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"44 - 9 + 16","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((69 * 8) - 7) + 70","answer":"615"}
{"prompt":"51 * 3 + ((8 * 7) - 8)","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 2 - 10) - (23 * 8)","answer":"-167"}
{"prompt":"32 * (45 - 7)","answer":"1216"}
{"prompt":"83 * ((22 * 2) * 5)","answer":"18260"}
{"prompt":"88 + (26 - 3 - 1)","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 4) + 3 - 59","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"57 + 35","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"75 + 67","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"24 + 63","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 9 + 3) - 91 + 10 * 6","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 10) + 8 * (68 * 7)","answer":"3868"}
{"prompt":"4 * 28","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"12 + 51 - 2","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"79 - 10 + 10 * (96 * 5) + 6","answer":"4875"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 8) * 94","answer":"846"}
{"prompt":"59 + 32","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 10) - (29 + 4)","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"55 + 14","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 10) * (83 - 3 - 6)","answer":"53280"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 5) * 38","answer":"2698"}
{"prompt":"77 - 92 + 5","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 3) + 52","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"26 * (88 * 3)","answer":"6864"}
{"prompt":"31 * 21","answer":"651"}
{"prompt":"94 * 7 - 3 * (31 - 5) * 9","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"47 - 62","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"24 + ((73 - 4) + 2)","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 8 * 9) + 18","answer":"6426"}
{"prompt":"15 + 3 * 9 * 66","answer":"1797"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 3) - 5 - 80","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 1) - 87 - 7 * 9","answer":"-79"}
{"prompt":"((69 - 9) - 5) - (30 - 3)","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"61 * (10 - 8) + 5","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"23 + 1 - 3 + 10","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"19 - (88 * 6) - 6","answer":"-515"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 10) + ((45 * 2) - 3)","answer":"257"}
{"prompt":"79 * 6 * 62","answer":"29388"}
{"prompt":"95 + 20","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"20 * 91","answer":"1820"}
{"prompt":"89 + 2","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"3 + 6 - 38 + 10","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"97 * 11","answer":"1067"}
{"prompt":"(25 - 5) - 61","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"98 * (25 + 9)","answer":"3332"}
{"prompt":"35 - 79","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"59 - 48","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"55 * 26","answer":"1430"}
{"prompt":"45 - 1 * 96","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"2 - 10 - 42","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"61 * 3 - (61 * 4 * 2)","answer":"-305"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 7) - 1 - (84 + 7)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 5) * 80","answer":"6800"}
{"prompt":"98 + 88","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"(97 * 1) * 1 * 97","answer":"9409"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 2) * 2 + 99 * 8 - 9","answer":"897"}
{"prompt":"71 + 37","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"34 + 19","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"23 + 19 * 9 - 8","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"37 + (20 + 7) * 2","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"45 + 53 * 3","answer":"204"}
{"prompt":"71 - (40 + 4)","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"58 - 95","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"83 - 94","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"58 + 6 - (1 + 7)","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"96 + 17","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"77 + 17","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"2 + 47","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"20 - ((56 * 9) + 10)","answer":"-494"}
{"prompt":"45 * (36 + 7)","answer":"1935"}
{"prompt":"70 + 3 * 50 * 7 + 5","answer":"1125"}
{"prompt":"85 - 7","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"((40 + 6) - 10) - 64","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"74 + 6 - 14 * 3","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"41 + (1 - 10 - 10)","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 7 - 5) + 41","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"7 + ((99 - 2) * 8)","answer":"783"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 5) + 4 + 56 - 8","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 9) + 7 * ((66 * 6) + 2)","answer":"2845"}
{"prompt":"46 * 55","answer":"2530"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 7) + (34 + 2) * 3","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"13 * 3 + 44 * 1 - 8","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(58 * 7) + 42 * 6 + 9","answer":"667"}
{"prompt":"24 - 1 - 40","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 7) * ((36 - 6) - 5)","answer":"2050"}
{"prompt":"5 + 99","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"11 * ((19 - 8) + 8)","answer":"209"}
{"prompt":"56 + 69 + 1","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"23 + 92","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"14 - 78","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"83 * 56","answer":"4648"}
{"prompt":"6 - 10 + 10 - 19","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 10) - (31 - 3 + 3)","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"98 + 83","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"27 - 90","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"(77 - 1) - 43","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"63 + 4 * 2 * (66 * 9)","answer":"4815"}
{"prompt":"39 * 28","answer":"1092"}
{"prompt":"86 + 3 - ((98 + 3) - 4)","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"34 - 6 + 27","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"83 * 18","answer":"1494"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 1) + 4) + 9","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"71 + 8 * 10 - 94","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"81 - (3 + 2 * 8)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"44 + (12 + 9)","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"9 * 4 - 96","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"(35 + 7) * 37 * 7","answer":"10878"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 8 + 1) - 8 - 2","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 3) - (28 - 6)","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"50 + 81","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"21 - (16 * 5) + 1","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"30 + (63 - 1 - 4)","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(19 - 8) + 3 - (10 + 2)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"37 + 7 + (31 - 4) - 4","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 9) + 1 - (35 - 3)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 1 + 7) * 12","answer":"1104"}
{"prompt":"98 + ((17 + 3) - 10)","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"59 + 18","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"7 * (9 * 1 + 6)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"((57 + 7) + 3) * (64 - 10)","answer":"3618"}
{"prompt":"44 * 100","answer":"4400"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 5) + 73","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 5 * 5) * 28","answer":"38500"}
{"prompt":"29 + 94 + 6","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"2 - (98 - 8)","answer":"-88"}
{"prompt":"6 + 100","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 6) + 5","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"86 * (79 - 6)","answer":"6278"}
{"prompt":"16 - (11 * 8)","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"14 - 6 * (8 + 8 - 4)","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"98 * 38","answer":"3724"}
{"prompt":"38 + 74","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 8) - (36 + 1)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"91 * 9 - 5 - 38 * 2","answer":"738"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 7) + (55 - 1)","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"((40 * 5) - 4) - (26 + 1)","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"74 * 99","answer":"7326"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 4 - 9) * 80 * 9","answer":"177840"}
{"prompt":"64 - (56 + 9)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"19 * 16","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"(34 - 3) + 5 + (97 + 6 * 6)","answer":"169"}
{"prompt":"99 - 52","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"24 + 4 + 26","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"((75 - 2) + 6) + 5","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"98 + 5 + (26 - 9 + 8)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"81 + 5 + 28 + 7 + 9","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 8) * 4 + (60 * 10)","answer":"1144"}
{"prompt":"73 * 63","answer":"4599"}
{"prompt":"15 * 52","answer":"780"}
{"prompt":"18 - 70","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"47 - 58","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"60 * 40 * 10","answer":"24000"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 1) + 58","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"((79 * 10) * 5) - (71 - 10) * 1","answer":"3889"}
{"prompt":"19 + 81 - 7 * 10","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"29 - 10 + (45 + 7 * 9)","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"62 + 39","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"54 - 18","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"31 * 8 * 7","answer":"1736"}
{"prompt":"70 - (24 + 8 * 5)","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"9 + 87","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 6) - 8) * ((11 + 3) * 4)","answer":"2576"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 8 * 9) * 45 * 10","answer":"-7200"}
{"prompt":"94 + 8 * 6 * 52","answer":"2590"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 10) + 48 - 8","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 1) - 5 * 89","answer":"-376"}
{"prompt":"48 - 1","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"95 - 4 * 6","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 10 * 7) * (91 - 8 + 5)","answer":"-1320"}
{"prompt":"15 - 6 - ((67 * 8) - 5)","answer":"-522"}
{"prompt":"35 * ((58 + 10) * 5)","answer":"11900"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 9) + 97 + 2 + 10","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"100 + (63 + 8)","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"42 * (1 - 10)","answer":"-378"}
{"prompt":"((33 - 7) - 4) * 32","answer":"704"}
{"prompt":"75 * 11","answer":"825"}
{"prompt":"60 + 6 - 7","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"10 + 3 * 5 + 45 * 9","answer":"430"}
{"prompt":"15 + 56","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"53 - 6 + 1 + (40 * 3 - 6)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 2) + 60","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"73 - 61","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"48 + ((17 + 10) - 8)","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"39 + 5 + (37 + 6)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"100 - 96 - 2 + 5","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"74 - 53","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"54 + 8 * 41","answer":"382"}
{"prompt":"31 + 17","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"26 * 57","answer":"1482"}
{"prompt":"30 - 91","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"64 + 40","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"18 + 38","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"49 + 58","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"88 - 10 - 6 - 97 * 3","answer":"-219"}
{"prompt":"16 * 1 - 4 * 58","answer":"-216"}
{"prompt":"87 * (21 * 5)","answer":"9135"}
{"prompt":"19 - 22","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"27 - 98 - 4 - 8","answer":"-83"}
{"prompt":"42 - 27","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"7 + (33 - 9) - 3","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 9) - 41","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"33 + 46 - 4","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"89 * 4 - 67","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"92 - 3 + (45 - 8)","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"26 + (61 + 7 - 2)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(17 - 10) + ((100 - 8) + 8)","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(56 + 9) * 7 + (4 - 10)","answer":"449"}
{"prompt":"69 - 85","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"15 + 1","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"27 * (26 + 1)","answer":"729"}
{"prompt":"62 * 8 + 27","answer":"523"}
{"prompt":"89 + 35","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"42 + 7 * 2","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"72 + 30","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"42 * 66","answer":"2772"}
{"prompt":"(40 + 7 + 3) * (98 - 6) + 5","answer":"4605"}
{"prompt":"13 * 4 - 78","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"93 * 8 + 5 - (63 + 3)","answer":"683"}
{"prompt":"(88 + 6) * (34 + 7) - 1","answer":"3853"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 4) * 9 * (97 * 1)","answer":"23571"}
{"prompt":"34 + 99","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"67 + 9 * 62 * 3","answer":"1741"}
{"prompt":"22 - 91","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 2) * 1 + 78 + 1","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"((66 + 9) * 9) - ((33 + 9) + 8)","answer":"625"}
{"prompt":"47 * 2","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"83 - 78","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"91 * 4","answer":"364"}
{"prompt":"38 - 75 * 3 + 5","answer":"-182"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 9) + 24","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"24 * 5","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 9) - 6) - 37","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 10 + 5) - 47","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"16 + (3 * 8)","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"82 + 39 + 8","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"21 + 4","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 1) * 7","answer":"364"}
{"prompt":"96 - 3 * 8 + 53","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"87 * 79","answer":"6873"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 9) + 22","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"79 + (20 - 2) * 9","answer":"241"}
{"prompt":"12 + 28 + 9","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 9) - 31 * 1","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"70 - 5 * 92","answer":"-390"}
{"prompt":"11 + 30","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"72 + (32 + 8)","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"94 * (97 + 2)","answer":"9306"}
{"prompt":"90 - (46 + 1 - 10)","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"83 - 37","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 8 - 5) - 12","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"59 * 26","answer":"1534"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 10) - 4 + 97","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"17 + 100 - 4","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"94 * 55","answer":"5170"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 9) - 78","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"91 + 68","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"94 - 47","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"60 * 70","answer":"4200"}
{"prompt":"61 - 37","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"43 * (76 + 10)","answer":"3698"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 1) + 65","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"95 * 3 - 46","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"33 * 66","answer":"2178"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 2) + 5 - 11","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"92 + (44 + 7) * 3","answer":"245"}
{"prompt":"93 * 91 * 6 + 7","answer":"50785"}
{"prompt":"(29 + 1 + 5) - 27 - 10","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(58 * 3) + 4 - 96","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"((45 - 10) + 5) * 73 + 7","answer":"2927"}
{"prompt":"77 - 1 + (87 + 8 + 4)","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"9 * 8 * 70 - 1","answer":"5039"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 2 * 9) - 85","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"14 - 21 * 8","answer":"-154"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 4) + 46 - 5","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"55 - (67 + 10)","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"68 + 56","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"74 * 4 + 8 + ((23 - 5) - 8)","answer":"314"}
{"prompt":"84 * 23 * 9","answer":"17388"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 10) + (20 - 3)","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"17 + 40 + 4 + 5","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"7 - 52","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"66 * 5 - 68","answer":"262"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 6) * 8","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"((24 - 9) - 8) * (21 * 10)","answer":"1470"}
{"prompt":"4 + 96","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"51 * 81","answer":"4131"}
{"prompt":"51 - 4 - 82","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"81 - 2 * 97","answer":"-113"}
{"prompt":"80 * 83 + 7","answer":"6647"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 10 - 6) - 24","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"33 * 4 * 30 + 2","answer":"3962"}
{"prompt":"14 + 75","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"98 * 7 * 61","answer":"41846"}
{"prompt":"75 + 16 - 6","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"59 * 10 + 10 - 90","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"51 - 97","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"((96 + 1) + 1) - 38","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"4 * 1 - 21","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"71 - 11","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"32 + (13 * 3) + 5","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"85 + 6 * 1 - ((47 + 6) - 10)","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"69 - 92","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"33 - (12 - 9) * 1","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 6 - 7) * 21 - 3","answer":"1488"}
{"prompt":"13 - (87 + 8) + 4","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 6 - 10) + 87","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"95 - 59","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"38 - (62 - 9) + 7","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"17 * 8 + ((52 * 2) + 2)","answer":"242"}
{"prompt":"82 + 10 - (34 * 3)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"46 + 5","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"47 + 1 * 90","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"95 + 100","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"3 * 40","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(66 * 5 + 9) * (46 - 1 * 3)","answer":"14577"}
{"prompt":"84 + (7 * 1) - 5","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"34 + 7 * 9 - 70","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"12 - 5","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"40 + 94","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 2) * 10 - ((15 - 6) + 7)","answer":"344"}
{"prompt":"54 + 8 - 9 + 50","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"61 + (19 * 6 * 1)","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"88 + (42 * 8)","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"75 + 46","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 2) + 9 + 85","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"62 + 1 + 63 - 2","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"94 * (81 * 6 + 6)","answer":"46248"}
{"prompt":"65 + 34","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 4) * 69","answer":"4968"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 7) * 99 + 5","answer":"2975"}
{"prompt":"56 * 3 - (55 + 2)","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"13 * 66 * 10","answer":"8580"}
{"prompt":"48 + 65","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"52 - 6 + 1 + 4","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"6 + (4 + 7)","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"23 + 24","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"80 + 8 - 69","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"56 * ((9 + 4) * 2)","answer":"1456"}
{"prompt":"38 + 9 - 41","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 9) + 10 + 24","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"85 + 3","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 2) + 91","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"51 + 22","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 4) * 10 + 98","answer":"358"}
{"prompt":"44 + 40","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"83 * 9 - 5 - 6","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 6) - 45","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 6 - 8) - (71 - 8)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 7 - 10) * 8","answer":"1880"}
{"prompt":"73 * 75 - 2","answer":"5473"}
{"prompt":"84 - 10 + (3 + 8 + 2)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"38 - (67 * 1 - 4)","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"36 - (92 + 10)","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"((36 * 9) * 9) + (69 * 4)","answer":"3192"}
{"prompt":"3 - 3 + 73","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"86 + 6 * 7 * 41 * 4","answer":"6974"}
{"prompt":"((86 * 8) + 5) - 19","answer":"674"}
{"prompt":"77 + 10 + 39","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"((76 * 5) + 9) * 10","answer":"3890"}
{"prompt":"((20 + 9) - 3) - 62 - 8","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"17 + 54","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"14 + 2","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"23 * 17","answer":"391"}
{"prompt":"99 + 5 + 1 + (30 + 3 - 1)","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"5 + (98 * 7)","answer":"691"}
{"prompt":"47 - 48 * 2","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"34 * 93","answer":"3162"}
{"prompt":"90 + 42","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"75 + ((76 - 7) + 7)","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"36 + 4 - 7","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"72 - 64","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"34 + 5 + 5 + 79","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 8) + 2 * ((96 * 5) - 4)","answer":"1036"}
{"prompt":"38 - 57","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 2) - 45","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"((76 - 9) * 2) * (75 - 3) - 7","answer":"9641"}
{"prompt":"((11 - 2) - 5) + (14 - 9)","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 6 * 7) + 93","answer":"387"}
{"prompt":"53 - (59 - 4)","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"1 * 6 + 36","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"36 * 8 * (58 * 10) + 10","answer":"167050"}
{"prompt":"((74 - 10) * 1) - (96 - 5)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"6 + 65","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"89 - (39 - 1)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"78 + 4 + 5 * 82","answer":"492"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 5) + 73","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"40 * 7 - 87 * 4 * 6","answer":"-1808"}
{"prompt":"39 + 7 + 63","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 8) * 8 + (67 * 1)","answer":"763"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 8) + (35 - 1)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"39 * 53","answer":"2067"}
{"prompt":"((57 - 3) * 1) * 21 * 6","answer":"6804"}
{"prompt":"59 - 35","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 9) - (76 - 2 + 8)","answer":"674"}
{"prompt":"62 * 57","answer":"3534"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 4 - 6) + 97","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"23 * 28","answer":"644"}
{"prompt":"63 * 53 + 5 + 10","answer":"3354"}
{"prompt":"(73 * 8 + 1) * 63 + 8","answer":"36863"}
{"prompt":"100 * 81 - 5","answer":"8095"}
{"prompt":"((64 - 5) + 10) * 14","answer":"966"}
{"prompt":"((76 - 8) + 8) + 38","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"88 * 4 + 68","answer":"420"}
{"prompt":"((79 - 6) - 9) - (49 + 3)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"18 - 30","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"75 * 4 - 32","answer":"268"}
{"prompt":"58 + 39","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"89 + 2 - 7 * 68 - 5 * 7","answer":"-420"}
{"prompt":"64 * 5 + 3 * 81 * 7","answer":"2021"}
{"prompt":"96 * 13","answer":"1248"}
{"prompt":"100 + 81","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 3 * 1) + 49 + 6 - 3","answer":"217"}
{"prompt":"14 + 53","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 3) + 9 + 93 + 9","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"36 + 9 - (8 - 6)","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(2 * 3 + 7) + 43","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"((3 * 7) + 7) - 31 * 5","answer":"-127"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 6) - (16 - 6 * 8)","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 10) + 4 * 52","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"69 - 70 + 8 - 1","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"51 + (62 + 3)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 1) * 31","answer":"2542"}
{"prompt":"39 * 1 + 3 + 54 + 7 + 4","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"31 - 10 - (37 - 1)","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"43 - (46 - 2)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"(35 * 1) * (25 * 6) + 9","answer":"5259"}
{"prompt":"100 * 24","answer":"2400"}
{"prompt":"94 + 37","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"47 + 52","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"((97 - 2) - 8) + 32","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(10 - 8) - ((72 * 6) - 5)","answer":"-425"}
{"prompt":"68 + 57","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"46 * (89 - 3)","answer":"3956"}
{"prompt":"4 - (84 + 7)","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"62 - 4 + (19 - 7)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(44 * 4) + 40","answer":"216"}
{"prompt":"69 + (73 + 5)","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 7 - 6) - ((64 - 9) * 10)","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"37 - 9","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 3) * 7 + 64","answer":"1198"}
{"prompt":"42 * 94","answer":"3948"}
{"prompt":"99 * (76 * 4) + 9","answer":"30105"}
{"prompt":"11 + 20 + 2 - 8","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 6) - (22 + 2)","answer":"312"}
{"prompt":"18 - 2 + 42","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"60 * 24 + 2 - 3","answer":"1439"}
{"prompt":"((63 - 1) - 7) + 24","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"58 - 35","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"67 + 56 - 8","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"74 * 2 + 5 * 51 + 10","answer":"413"}
{"prompt":"54 * 1","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"55 * (16 + 9)","answer":"1375"}
{"prompt":"46 - 28","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"17 + 35 - 3","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(99 * 5 * 2) - 63","answer":"927"}
{"prompt":"28 - (54 + 3 + 4)","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"94 - 3 - ((90 * 3) * 7)","answer":"-1799"}
{"prompt":"8 - 8 * 81","answer":"-640"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 7) * 4 - 94 - 8","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 6) * (68 - 3)","answer":"1950"}
{"prompt":"57 * 2 * 73 + 2","answer":"8324"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 6) * ((98 - 10) + 1)","answer":"25632"}
{"prompt":"55 - (66 + 4)","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 1) * (52 * 2)","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"((4 - 9) - 4) - 57","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"81 - 23","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"15 - 5 - 26","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"39 + 6 + (10 - 7)","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"90 * 42 + 9 + 4","answer":"3793"}
{"prompt":"38 - 34 - 2","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"63 + (10 * 3)","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"87 * 58 - 2","answer":"5044"}
{"prompt":"26 - 42 * 4","answer":"-142"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1) * 6 * 68 + 6","answer":"15102"}
{"prompt":"((36 - 5) + 5) - 92","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 10) * (22 - 5) - 8","answer":"1148"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 6 - 6) + 43 * 7","answer":"853"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 6) + 9 + 13 * 2","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"90 + 55","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"53 * 20","answer":"1060"}
{"prompt":"36 - 3 * 98","answer":"-258"}
{"prompt":"((29 - 3) * 5) + 89","answer":"219"}
{"prompt":"67 * 16","answer":"1072"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 5 + 2) - 65","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"51 * 1 * (48 - 4 + 4)","answer":"2448"}
{"prompt":"66 - 60","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"37 * 5 * 9 + 47","answer":"1712"}
{"prompt":"71 + 3 - 4 * 69 * 3 * 6","answer":"-4894"}
{"prompt":"55 + 2 * 9","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"26 - ((63 - 8) * 7)","answer":"-359"}
{"prompt":"88 + (4 * 9 - 6)","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"22 - (21 - 3)","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 2 * 2) - 72","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"96 - 31","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 10) - 94","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"62 + 10 - 10","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"3 - 47","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"((58 + 7) + 2) - 59","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"18 + 10 * 6 * 47","answer":"2838"}
{"prompt":"4 + (76 * 5)","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"((96 * 1) - 3) + (11 + 5) - 6","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"66 - 56","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"20 + 89","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 6) + ((46 - 10) - 6)","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"88 - ((79 + 5) + 1)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"((34 + 4) - 5) - 16","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"67 * 23","answer":"1541"}
{"prompt":"77 * 69","answer":"5313"}
{"prompt":"55 * ((11 + 3) - 9)","answer":"275"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 5) + 60 * 3","answer":"570"}
{"prompt":"84 + 81 * 3","answer":"327"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 10) - 9 * 5","answer":"425"}
{"prompt":"78 + 1 - 8 * 59 * 6 + 7","answer":"-2746"}
{"prompt":"81 + 5 * 93","answer":"546"}
{"prompt":"47 * 6 - 95 - 2","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"87 * (72 + 3 * 6)","answer":"7830"}
{"prompt":"3 - 15 - 10","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"66 - (41 - 7 + 9)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 7) - 4 * 85","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 1) - 12","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"(4 - 6) + ((43 - 2) * 10)","answer":"408"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 4) + ((39 + 9) * 6)","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"79 * (79 - 2)","answer":"6083"}
{"prompt":"(86 - 2 + 7) - 37","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"81 * 1 * 49 - 3","answer":"3966"}
{"prompt":"4 + (96 - 6) + 3","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"42 + 28","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"8 * 7 - 55","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"33 + 8 + 3 - 61","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"69 - 54","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(6 * 4 + 7) * 72","answer":"2232"}
{"prompt":"40 + 24","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"64 + 9 * 5 - 10 * 3 - 2","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"((20 * 4) + 3) - 74","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"95 * 71 * 5","answer":"33725"}
{"prompt":"36 * 74 * 7 - 1","answer":"18647"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 1 + 4) - 79","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"22 * 10 * 10 + (15 + 7)","answer":"2222"}
{"prompt":"24 * 35 - 8 - 3","answer":"829"}
{"prompt":"59 - 9 + 3 * (75 - 9) + 2","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 8) - (38 * 4 + 4)","answer":"-105"}
{"prompt":"60 * (73 * 4 * 9)","answer":"157680"}
{"prompt":"25 + (93 + 3 + 9)","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"27 + 70","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"(12 - 8) - (15 * 4) + 6","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"57 * 75","answer":"4275"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 5 * 3) + 77 - 3","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 10) - 25","answer":"935"}
{"prompt":"70 + (48 + 5 - 4)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"67 + 35","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 10 + 8) + (92 * 7) - 5","answer":"937"}
{"prompt":"29 - 90","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 7) + (7 + 6)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"55 + 82 - 8","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"95 * 47","answer":"4465"}
{"prompt":"67 * 18 * 1 * 3","answer":"3618"}
{"prompt":"25 - 32","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 3) - 16","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"5 - (47 - 8)","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"((65 * 8) - 10) - 80","answer":"430"}
{"prompt":"58 - 2 - 4 + 15","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"62 * (39 + 8)","answer":"2914"}
{"prompt":"93 * 45","answer":"4185"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 10 + 10) - 33 - 9","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 3) - 29 * 5","answer":"-121"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 4) - 81","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"44 * 6 - 8 - ((57 * 10) + 9)","answer":"-323"}
{"prompt":"((26 * 6) - 2) - 1","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"(94 + 1) + 3 - 77","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"55 + 2 + 88","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"78 * 8 * 35","answer":"21840"}
{"prompt":"87 - 9 - 8","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 3) + 7 - (86 + 9 * 7)","answer":"-78"}
{"prompt":"34 * (56 * 5)","answer":"9520"}
{"prompt":"76 + 74 * 7","answer":"594"}
{"prompt":"86 + 81 + 7","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"84 - 5 - 7 * 2","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"89 - 87","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"21 - 5 - 8 + (81 - 8)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"93 * 71","answer":"6603"}
{"prompt":"((75 + 10) + 8) * 84","answer":"7812"}
{"prompt":"97 - 43 + 6","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"59 * 58 * 6 - 8","answer":"20524"}
{"prompt":"76 * 34 + 10","answer":"2594"}
{"prompt":"37 - 8 * 75 - 3 + 8","answer":"-558"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 1) * 17 - 5 * 7","answer":"288"}
{"prompt":"2 + 14 - 7","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"75 - 99","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"(68 * 3) - 65","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"29 - 5 + (28 - 2) + 7","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"29 * 7 - 65 * 10 - 9","answer":"-456"}
{"prompt":"69 + 11 - 4 * 5","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"15 + (56 - 7) * 1","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"13 + ((52 - 5) + 4)","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"28 * 3 - ((60 + 7) * 7)","answer":"-385"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 5 * 4) * 93","answer":"10323"}
{"prompt":"15 + 1 * 10 - (19 - 5)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(42 + 6 - 9) + 1 + 3","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"61 - 4 + 98","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(3 + 10) - 41 * 4 + 7","answer":"-144"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 6) + ((37 - 3) + 3)","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"64 + (94 * 4)","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"(9 * 1) - (7 + 9) - 7","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"89 - 5 + 5 * (70 + 2)","answer":"444"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 9) + 71","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"83 * 34","answer":"2822"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 2) - 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(79 - 6) - (22 - 3)","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"84 * (3 + 2)","answer":"420"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 7) + 1 - 1 * 7 - 2","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"13 - 1 - (80 + 6 * 9)","answer":"-122"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 6) * 1 + 76","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 4) - 37","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 7) + 4 - 83","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"5 - 6 + 82 * 1 + 10","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"55 + 31","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"14 - ((62 - 5) - 4)","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"99 + 60 - 4","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(34 * 3) + 7 + (77 * 5 - 8)","answer":"486"}
{"prompt":"86 - 24","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"96 + (51 - 3)","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 3) - 6","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"28 * 84 + 8","answer":"2360"}
{"prompt":"((23 + 5) - 2) + (86 + 3 + 4)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 4) + 20 + 6","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"67 - 79","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"63 - 3 - 86","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 2) * (20 + 2)","answer":"4224"}
{"prompt":"50 * (40 * 6)","answer":"12000"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 4 + 10) * (36 + 7)","answer":"4042"}
{"prompt":"29 + 27","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"79 - 9 - 82","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"(60 - 7) + 55","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"25 - (80 - 2) + 2","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"99 * 51 + 7","answer":"5056"}
{"prompt":"((49 - 4) - 7) + 44","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 5) - 96","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"77 * 3 * 38","answer":"8778"}
{"prompt":"((50 + 6) * 1) + 40 * 9","answer":"416"}
{"prompt":"62 + 87","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 10) + 64","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"((2 * 10) + 3) * 6","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"((10 * 6) + 9) - (49 - 3)","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"58 - 12","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"35 - 3 - 87","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"62 - 6 + 6 - 74","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 1 - 6) - (38 + 9)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 10 + 8) * 14","answer":"938"}
{"prompt":"91 - (6 - 8)","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"97 + 5 - 88","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"79 - (47 * 5)","answer":"-156"}
{"prompt":"8 - 7 - 75 * 10","answer":"-749"}
{"prompt":"((97 + 4) * 7) * 73","answer":"51611"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 2 + 8) * 31","answer":"341"}
{"prompt":"58 + 83","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"66 + 18 + 1 * 10","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 10 + 1) - 59","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(87 + 8 * 3) + 16","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"46 + (4 * 4)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 3 - 3) * ((26 - 4) - 6)","answer":"752"}
{"prompt":"((34 * 3) * 9) - 33","answer":"885"}
{"prompt":"91 - 5 + 47","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"68 + 9 + 94","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"57 + 9","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"99 - 59 + 9","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 5) - 5 + (70 * 7)","answer":"725"}
{"prompt":"17 + (11 * 9)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"35 * (50 - 9)","answer":"1435"}
{"prompt":"((97 * 3) * 4) + 27 + 1","answer":"1192"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 3) - 30","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"40 + 81","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(47 + 5) + 69","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"23 * 9","answer":"207"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 6) + 62 + 4","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"71 - 21","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"19 - ((18 * 1) + 5)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"((95 * 3) * 2) * 20 + 9","answer":"11409"}
{"prompt":"52 - 81","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"48 + 8 + 17","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 10) * 5 + (85 - 3)","answer":"227"}
{"prompt":"83 - 1 - 10","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"49 * 53","answer":"2597"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 6 - 6) + 32 - 6 * 3","answer":"266"}
{"prompt":"22 * 8 + 7 - ((6 + 7) * 6)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"52 - 77 * 8","answer":"-564"}
{"prompt":"68 - 4 * 3 * 7","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"10 + (94 + 1) - 2","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"46 - ((92 * 2) * 8)","answer":"-1426"}
{"prompt":"(86 * 5) + 4 - (37 - 1)","answer":"398"}
{"prompt":"77 + 52","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"95 - 91 * 7","answer":"-542"}
{"prompt":"68 - 55","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"35 + (85 * 4 + 1)","answer":"376"}
{"prompt":"91 * 92 - 10 * 2","answer":"8352"}
{"prompt":"83 * 3 - (89 - 10) + 9","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"8 + 99","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 3 * 9) * (20 * 5) + 10","answer":"2810"}
{"prompt":"84 - 58","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 2) * ((12 * 8) * 4)","answer":"30336"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 8) - 3 * (37 * 10)","answer":"-1058"}
{"prompt":"69 - 78 * 8 * 7","answer":"-4299"}
{"prompt":"51 - 2 - (9 + 9)","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 3) + (92 * 2) + 9","answer":"279"}
{"prompt":"93 + 7 + (91 * 7) - 9","answer":"728"}
{"prompt":"79 + (50 + 5)","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 3) - 9 - 82 + 9","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"39 - 99","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"2 * 86 - 10 + 2","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 6) - 3","answer":"495"}
{"prompt":"51 + ((33 - 6) + 2)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"32 * 35 * 4 - 2","answer":"4478"}
{"prompt":"71 * 3 - 85","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"28 + 85 * 1","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"94 + 43","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"29 - 41","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"64 - ((67 * 4) * 3)","answer":"-740"}
{"prompt":"97 - 83","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 9) + 70 - 5","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 1) + 72 + 1","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"10 - ((37 - 10) - 2)","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 4 * 7) - 32 - 8 * 2","answer":"1016"}
{"prompt":"((99 + 2) * 5) + ((89 + 3) - 8)","answer":"589"}
{"prompt":"87 + 99","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"12 - ((32 - 8) - 5)","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 2) - (70 * 10 * 2)","answer":"-1347"}
{"prompt":"59 + 3 * 1 - 76","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(64 + 10) - 3 * 57 - 6","answer":"-103"}
{"prompt":"100 * 62 - 5","answer":"6195"}
{"prompt":"85 - 63","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"16 + 7 - ((74 * 8) * 1)","answer":"-569"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 3) + 6 * ((11 * 2) * 2)","answer":"285"}
{"prompt":"13 + 2","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"4 - 70","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"20 + 56","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"55 * 7 + 8 + 4 * 9 - 10","answer":"419"}
{"prompt":"20 + 3 * 10 * (77 - 1) + 9","answer":"2309"}
{"prompt":"(20 + 6 * 2) - (93 + 1) * 3","answer":"-250"}
{"prompt":"13 + 44","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"30 + ((13 * 10) + 5)","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"86 + 18","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"8 + 1","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"13 - 1 * 99 * 9 - 9","answer":"-887"}
{"prompt":"48 - 87 * 3","answer":"-213"}
{"prompt":"35 - 64 - 6 + 10","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"76 + (96 * 5) * 6","answer":"2956"}
{"prompt":"86 + 2 - (34 * 5)","answer":"-82"}
{"prompt":"25 - 2 - (72 + 5)","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 1 + 5) - 71","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 6) + 47 + 4 + 3","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"(71 - 2 + 1) - 70","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"8 * 61","answer":"488"}
{"prompt":"38 + (19 - 6)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((72 - 3) * 2) * 66 * 8","answer":"72864"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 6) * 4 + (86 - 9)","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 3) * 4","answer":"768"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 6) - 49 - 10","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"52 - 24","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"45 - 12 * 10","answer":"-75"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 9) + 84","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"94 * 6 * 10 * 4","answer":"22560"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 7 + 8) + (11 - 3) + 1","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"9 - 52 - 3 - 6","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"65 + 14","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"97 + (61 + 4)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"18 * 90","answer":"1620"}
{"prompt":"27 * 6 + 10 + ((46 * 1) + 1)","answer":"219"}
{"prompt":"84 - 59","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"3 * 64","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 7) - 6 * (80 - 9)","answer":"-223"}
{"prompt":"57 + (12 * 1 - 2)","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"99 * (18 * 5 - 8)","answer":"8118"}
{"prompt":"5 + 65 - 8","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"45 + 9","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"61 - 84 + 10 * 5","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 3) - 47","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 7) + (49 - 8 - 8)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"63 * 4 - 7 - 26","answer":"219"}
{"prompt":"12 * (26 + 10 + 8)","answer":"528"}
{"prompt":"16 * (20 * 8 + 10)","answer":"2720"}
{"prompt":"54 - 6 * 20 * 2","answer":"-186"}
{"prompt":"62 * 29","answer":"1798"}
{"prompt":"92 - 3 * 76 + 2","answer":"-134"}
{"prompt":"32 + (66 + 1)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 1) - 37","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"((95 - 10) - 10) * (90 * 7) - 5","answer":"47245"}
{"prompt":"3 * (33 * 8)","answer":"792"}
{"prompt":"63 * 9","answer":"567"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 3) + 19","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"96 - (82 * 10 + 4)","answer":"-728"}
{"prompt":"3 + 10 - 6 * ((2 - 7) + 7)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(87 * 8 - 7) * 58","answer":"39962"}
{"prompt":"21 + 3 + 6 + (85 - 5)","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 1) * 4 - 73","answer":"191"}
{"prompt":"35 + 3 - 4 * 96","answer":"-346"}
{"prompt":"82 - 92","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"38 - 36","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 6) + 2 * 46 * 9","answer":"843"}
{"prompt":"78 - 18","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"71 + ((54 + 6) - 1)","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"62 + 3 * 6 * 2","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"98 * (48 + 1)","answer":"4802"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 1) * 3 * 62","answer":"17484"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 2) - 1 * 30 - 3","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"1 + 65 + 9","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"90 * 72","answer":"6480"}
{"prompt":"((61 * 7) - 2) * 33","answer":"14025"}
{"prompt":"4 - 33 - 8","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"((30 * 1) + 9) - (80 + 9)","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 2) - (71 - 7 * 4)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"91 * 2 + 10 + 43 * 8 + 8","answer":"544"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 4) - 10","answer":"206"}
{"prompt":"5 + 66","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"36 + 94","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 2) - 90","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 8) - 6 + 3","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"((65 * 1) * 1) + (38 + 10)","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"14 - 31","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"2 * 19 * 9 - 6","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"64 - (64 + 10) * 3","answer":"-158"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 2) - 78","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"43 + ((82 + 4) * 6)","answer":"559"}
{"prompt":"54 * (27 - 3 - 3)","answer":"1134"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 8) * 10 - 26","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 8) + 10 + 65","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 9) + (88 + 6)","answer":"382"}
{"prompt":"(85 + 1) - 97","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"90 + (58 - 2)","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"95 * 3 * 7","answer":"1995"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 7) * 68 + 7 + 4","answer":"6811"}
{"prompt":"52 - 18 - 9","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"26 + 59","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 4 * 4) - 9","answer":"871"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 9) + 85 - 1","answer":"912"}
{"prompt":"((65 + 10) * 2) * 17","answer":"2550"}
{"prompt":"76 + (44 - 2 - 1)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"69 - (84 + 1)","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 4) + 10 * 87","answer":"1234"}
{"prompt":"18 * 4 + (11 + 7) + 5","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"89 * 37","answer":"3293"}
{"prompt":"61 - 2 * 1 + 3","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 8) - 1 - 76 - 3","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"((95 + 8) * 6) - (28 * 1) * 6","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"19 - (89 + 7)","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"96 * 2 - 3 + 14 + 1","answer":"204"}
{"prompt":"56 + (41 - 7) * 7","answer":"294"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 7) + 7 * 68 + 10","answer":"1158"}
{"prompt":"61 - 10 * 7 + 8","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"1 * 12 + 1","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"76 - ((70 + 1) - 1)","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"15 * 83","answer":"1245"}
{"prompt":"((93 + 7) * 8) + (98 - 2)","answer":"896"}
{"prompt":"56 * (26 + 7) * 4","answer":"7392"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 2) - (93 * 1 - 5)","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"89 - 6 + 4 * (21 + 7 * 10)","answer":"447"}
{"prompt":"73 + 96 - 5","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"40 * ((80 + 4) + 4)","answer":"3520"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 2) - 86","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"((40 - 5) + 7) + ((75 * 2) - 4)","answer":"188"}
{"prompt":"(53 - 1) + (19 * 3) - 2","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 2 + 7) - 59","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"85 * (82 + 9)","answer":"7735"}
{"prompt":"3 + 2","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"42 * 92 + 8","answer":"3872"}
{"prompt":"45 - 68","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"37 - ((74 * 10) + 10)","answer":"-713"}
{"prompt":"((66 + 5) - 3) - 91","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"62 + 8 + (17 + 5)","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"51 + 24","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"((76 * 4) * 10) - (13 + 3)","answer":"3024"}
{"prompt":"24 + 86 + 10 + 2","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 5) + ((27 - 4) + 5)","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"24 + 1 - 93","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"6 + 92","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(77 + 6) + (32 + 7)","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 4) - 6 - ((59 + 7) * 2)","answer":"-111"}
{"prompt":"92 + 10 * 10 - (97 - 5)","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"38 - 8 - (49 * 5)","answer":"-215"}
{"prompt":"6 + 3 + 9 * 66 + 5 - 4","answer":"604"}
{"prompt":"59 * 88","answer":"5192"}
{"prompt":"28 - 2 + ((41 * 9) + 2)","answer":"397"}
{"prompt":"(89 - 6) - 5 - 89","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"((69 * 10) + 7) + 53","answer":"750"}
{"prompt":"61 + 80","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"28 * 52 * 5 - 3","answer":"7277"}
{"prompt":"24 - 51","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"19 * 87","answer":"1653"}
{"prompt":"19 * 4 + 8 * 3","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"39 - 33","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"27 - 3 * 76","answer":"-201"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 10) - 7 + 50","answer":"813"}
{"prompt":"10 + (89 * 5) * 3","answer":"1345"}
{"prompt":"((31 - 10) + 1) + 69","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 10) + (44 * 8 + 4)","answer":"926"}
{"prompt":"7 * (17 + 6)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"37 - 9 - 3 + 38","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"42 * 4 - (36 + 9)","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"69 - 22","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"25 + (83 + 9)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"78 + 80 * 6 * 1","answer":"558"}
{"prompt":"50 + 2 * 6 - (32 + 2 - 4)","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"96 + 34","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 1 - 5) - 67 * 4","answer":"-221"}
{"prompt":"(13 - 4) * (79 - 6)","answer":"657"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 1) * 7 + 93 * 7","answer":"1330"}
{"prompt":"88 * 67","answer":"5896"}
{"prompt":"44 + (34 + 2)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 7) * 53","answer":"4081"}
{"prompt":"((100 - 2) * 6) + 23 - 6 + 2","answer":"607"}
{"prompt":"21 - 1 * 99 - 4","answer":"-82"}
{"prompt":"74 - 53","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"93 * (55 + 9) + 3","answer":"5955"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 6) + 34","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"96 + 13","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 2) + (31 + 4) - 4","answer":"201"}
{"prompt":"((63 + 1) - 8) * 37","answer":"2072"}
{"prompt":"39 - 7 * 69 + 8","answer":"-436"}
{"prompt":"49 - 37","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"10 - 1 + 84","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"43 - (75 - 1) * 10","answer":"-697"}
{"prompt":"25 * 86","answer":"2150"}
{"prompt":"83 * 71","answer":"5893"}
{"prompt":"57 - 1 + 37 * 10 - 8","answer":"418"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 7) - 65","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"20 * 7 - 70","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"88 * 25","answer":"2200"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 9) * 29 + 4 - 2","answer":"1829"}
{"prompt":"23 + 1 + 7 * 95","answer":"689"}
{"prompt":"11 - (89 + 8)","answer":"-86"}
{"prompt":"49 + 68 - 1 * 9","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"97 - (62 + 7 * 10)","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"76 * (41 - 6) - 1","answer":"2659"}
{"prompt":"(2 + 6 + 10) - 82","answer":"-64"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 5) + (48 + 9 + 5)","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"35 + 47","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"61 * 18 * 9","answer":"9882"}
{"prompt":"51 - (36 + 9)","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"95 - 15 * 10","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"56 - 87","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 9) - 38","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"62 - 92","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"48 * 77","answer":"3696"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 7) * 2) - 53 - 2","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 9) + 72","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"71 - 84","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"22 + ((86 + 6) - 9)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 2) * 9 - 71","answer":"343"}
{"prompt":"86 * 67","answer":"5762"}
{"prompt":"2 + 55","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"52 - 27","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"78 * 2 - (36 - 7)","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"34 + 1 + (46 * 2) - 6","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 4) + (41 + 7)","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 4) - (2 + 1)","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"3 + 75","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"30 + (22 - 9)","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"5 * 4 + 33","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"69 + 73","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"((94 - 8) + 3) - 76","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"40 - 43","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 2) * (85 + 6)","answer":"3458"}
{"prompt":"13 - 67","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"86 * 4 * 6 - 72 + 8 + 8","answer":"2008"}
{"prompt":"100 * 91 + 3","answer":"9103"}
{"prompt":"24 + 98 + 6","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"88 + 11","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"47 + 9 * 9 - (94 * 2)","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"((71 - 7) - 10) + 63","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"53 * 8","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"5 * 37","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 1) - (81 + 8 - 4)","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"99 * 70","answer":"6930"}
{"prompt":"45 * 39","answer":"1755"}
{"prompt":"100 * (40 + 5 * 2)","answer":"5000"}
{"prompt":"22 - 49","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"38 - (92 + 4)","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"67 * 8 + 27 * 3","answer":"617"}
{"prompt":"21 - 54","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"51 + 23 - 10","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"70 * (39 * 5) * 5","answer":"68250"}
{"prompt":"42 + 42 - 7","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 6) - 8 * ((60 * 2) - 7)","answer":"-860"}
{"prompt":"45 - 40","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"76 - 96","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"((36 - 10) - 10) - 66","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"84 * (50 * 9)","answer":"37800"}
{"prompt":"18 + 2 + 58","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"((93 - 5) + 3) - (92 + 5) + 1","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"51 * 6","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 6) + 46 * 6","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 10) * 2 - 43","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"49 + (3 * 6 - 2)","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"10 * 2 - 5 - 60","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"70 + 9 + (62 - 6 * 7)","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 2) - 1 - 41","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"((50 - 2) + 4) + 98 + 4","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 1 * 8) - 96","answer":"-99"}
{"prompt":"(45 + 3) * 1 + (75 * 10)","answer":"798"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 3) - 66","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"(100 * 2) - 1","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"23 - 10 - 6 * 84 - 3","answer":"-494"}
{"prompt":"65 - 8 * 10 + 2","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"73 * ((67 * 2) - 6)","answer":"9344"}
{"prompt":"35 * 98","answer":"3430"}
{"prompt":"78 * 28","answer":"2184"}
{"prompt":"43 * 12","answer":"516"}
{"prompt":"64 - 44","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"42 * 82","answer":"3444"}
{"prompt":"92 * 33 + 4 + 10","answer":"3050"}
{"prompt":"32 - (95 + 2)","answer":"-65"}
{"prompt":"64 * (38 * 8)","answer":"19456"}
{"prompt":"77 * 8 - 5 * 86 * 1","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 7 + 6) + 41 * 9 + 7","answer":"434"}
{"prompt":"94 * 59 + 7 + 1","answer":"5554"}
{"prompt":"(84 - 3) * 17","answer":"1377"}
{"prompt":"52 + 1","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"55 + 80 + 2","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"13 * 4 + 45","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"3 + (38 * 8 - 10)","answer":"297"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 2) - 76","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"51 * 12","answer":"612"}
{"prompt":"71 + 93","answer":"164"}
{"prompt":"60 + 1 - 39","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"28 * 89 + 4","answer":"2496"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 8) + 71","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"54 - 2 + 36","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"2 - 8 + 5 + 4","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 2) - 64","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"43 + 34","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"24 + (47 * 8)","answer":"400"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 5) - 57 * 3","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"5 * 1 * 10 + 49 + 3","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"16 - 4 * 44","answer":"-160"}
{"prompt":"78 - (53 - 5)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"10 + 71 - 7 + 10","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(91 * 4 * 6) - 46 - 3","answer":"2135"}
{"prompt":"87 + 89","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"72 - (62 + 6) + 2","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 2) - (87 + 7)","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"((56 - 8) * 2) * (43 - 7) + 7","answer":"3463"}
{"prompt":"67 * 1 + 6 + (1 - 4) * 5","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"35 + 95","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"91 * 20 + 3","answer":"1823"}
{"prompt":"6 + ((39 * 1) + 5)","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 10 - 8) * (37 * 3)","answer":"2331"}
{"prompt":"43 * 6 + 86 + 8 * 10","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 1) + 91","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"28 * 85","answer":"2380"}
{"prompt":"((48 * 9) * 3) - 34 * 9","answer":"990"}
{"prompt":"(38 * 1) * (53 + 3) * 7","answer":"14896"}
{"prompt":"82 + 47 - 8","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"12 * 7 + 7 - 6","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"68 * (18 + 8)","answer":"1768"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 5) * 10 * 56","answer":"75600"}
{"prompt":"((13 - 6) * 8) * ((43 + 7) * 5)","answer":"14000"}
{"prompt":"93 * 21","answer":"1953"}
{"prompt":"95 * (60 * 8 + 8)","answer":"46360"}
{"prompt":"64 * 79","answer":"5056"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 9) + 61","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"81 + 3 + 9 + 16","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"48 * 19","answer":"912"}
{"prompt":"34 + (15 - 1) - 3","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 6) - 45","answer":"273"}
{"prompt":"4 * 1 - 24","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"25 - (77 - 6)","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"21 - 43 + 7","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 8 + 6) - ((76 + 2) - 4)","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"27 * 21","answer":"567"}
{"prompt":"71 * 60","answer":"4260"}
{"prompt":"((61 + 10) + 8) + 28","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"41 - 69","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 4) * 5) * 42 + 7","answer":"8407"}
{"prompt":"6 - 8 - 10 + (25 + 10) + 8","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"76 - 87","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"66 + 58","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(34 - 9) - 4 + 84","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 1 + 1) + 29","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 4 - 6) * 65","answer":"3640"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 8) * 7 * (60 - 2)","answer":"68208"}
{"prompt":"54 - 79 + 3 + 2","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 2) * 74 * 10","answer":"116920"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 2 + 10) + (99 * 1 * 5)","answer":"556"}
{"prompt":"59 + 30","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"1 + 6 * 10 + (56 * 8)","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"99 * (22 - 10) * 2","answer":"2376"}
{"prompt":"82 * ((33 + 1) * 10)","answer":"27880"}
{"prompt":"58 * 66 - 10 - 1","answer":"3817"}
{"prompt":"7 + 7 * 19","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 4 * 3) * 48 * 10","answer":"26400"}
{"prompt":"64 * 92","answer":"5888"}
{"prompt":"89 * 83","answer":"7387"}
{"prompt":"2 * 15","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"40 * 40 - 4 - 2","answer":"1594"}
{"prompt":"22 - 32 + 5 - 5","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(48 - 6) - 1 + 14 * 2","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"89 + 23 * 8 * 9","answer":"1745"}
{"prompt":"87 - 2 + 5","answer":"90"}
{"prompt":"38 - ((37 * 2) * 9)","answer":"-628"}
{"prompt":"40 + 9 + 67 + 4","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"66 - 3 * 77","answer":"-165"}
{"prompt":"(22 * 10 - 4) - 86","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"25 + 2 - 9 * 75","answer":"-648"}
{"prompt":"46 + 29","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 3) - (30 * 5 - 8)","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"70 - 95","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"23 - 28","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"91 + 38","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 3 * 8) + ((3 - 1) - 4)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"57 + 10 + (94 * 1 + 10)","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"72 + 9 - 66","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"75 + 2 + 5 * 2","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"((17 + 9) * 1) - 5","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"81 * 9 * (4 - 7) - 6","answer":"-2193"}
{"prompt":"79 - (96 + 9) + 1","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"60 + 70 + 4","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"65 - 27 * 2 - 4","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"90 + (41 + 3) - 3","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"4 + (34 - 4)","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"30 - 87 + 7","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 8) - 49","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"29 * 1 - 7 - 75 * 5","answer":"-353"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 1 - 4) + ((85 + 9) * 8)","answer":"814"}
{"prompt":"71 + (81 + 10)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"89 + (91 - 2)","answer":"178"}
{"prompt":"28 * 31","answer":"868"}
{"prompt":"17 * 39","answer":"663"}
{"prompt":"((99 + 5) - 10) * 52","answer":"4888"}
{"prompt":"29 + 1 - 3 - (66 + 6)","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"57 + 95","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"85 - 9 - 4","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"74 * 27","answer":"1998"}
{"prompt":"71 + 72","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"40 - 69","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"94 + (98 - 5) + 6","answer":"193"}
{"prompt":"74 + 43 * 7","answer":"375"}
{"prompt":"69 + (29 + 10 - 3)","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 8) - 23 - 9","answer":"648"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 2) + 70","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"75 + 22 + 3","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"18 + 50 * 1","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"99 * 72","answer":"7128"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 9) * 92","answer":"7728"}
{"prompt":"39 - (85 * 1)","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"81 * 6 * 13","answer":"6318"}
{"prompt":"6 * (61 + 1)","answer":"372"}
{"prompt":"62 - (79 * 5) - 6","answer":"-339"}
{"prompt":"23 - 18 + 5 * 4","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"42 - 41","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 6) + 66","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"87 - 66","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"55 + 6 * 7 * (54 + 1 + 4)","answer":"2533"}
{"prompt":"44 + 65 * 1","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"75 - 77","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"98 * 1","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"98 * 42","answer":"4116"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 7) + 6 * (62 - 10)","answer":"361"}
{"prompt":"36 + 42","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"97 + (38 + 8) - 7","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"54 * (92 - 3)","answer":"4806"}
{"prompt":"75 + 10 + 2 + 27","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"41 - (98 - 4) - 7","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"98 - 19 - 8","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"91 * 48","answer":"4368"}
{"prompt":"((2 * 8) + 1) * 49","answer":"833"}
{"prompt":"33 * 8","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"58 - 39","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"2 - 7 + 23","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"19 * 9 + 39 * 9","answer":"522"}
{"prompt":"57 * 2 * 98","answer":"11172"}
{"prompt":"58 + (58 + 4)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 7 - 8) * 75","answer":"4800"}
{"prompt":"91 + 6 * 4 + 50","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"94 - 5 - 39","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(13 - 1) + 6 + 52","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"93 - 41","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"8 + 3 + 4 + 54 * 1","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"((42 * 6) + 5) * (43 - 4 - 2)","answer":"9509"}
{"prompt":"98 - 8 + 55 - 9","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 10) + (47 - 4 * 3)","answer":"315"}
{"prompt":"4 * (96 - 1)","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"80 * (79 * 9)","answer":"56880"}
{"prompt":"77 - (11 - 5 - 7)","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"100 - 10 - 1 * 17 - 8","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 8) - 88","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"85 - (3 + 9 + 10)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"53 - 10 + 10","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"18 + 59 + 8 + 2","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(31 - 5 + 4) - ((18 + 4) - 7)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 3) * 3) * (45 - 9) * 1","answer":"6156"}
{"prompt":"72 - 21","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"84 * 33","answer":"2772"}
{"prompt":"((3 - 2) * 5) - 9","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 2 - 9) + (70 - 1)","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 5 + 4) * 3 + 5","answer":"1247"}
{"prompt":"53 + 5 - 31","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"40 - 2 + 8","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"83 * (86 - 6)","answer":"6640"}
{"prompt":"35 - 54 * 7 - 2","answer":"-345"}
{"prompt":"11 * 92","answer":"1012"}
{"prompt":"42 * 88","answer":"3696"}
{"prompt":"(43 * 10) - 2 * ((30 * 1) + 10)","answer":"350"}
{"prompt":"75 + (1 * 6)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 3) * 9 + 30","answer":"399"}
{"prompt":"20 + 95","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"76 + 18","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"11 + 82 - 6 * 3","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 2 + 1) - 70","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"22 - 36","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"86 + 18","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"30 - 42 - 6 + 2","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"67 + 59","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"82 + 5 + 9 * 52","answer":"555"}
{"prompt":"36 + 81 + 1","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"14 * 68","answer":"952"}
{"prompt":"29 - 4 * 8 * (17 + 10 - 3)","answer":"-739"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 7) * ((44 * 7) * 1)","answer":"16324"}
{"prompt":"44 + 11","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"35 + (21 + 7)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(62 - 10) - 65","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(5 + 2 * 8) * 42","answer":"882"}
{"prompt":"48 * 7 + 44 + 4","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"23 + 5 * 17 * 8","answer":"703"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 2) * (75 * 4)","answer":"12600"}
{"prompt":"(83 - 10) * (52 + 7 - 3)","answer":"4088"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 1) * 31 * 5","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"((29 - 10) * 4) + (14 - 8) + 3","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"74 - 55","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"38 + (37 - 1) - 10","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 3) * 100","answer":"20100"}
{"prompt":"22 + 2 + 15","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"73 * 75","answer":"5475"}
{"prompt":"59 - 9 + 83","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"30 - (38 * 6)","answer":"-198"}
{"prompt":"3 * 2 - (85 * 6)","answer":"-504"}
{"prompt":"1 + (47 - 2)","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"5 * 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"76 + 1 - 7 - 67","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"70 * 28","answer":"1960"}
{"prompt":"4 - 33","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"60 - (49 * 6)","answer":"-234"}
{"prompt":"91 - 29","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"89 - 65 * 10","answer":"-561"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 5) - 1 - (3 + 5)","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"65 + 36","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"41 - 9 - 75","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"18 * 4 + 5 + 16 * 7","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 5) * 2 - (53 - 7)","answer":"504"}
{"prompt":"90 + 94","answer":"184"}
{"prompt":"48 + 48","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"42 * 40","answer":"1680"}
{"prompt":"86 - ((62 * 9) + 2)","answer":"-474"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 9) + 100","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 7 * 3) + 88","answer":"361"}
{"prompt":"36 - 82","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"48 * 52","answer":"2496"}
{"prompt":"34 * 4 + 1 * 15","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"44 + (96 * 4)","answer":"428"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 1) * 31 - 4","answer":"616"}
{"prompt":"16 * 24","answer":"384"}
{"prompt":"36 + (27 - 1)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(22 - 8) * 18 * 1","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"84 * 67","answer":"5628"}
{"prompt":"20 * 22","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"95 - 24","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"66 * 6 + 85","answer":"481"}
{"prompt":"(36 - 4) - 65 * 4","answer":"-228"}
{"prompt":"71 * 7 * 8 * 71","answer":"282296"}
{"prompt":"5 * 2 * 63","answer":"630"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 8) * ((97 + 7) - 10)","answer":"4982"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 9) + ((83 + 6) * 7)","answer":"1172"}
{"prompt":"5 - 35","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"52 * (64 * 6)","answer":"19968"}
{"prompt":"14 - (17 - 9 * 3)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"37 - (97 - 2 - 7)","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 5) + 1) * 93","answer":"8742"}
{"prompt":"48 + 1 * 3 - (76 * 4 - 4)","answer":"-249"}
{"prompt":"56 * 65","answer":"3640"}
{"prompt":"(4 + 8) - 88","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"52 * 83","answer":"4316"}
{"prompt":"95 + 57","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 6 * 4) + 4","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"27 - ((81 - 3) * 1)","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"61 + 1 + (9 - 9)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"10 - 85 - 1","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"60 - 4 + 2 + (43 * 10 * 2)","answer":"918"}
{"prompt":"47 * 9 + 6 - 12","answer":"417"}
{"prompt":"65 * 82 - 5","answer":"5325"}
{"prompt":"83 * 53","answer":"4399"}
{"prompt":"((84 - 7) * 5) * (94 - 6)","answer":"33880"}
{"prompt":"79 - 9 - ((70 + 9) - 5)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"87 * 13","answer":"1131"}
{"prompt":"18 * (1 - 5 - 2)","answer":"-108"}
{"prompt":"37 * 67","answer":"2479"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 5) - 24","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 9) - ((17 - 8) * 8)","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"40 + 40","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"36 * 76 * 3","answer":"8208"}
{"prompt":"((8 - 8) * 3) * 64","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"72 + 7 - 56","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 7) - 10 - 25 - 6","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 4) * 57","answer":"3591"}
{"prompt":"93 - ((24 * 9) - 10)","answer":"-113"}
{"prompt":"48 - 38","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 5) - 2 * 98","answer":"-184"}
{"prompt":"32 + 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"18 * (35 * 9 - 10)","answer":"5490"}
{"prompt":"29 * 100","answer":"2900"}
{"prompt":"46 + 26","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"49 + 95","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 8) * 56","answer":"3360"}
{"prompt":"42 * 30","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"92 * (83 * 9) + 9","answer":"68733"}
{"prompt":"68 * 7 - 96","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"11 - 2 - ((37 + 4) - 5)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 5) * 6) * 60","answer":"6480"}
{"prompt":"25 - 89 + 6","answer":"-58"}
{"prompt":"38 * 7 + 9 - (20 - 4)","answer":"259"}
{"prompt":"65 * 1","answer":"65"}
{"prompt":"(80 - 1) - (96 - 4) - 4","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"66 + 36","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"21 + 5 + 3 - 43","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 8) + 51","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"10 * 18","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"57 - 9 * 62","answer":"-501"}
{"prompt":"34 * (62 + 2)","answer":"2176"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 10) - 67 + 2","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(48 + 7) - (45 - 8)","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 5) * 10","answer":"290"}
{"prompt":"69 * 89 - 1 * 9","answer":"6132"}
{"prompt":"15 + 28","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"61 * 62","answer":"3782"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 2) * 2 * 64","answer":"5120"}
{"prompt":"58 - 4 + 10 + 10","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"83 + 62","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"29 * 16","answer":"464"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 9) + 5 + 7","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"35 + (26 * 4) - 3","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 4) * 99","answer":"15444"}
{"prompt":"9 * 4 - (17 - 8 - 3)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"77 + 9 + 32 - 10","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 2) - 7 - 9","answer":"59"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 2) - (68 - 10)","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"22 * 7 + 48 - 3","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"14 * ((21 * 5) - 5)","answer":"1400"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((81 - 6) - 7)","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 7) + 4 - 1 * 6","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 7) - (99 + 2) + 5","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"27 - 43 - 5 + 4","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 7) + (63 * 1) - 7","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"66 - 69 - 1","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"44 - (46 + 4 * 7)","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"62 - 39 + 9","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"22 + (93 - 3) + 1","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"56 * (77 * 6) * 3","answer":"77616"}
{"prompt":"((11 - 7) - 6) - 90","answer":"-92"}
{"prompt":"20 * 39","answer":"780"}
{"prompt":"15 + ((34 * 2) * 8)","answer":"559"}
{"prompt":"17 * 50","answer":"850"}
{"prompt":"((80 * 9) + 2) + 65 * 8 + 6","answer":"1248"}
{"prompt":"(46 + 1 * 4) + 60 - 2","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"3 * 91","answer":"273"}
{"prompt":"92 + (24 * 3 - 3)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"73 + 88 - 6 - 1","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"98 + 41 * 3 * 9","answer":"1205"}
{"prompt":"45 * 12 - 9","answer":"531"}
{"prompt":"88 + 60","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"8 - 32","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"95 * 2 + (19 + 4)","answer":"213"}
{"prompt":"(17 + 9 - 6) - 96","answer":"-76"}
{"prompt":"76 * ((91 + 2) + 3)","answer":"7296"}
{"prompt":"99 - (41 + 3)","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"85 * 91","answer":"7735"}
{"prompt":"56 - 97 + 8 - 3","answer":"-36"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 5) - 8 * 80","answer":"-485"}
{"prompt":"26 * 99","answer":"2574"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 7) * 3) * ((60 - 5) * 7)","answer":"109725"}
{"prompt":"((3 - 7) + 8) * 95","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 9 - 1) + 63 * 10","answer":"1331"}
{"prompt":"1 - ((41 * 2) - 7)","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"((43 + 1) - 5) - 17","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"50 - (9 + 4) * 7","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 10) - 88 * 6","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"84 * 62","answer":"5208"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 10 + 8) * (40 * 8)","answer":"13120"}
{"prompt":"74 + (34 * 2 - 7)","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"74 + 58 * 9","answer":"596"}
{"prompt":"53 - 7 + 10 - 34","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"51 * 4 - (88 * 4)","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"75 * (59 + 8)","answer":"5025"}
{"prompt":"21 * 6 - (96 - 4)","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"7 - 85 * 10 * 6","answer":"-5093"}
{"prompt":"2 * (42 - 7)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"46 + ((17 - 3) - 2)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"4 * 98 + 1","answer":"393"}
{"prompt":"43 * 7 - 6 * (71 - 5)","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"69 + 65 + 1","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"68 * (83 * 8)","answer":"45152"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 7) + (5 - 9) * 6","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"53 * 21","answer":"1113"}
{"prompt":"97 * 7 + ((11 - 2) + 8)","answer":"696"}
{"prompt":"84 + ((14 + 9) * 4)","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"13 - 100","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"17 + 5 * 73","answer":"382"}
{"prompt":"65 + 26","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"68 - (98 * 4)","answer":"-324"}
{"prompt":"52 + 66 * 1 - 8","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(86 + 1 + 3) - 71","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"37 - (25 - 8) + 6","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"15 + (78 * 9)","answer":"717"}
{"prompt":"60 + (98 + 7 * 10)","answer":"228"}
{"prompt":"88 - (67 - 7) - 6","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"66 + ((27 - 10) * 1)","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"16 * 9 - 50","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"20 - (1 - 2 - 5)","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"56 * 26","answer":"1456"}
{"prompt":"5 - 4 + 13","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"25 * 7 * 4 - (36 * 2) + 6","answer":"634"}
{"prompt":"55 - (78 + 1)","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"71 + 2 + 58","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"7 + 31 - 6","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 3) - 2","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"69 + ((48 - 9) * 8)","answer":"381"}
{"prompt":"94 * (48 * 2)","answer":"9024"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 1) * 6 * 32","answer":"5184"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 8) - 97","answer":"-81"}
{"prompt":"41 * 16","answer":"656"}
{"prompt":"15 - 78","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"37 - 3 * (99 + 3 - 1)","answer":"-266"}
{"prompt":"35 * 9 - 46","answer":"269"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 4 + 10) * 70","answer":"23940"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 8) + 9) * 4 + 1","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 10) + 34 * 1 + 7","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(13 + 5) + (40 + 9 - 9)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(62 * 3 - 7) - 36 * 2","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 3) + 7 - 26","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"1 + 79 - 9","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 10) + (90 * 10 * 10)","answer":"9540"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 9 + 1) - 97","answer":"-79"}
{"prompt":"(67 + 1) - 1 - 72","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"1 + 63 - 1 + 9","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"20 + 46 + 3","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"41 + 4 + 17","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 1) + 25","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"66 + 9 - 50","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"46 + 76","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"20 - 1","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(78 - 7 - 2) + (85 - 6)","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"34 + 78 + 5 - 10","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"88 * 3 - 64","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"11 * 2 * (57 - 4)","answer":"1166"}
{"prompt":"74 * 3 - 3 - 61","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"98 + 6 - (65 - 1) + 3","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(7 - 8) - 59","answer":"-60"}
{"prompt":"60 + 24","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"((80 - 8) - 5) * (3 - 1)","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"69 - 16 * 6 + 9","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"87 - (95 * 4) - 1","answer":"-294"}
{"prompt":"10 * 71","answer":"710"}
{"prompt":"19 * 25","answer":"475"}
{"prompt":"(59 * 2 + 3) + 87","answer":"208"}
{"prompt":"35 + 9 + 58 + 2","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 7) + (2 + 4)","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 10 + 6) * 91","answer":"6734"}
{"prompt":"62 - (76 + 2)","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"53 * 38","answer":"2014"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 10) * 56","answer":"5600"}
{"prompt":"15 * 3 - 6 - 32","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"61 - 68","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"66 + (99 - 1 - 2)","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"50 + 3 * 4 * 19","answer":"278"}
{"prompt":"46 - (11 + 8 * 2)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 6 * 3) - 38","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"38 + 2","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"17 * 81","answer":"1377"}
{"prompt":"(75 * 4) + 4","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"70 * 10 - 2 * 10 + 1","answer":"681"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 10) - 9 - 93","answer":"-84"}
{"prompt":"93 - 7 + 43","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"81 + 8 * 96","answer":"849"}
{"prompt":"10 * 32","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"20 - (12 - 8) + 9","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"53 + 4 * 66","answer":"317"}
{"prompt":"65 * 8 * 6 - 81","answer":"3039"}
{"prompt":"96 - 49","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"58 * 10 - 10 * 91","answer":"-330"}
{"prompt":"66 * 9 - 6 * 92","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"11 + 90","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"100 * 3 - 21","answer":"279"}
{"prompt":"((30 - 8) + 9) * 10 + 6","answer":"316"}
{"prompt":"14 + 87","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"((62 - 4) * 8) * 86","answer":"39904"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 9 - 3) - (63 - 10)","answer":"403"}
{"prompt":"92 - 5 + 6 + 5 + 4","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"49 - (54 - 1)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"61 - 9 + 39","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"6 + 25 * 3","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"(10 + 9) * (23 - 5)","answer":"342"}
{"prompt":"56 - (52 + 3)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"2 + 4 * (7 - 1 + 4)","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"5 + 9 * 1 + 21","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"31 + 54 - 9","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 8) * 87","answer":"7308"}
{"prompt":"93 - 9 + 10 * 1","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"70 - 6 + 94 + 2","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"60 - (85 + 2)","answer":"-27"}
{"prompt":"41 + 5","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"39 + 84","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"96 - (68 + 6)","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"77 * 34 - 1 - 5","answer":"2612"}
{"prompt":"61 - 87","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"17 + 10 - 79 - 9","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"18 + 12 * 10 * 3","answer":"378"}
{"prompt":"4 - 4 * 27 + 6","answer":"-98"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 3) * 6 - 98","answer":"268"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 5 + 2) * 98","answer":"2450"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 4) * 36","answer":"828"}
{"prompt":"25 * 5 * 90","answer":"11250"}
{"prompt":"44 - (15 * 5)","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 4 - 2) + 96 * 4","answer":"474"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 9 * 6) - (12 + 9) + 9","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(31 * 2 * 7) + 10","answer":"444"}
{"prompt":"61 - 51","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 3) - 2 * (47 * 4) - 2","answer":"-332"}
{"prompt":"13 + 5 * (4 - 4) + 9","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"94 + ((37 + 7) * 7)","answer":"402"}
{"prompt":"31 * 24 * 4","answer":"2976"}
{"prompt":"38 + 1 * (92 + 10)","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"15 * 2 * 39 + 9","answer":"1179"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 1) - (11 * 10 - 2)","answer":"-77"}
{"prompt":"32 + 80","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 1) * (34 - 2)","answer":"1184"}
{"prompt":"84 - (32 * 10 + 8)","answer":"-244"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 7) + (39 - 6)","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 1 * 2) - 94","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"17 * 87 - 5","answer":"1474"}
{"prompt":"(60 * 4) * 6 + 57","answer":"1497"}
{"prompt":"((15 - 7) + 3) * 57","answer":"627"}
{"prompt":"((93 * 8) + 7) - 80","answer":"671"}
{"prompt":"32 * 2 * (11 + 10 * 3)","answer":"2624"}
{"prompt":"29 * 7 * 5 * 43","answer":"43645"}
{"prompt":"47 * 53","answer":"2491"}
{"prompt":"85 * 37","answer":"3145"}
{"prompt":"42 - (52 * 9 + 10)","answer":"-436"}
{"prompt":"((44 + 4) + 8) - (77 - 8)","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"95 - ((64 + 5) * 4)","answer":"-181"}
{"prompt":"8 - 2 + 4 - 52 + 7 - 9","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"94 * 96 - 3 + 5","answer":"9026"}
{"prompt":"23 * 6 - 42","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"54 + 7 + ((93 * 2) - 6)","answer":"241"}
{"prompt":"56 + 95","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 1) - 1 * 99","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"(80 * 3) + 24","answer":"264"}
{"prompt":"39 + 34","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"7 + 1 + 34","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"73 * (20 * 6) - 9","answer":"8751"}
{"prompt":"30 + 2 - 8 * 67","answer":"-504"}
{"prompt":"9 * (68 - 9) + 8","answer":"539"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 4) + 10 * (21 + 10 - 8)","answer":"294"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 1) * (55 - 5) + 4","answer":"3004"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 1 * 6) + (16 * 5 - 9)","answer":"359"}
{"prompt":"8 + 48 + 2 - 5","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"93 + 64","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"(66 - 2) - 1 - 49 + 1","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"17 - 2","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 3 - 10) - 48 * 4 - 9","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"88 + (90 - 2)","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"43 - 1 - 72","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"46 - 9 + ((37 - 6) * 5)","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"81 * 8 * 93","answer":"60264"}
{"prompt":"42 * 42 + 6","answer":"1770"}
{"prompt":"23 * (36 - 5 + 1)","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"21 - 97 + 10","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"14 + 94","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"30 - 96","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 5) + (62 * 4 + 4)","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"44 - (40 - 9)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"58 - 63","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"75 * 34 * 3 - 8","answer":"7642"}
{"prompt":"80 * 2 * 65 + 7","answer":"10407"}
{"prompt":"98 - 72","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"17 - 2 - 10 + (59 * 10)","answer":"595"}
{"prompt":"61 + 3 - 18","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"5 * (1 - 10)","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"(100 + 7) * (48 + 6 + 2)","answer":"5992"}
{"prompt":"45 + 39","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"8 + 10","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"6 + 30","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"33 - 98 - 5","answer":"-70"}
{"prompt":"30 + 37","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 1 + 6) + 82 - 10","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"60 + 75 * 2 + 4","answer":"214"}
{"prompt":"48 - 19 + 4","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"96 + (65 + 5)","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"21 * 95","answer":"1995"}
{"prompt":"17 - 8 * 41","answer":"-311"}
{"prompt":"14 * 88","answer":"1232"}
{"prompt":"37 + (99 + 4)","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"53 * 7 - 32","answer":"339"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 3) - 95 - 9 - 7","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"40 - 73","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"57 + 82","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 4) - 75","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"40 + 4 * 75","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"33 - 63","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"76 * 74","answer":"5624"}
{"prompt":"11 + (89 * 10 - 9)","answer":"892"}
{"prompt":"36 - 6 - 60","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"42 + 72","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"95 + 6 - 2","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"(76 + 4) * 4 - 48","answer":"272"}
{"prompt":"85 - 54","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"28 - (57 + 10)","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"23 - 46","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"12 * 16","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 10) - 94","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"58 * 5 - 8 + 14 * 1 + 5","answer":"301"}
{"prompt":"(23 + 8) + 7 * 48","answer":"367"}
{"prompt":"77 + 7 + 5 + 16","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"((19 + 1) - 6) - 7 + 9","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"((84 - 6) + 10) * 6","answer":"528"}
{"prompt":"30 + 82","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"92 + (65 * 4)","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 4 * 5) - 75","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"50 - 10 - 1 * 41","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 8) + 11","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"86 * 40","answer":"3440"}
{"prompt":"34 + 19","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"95 + 10","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"89 - 10 * 99 + 7","answer":"-894"}
{"prompt":"((57 + 8) + 7) * (89 - 6 * 1)","answer":"5976"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 5) * 73","answer":"2482"}
{"prompt":"94 + (90 - 2 - 3)","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"43 + ((68 + 2) * 10)","answer":"743"}
{"prompt":"27 + 3 + 1","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"2 - 58","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"9 + (78 - 7 - 4)","answer":"76"}
{"prompt":"100 * 4 + 91","answer":"491"}
{"prompt":"35 + 42","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(45 * 7) * 34","answer":"10710"}
{"prompt":"7 + 1 * 7 * (26 + 3)","answer":"210"}
{"prompt":"((94 * 7) * 7) - 84","answer":"4522"}
{"prompt":"39 - 3 * ((50 + 10) * 10)","answer":"-1761"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 5) * 5 - 95","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"65 + 7 + (10 + 5 * 7)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 10) + 6 * (66 - 7 * 10)","answer":"276"}
{"prompt":"70 - 4 - (83 + 1) * 9","answer":"-690"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 6 * 9) * 38","answer":"-456"}
{"prompt":"24 * 1 - ((90 * 4) * 3)","answer":"-1056"}
{"prompt":"34 - 55 * 1","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"66 - (95 + 5) * 5","answer":"-434"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 5) * 2 - (87 + 2 + 9)","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"25 + 100 + 7 - 3","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"(71 + 6 + 3) + 76 * 2","answer":"232"}
{"prompt":"6 + (30 * 9)","answer":"276"}
{"prompt":"70 - 41","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"99 - (63 * 7 * 2)","answer":"-783"}
{"prompt":"31 + (79 + 1)","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"14 + 79","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 5 * 10) * 24","answer":"-312"}
{"prompt":"26 * 54","answer":"1404"}
{"prompt":"79 - (30 - 2)","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"78 + 3 * ((9 - 10) * 3)","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"13 + 85 - 6","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"(25 * 8) - 34","answer":"166"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 2) * 5 - (42 * 10) - 3","answer":"-73"}
{"prompt":"56 + 75","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"72 - 100 * 9","answer":"-828"}
{"prompt":"36 + 8 + 47","answer":"91"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 1) * 7 * (18 - 2) - 7","answer":"3801"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 5 + 1) - (91 + 3 * 3)","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"25 + (43 + 4) - 5","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"66 - 98","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"(63 * 4) + 4 - 74","answer":"182"}
{"prompt":"2 + 67 + 10","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"94 - 69 * 7","answer":"-389"}
{"prompt":"94 * 37","answer":"3478"}
{"prompt":"3 - (38 * 10)","answer":"-377"}
{"prompt":"8 + 50","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"8 - 5","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"(49 * 6) - 9 - 73","answer":"212"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 4) - (13 + 5)","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"26 - (9 + 5)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 5) - 3 * 40","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 9) * 4 - (40 + 2) * 1","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 8) * ((72 + 4) * 2)","answer":"3648"}
{"prompt":"42 + (63 + 10)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"(44 + 9) - 5 + 8","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"34 - 36","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(57 * 8 - 7) * 27","answer":"12123"}
{"prompt":"18 - 15 + 8 + 2","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"((100 + 10) - 5) + 87 + 5","answer":"197"}
{"prompt":"4 * 18 + 9","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"81 * ((98 - 4) - 7)","answer":"7047"}
{"prompt":"36 * 8 + 5 + (14 - 2)","answer":"305"}
{"prompt":"((68 * 5) * 6) * 43 * 3","answer":"263160"}
{"prompt":"(16 * 3 - 1) * 45","answer":"2115"}
{"prompt":"89 * (1 + 8 + 10)","answer":"1691"}
{"prompt":"39 * 46 * 2","answer":"3588"}
{"prompt":"46 * ((36 + 3) + 5)","answer":"2024"}
{"prompt":"67 + 2 - 2 + 38 + 9 - 10","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"20 - (88 * 5 + 7)","answer":"-427"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 7) * 6 - 56","answer":"3514"}
{"prompt":"81 - 72","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"74 + 11","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"76 * 10 * 9 * 56 - 10","answer":"383030"}
{"prompt":"(5 * 1) * 33","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"(87 - 9) + 93","answer":"171"}
{"prompt":"73 - 2 - 10 * 40","answer":"-329"}
{"prompt":"25 + 2 - (79 * 7 * 4)","answer":"-2185"}
{"prompt":"11 * ((29 + 2) + 2)","answer":"363"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 2 + 9) - 25","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"25 - (24 + 4)","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(54 + 6) + 2 * 86","answer":"232"}
{"prompt":"(83 + 1) * 43","answer":"3612"}
{"prompt":"25 - 14 + 3","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"25 - 25","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"67 * (31 - 5 + 5)","answer":"2077"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 4) - (31 * 6) * 1","answer":"-135"}
{"prompt":"60 * 7 * (78 * 8)","answer":"262080"}
{"prompt":"57 + (3 * 4)","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(83 * 2) * ((29 * 7) * 8)","answer":"269584"}
{"prompt":"51 + 61","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"83 * 10 + 9 * (6 * 2 * 1)","answer":"938"}
{"prompt":"22 - 5 + 9 + 2","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"(93 - 4 + 8) + (31 - 2)","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"(89 - 3 - 1) - 54","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 10) - 91","answer":"629"}
{"prompt":"(73 - 1) - 9 + 57","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 4) - 5","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"5 - 15","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"51 - 2 + 1 * 15","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"54 - 9 - ((84 * 9) + 2)","answer":"-713"}
{"prompt":"(21 * 3) + 85 * 5 * 3","answer":"1338"}
{"prompt":"19 + 9 * 100","answer":"919"}
{"prompt":"92 - 3 * 91","answer":"-181"}
{"prompt":"64 * 9 - 67","answer":"509"}
{"prompt":"1 - (76 + 4)","answer":"-79"}
{"prompt":"99 - ((93 * 8) + 9)","answer":"-654"}
{"prompt":"79 + 10","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 6) * 79","answer":"26544"}
{"prompt":"59 + 97","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"28 * 45","answer":"1260"}
{"prompt":"78 * 72","answer":"5616"}
{"prompt":"84 + 44","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"((13 + 9) - 1) * (19 * 3 + 4)","answer":"1281"}
{"prompt":"68 + 84 * 10","answer":"908"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 1) * 6 - (40 - 7) + 8","answer":"389"}
{"prompt":"39 * 2 * 2 - ((13 - 5) * 9)","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"42 - 57 + 9","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"36 + 10 - 7 - 5 - 2","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"((2 - 1) + 6) + (32 - 10)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"(31 + 3) - (44 * 1) * 5","answer":"-186"}
{"prompt":"19 * ((100 * 10) + 7)","answer":"19133"}
{"prompt":"71 + 6 + 71","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"(68 * 3) * 6 + (90 - 4)","answer":"1310"}
{"prompt":"2 * 42","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"69 - 20","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 4 - 6) + (13 + 5 - 8)","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"1 + 50","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((12 + 7) - 7) + (35 * 4 + 9)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"89 * 5 + 62 * 7","answer":"879"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 5) - 35 * 3 * 4","answer":"-341"}
{"prompt":"87 - 82","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"17 - ((93 + 9) * 1)","answer":"-85"}
{"prompt":"89 - 5","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(93 + 10) * 3 * 25","answer":"7725"}
{"prompt":"23 * 21 + 9","answer":"492"}
{"prompt":"33 * (17 + 3)","answer":"660"}
{"prompt":"23 + (32 + 7)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"100 * 8 - 8 * 15","answer":"680"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 4) + 8 * 97","answer":"801"}
{"prompt":"37 - 21 - 5","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 9) + 22","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 4 * 7) - 32","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"(72 - 6) - 9 - (90 + 9 + 2)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"53 - (19 - 8)","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"51 * 10 * 10 + 32 + 2 + 9","answer":"5143"}
{"prompt":"38 * 50","answer":"1900"}
{"prompt":"82 + (88 + 8 - 8)","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"99 * 81","answer":"8019"}
{"prompt":"((40 - 10) - 3) * (51 * 10) * 3","answer":"41310"}
{"prompt":"3 + 5 * 6 * 72","answer":"2163"}
{"prompt":"96 * (95 - 4)","answer":"8736"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 4) * 29","answer":"522"}
{"prompt":"(7 + 10) + (42 + 9)","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"((29 - 5) - 7) + 61","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"6 - (36 * 5) + 8","answer":"-166"}
{"prompt":"57 - 2 - 6 - 86","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(61 * 7) + 3 - 89","answer":"341"}
{"prompt":"18 * 14","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"90 - 62","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"63 * 71","answer":"4473"}
{"prompt":"16 * 68 + 2","answer":"1090"}
{"prompt":"16 - 4 - 3 - 81","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"28 + 95","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"26 + 70","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"45 + 76","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"59 * 10 - 7 - 75","answer":"508"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 6) - 9 * (27 + 7)","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"((22 - 4) * 3) + 1","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"65 - 60","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"59 - (11 - 7)","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 2) + 22","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"46 * 1 - 4 - 86","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"((35 * 5) - 1) - 77","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"17 - 89","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"(29 - 10 * 5) + 71 - 7","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"4 * 8","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 5) - 4 - 1","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 2 * 10) - 100 - 2","answer":"1418"}
{"prompt":"77 - 86 + 10 - 3","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"3 - 77","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"64 + 36","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 9) + 37","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"56 + (61 - 2)","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"37 - (36 * 2 * 2)","answer":"-107"}
{"prompt":"((92 + 2) - 10) - 39 * 6","answer":"-150"}
{"prompt":"28 * 5 * 15","answer":"2100"}
{"prompt":"65 + 42 * 4 + 7","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"68 - 4 - 65","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"86 + 42 - 10","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"19 + 33","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"56 + 4 + 11","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"10 - 1 * 8 + (16 * 6 - 9)","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"59 + 37","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"((99 - 7) + 2) * 78","answer":"7332"}
{"prompt":"37 * 1 + ((76 - 6) - 1)","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"(80 + 2) * 4","answer":"328"}
{"prompt":"93 * (12 + 2)","answer":"1302"}
{"prompt":"25 * 7 - 77","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"20 * 73","answer":"1460"}
{"prompt":"95 + 2 - 7 - 100","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(75 - 6 + 9) * 25","answer":"1950"}
{"prompt":"(34 + 6) - 21","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"53 + 77 * 5 + 8","answer":"446"}
{"prompt":"75 - 77","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 10) * 3 + 60","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"3 * (20 - 8) + 5","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"22 * (100 - 4) + 10","answer":"2122"}
{"prompt":"75 * 2","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 9) - 10 + 1","answer":"819"}
{"prompt":"56 - 37 * 5","answer":"-129"}
{"prompt":"20 * 97 * 1","answer":"1940"}
{"prompt":"36 - ((30 + 10) * 1)","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"((93 * 7) + 6) + 15","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 3) * 44","answer":"3608"}
{"prompt":"85 - ((94 * 3) * 2)","answer":"-479"}
{"prompt":"85 - 7 + 97","answer":"175"}
{"prompt":"59 * 11 * 5 * 2","answer":"6490"}
{"prompt":"63 - 76","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(12 * 6) * 49","answer":"3528"}
{"prompt":"(27 * 4) - 1 * 44 * 8 + 2","answer":"-242"}
{"prompt":"81 - 9 + 68","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"29 * 93","answer":"2697"}
{"prompt":"46 * ((36 * 8) * 9)","answer":"119232"}
{"prompt":"77 * 73","answer":"5621"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 3) + (54 * 8 * 8)","answer":"3521"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 5) + 3) - (41 - 2) + 8","answer":"262"}
{"prompt":"((24 + 8) + 1) * 97","answer":"3201"}
{"prompt":"50 - 80","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 5) + 22","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"66 - 12","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"32 + 71","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"85 - 7 - 56 * 10","answer":"-482"}
{"prompt":"63 + 84 - 8","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"22 - (10 - 2)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"92 - 85 - 4","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"34 * 13","answer":"442"}
{"prompt":"68 * 1 - 8 - 66 - 3 - 5","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(86 + 4) + (94 * 10) - 1","answer":"1029"}
{"prompt":"52 + ((26 - 2) * 10)","answer":"292"}
{"prompt":"9 + 9","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"70 - 90","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"33 * 90","answer":"2970"}
{"prompt":"35 * 2 * 10 - 99 - 2","answer":"599"}
{"prompt":"36 + 9 + 84","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"92 * 100","answer":"9200"}
{"prompt":"(93 * 10) - 58 + 7","answer":"879"}
{"prompt":"21 * 7 + 9 + 66","answer":"222"}
{"prompt":"72 + 3 + (9 - 2)","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"79 * 50 - 8","answer":"3942"}
{"prompt":"92 - 27 - 7 - 5","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"72 + 61","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"82 + (49 + 3)","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"48 - 3","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"12 - 100 * 8","answer":"-788"}
{"prompt":"16 - (33 + 9)","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"48 * 18 - 9","answer":"855"}
{"prompt":"(28 * 10) + 89 - 10","answer":"359"}
{"prompt":"13 + 9 + 100","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 2 - 8) + 76 + 10","answer":"248"}
{"prompt":"(37 * 9) - 1 + (38 - 9 - 7)","answer":"354"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((100 * 1) + 6)","answer":"-66"}
{"prompt":"(29 * 10) - 1 + 73 * 4","answer":"581"}
{"prompt":"62 * 9 * 33","answer":"18414"}
{"prompt":"((22 - 6) - 10) + 46","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"90 * 80","answer":"7200"}
{"prompt":"79 + 3 - 45","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"18 + 3 - 1 * 4","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(69 * 3) * 10 - 76","answer":"1994"}
{"prompt":"33 - 86","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"24 + (66 + 10 + 3)","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"39 + 3 * 2 * 60","answer":"399"}
{"prompt":"80 + 38","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 1) - 8 * ((43 + 9) - 8)","answer":"-306"}
{"prompt":"(25 + 5 + 9) + 66","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"8 + 8 - 8 + 42","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"95 - 2 - 75","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"39 - 57","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"43 + ((60 - 8) - 9)","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 4) - 68 - 6 * 4","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"53 * (11 * 5) * 2","answer":"5830"}
{"prompt":"89 - 72 * 6","answer":"-343"}
{"prompt":"((55 + 3) - 5) + ((60 - 7) * 10)","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"26 * (72 * 1 - 4)","answer":"1768"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 3) + 9 - 3 * 10","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"((38 - 10) * 1) + (60 - 3)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"54 + 15","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 1 * 10) + 28","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"41 * (83 + 2) * 4","answer":"13940"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 7 * 1) + (96 + 2)","answer":"595"}
{"prompt":"72 - 68 * 7 + 1","answer":"-403"}
{"prompt":"((77 - 4) * 8) - 90","answer":"494"}
{"prompt":"6 * 90","answer":"540"}
{"prompt":"70 - (63 - 8)","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(27 + 7) * 43 - 10","answer":"1452"}
{"prompt":"48 - (79 + 1) + 7","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"32 * (78 - 10 * 7)","answer":"256"}
{"prompt":"80 + 86 + 6","answer":"172"}
{"prompt":"10 - 76 * 1 - 2","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 2 - 1) + ((47 * 7) * 10)","answer":"3346"}
{"prompt":"30 * 44","answer":"1320"}
{"prompt":"((17 + 7) * 1) - 15 * 10","answer":"-126"}
{"prompt":"((99 - 4) * 7) * 90","answer":"59850"}
{"prompt":"89 + (89 * 4) * 4","answer":"1513"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 2) + 8 - 80 + 6","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"38 - (53 * 8)","answer":"-386"}
{"prompt":"14 + 84 + 7","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"70 - 2 * 88","answer":"-106"}
{"prompt":"94 - 20","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"68 - 71","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 8) - 7 - 22 + 2","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 4 * 5) * (38 - 9)","answer":"493"}
{"prompt":"(68 + 1 + 5) * ((86 * 8) + 5)","answer":"51282"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 9 - 7) + 15 * 1","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 9) * (39 + 1) * 9","answer":"-2520"}
{"prompt":"56 - 60","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"21 * 7","answer":"147"}
{"prompt":"82 - 63","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 1) * (43 * 8)","answer":"11696"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 5) - 90","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"66 + (75 * 5)","answer":"441"}
{"prompt":"100 + ((37 + 10) + 2)","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"100 + 59 + 4","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"46 * 47","answer":"2162"}
{"prompt":"97 - 35","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"87 + 15 + 2","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"39 + 91 * 1 - 7","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"91 * 24","answer":"2184"}
{"prompt":"98 + 7 + 8","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"66 + 28","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"5 + 2 + ((87 + 3) - 3)","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(66 * 4) * 4 * (12 - 10)","answer":"2112"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 1) - 75","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"39 + 9","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"((99 + 10) * 5) + (27 + 1)","answer":"573"}
{"prompt":"18 + 78","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"91 * 44","answer":"4004"}
{"prompt":"41 + 12","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"22 * (55 + 7)","answer":"1364"}
{"prompt":"51 * 65 - 4","answer":"3311"}
{"prompt":"28 * 9 + 66 * 6","answer":"648"}
{"prompt":"(89 + 3 * 1) * ((76 + 8) + 8)","answer":"8464"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 9) * 10 + (35 - 4)","answer":"7951"}
{"prompt":"92 - (13 + 2) + 9","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"55 * 4 * 3 + 41","answer":"701"}
{"prompt":"31 - 62","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"75 - (94 - 5 + 9)","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"27 + ((84 - 7) * 8)","answer":"643"}
{"prompt":"((74 * 7) * 6) * 18","answer":"55944"}
{"prompt":"81 + ((34 - 9) * 5)","answer":"206"}
{"prompt":"95 + 5 + 29","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"85 - 5 - 4 * (36 * 9)","answer":"-1216"}
{"prompt":"15 * 5","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 6) - 80","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"21 + ((100 - 9) + 5)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(88 * 5) - 77","answer":"363"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 5) - (39 - 4)","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 6) * (60 - 10) * 7","answer":"23800"}
{"prompt":"(92 + 6) * 9 + 21","answer":"903"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 6 - 3) * (44 + 5) - 10","answer":"1656"}
{"prompt":"49 + 12","answer":"61"}
{"prompt":"(40 * 10) - (32 * 10) - 10","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"((43 * 1) + 6) + 71","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"84 - 22 + 6","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 7) * 78","answer":"3354"}
{"prompt":"93 + (29 * 3)","answer":"180"}
{"prompt":"83 * 75","answer":"6225"}
{"prompt":"(33 * 2) + 4","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"(69 - 1) * 67","answer":"4556"}
{"prompt":"(62 * 5 * 8) - 15","answer":"2465"}
{"prompt":"21 * 33","answer":"693"}
{"prompt":"12 + 10 - (40 * 8 + 6)","answer":"-304"}
{"prompt":"80 * 10 - 83","answer":"717"}
{"prompt":"84 - 6 - 3 - 80","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(92 * 2) * 5 * 25","answer":"23000"}
{"prompt":"55 * 35 * 1","answer":"1925"}
{"prompt":"14 * 88","answer":"1232"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 2) - 46","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"((74 - 4) + 6) + 3","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"20 * 99 - 1","answer":"1979"}
{"prompt":"70 * (57 * 8)","answer":"31920"}
{"prompt":"22 - 72","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"(55 - 5) - 8","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"53 * 8 - 7","answer":"417"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 2) * (96 * 6)","answer":"576"}
{"prompt":"56 + 66","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"38 + 71","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"74 * 7 * (77 * 7)","answer":"279202"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 7 - 1) * 31","answer":"-186"}
{"prompt":"((83 * 3) + 6) + 8","answer":"263"}
{"prompt":"93 + 96","answer":"189"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 2) + 8) - 82","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 4) + 1 - (94 - 5) * 6","answer":"-511"}
{"prompt":"39 + 76","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"13 + 1 + 20","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"41 + (96 * 7) + 1","answer":"714"}
{"prompt":"21 * 1 * 70 * 6","answer":"8820"}
{"prompt":"55 + 6 + 93","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"36 * 67","answer":"2412"}
{"prompt":"18 + 4 - 43","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"45 * (82 - 6)","answer":"3420"}
{"prompt":"61 - 7 - 78 - 8 - 10","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"27 * (73 * 7)","answer":"13797"}
{"prompt":"(59 + 9 - 10) + (7 - 2) + 3","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 2) - 8 * 95 + 2","answer":"-715"}
{"prompt":"53 - ((50 + 1) - 3)","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"53 - 1 + 9 * 59","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 3) * 43","answer":"1462"}
{"prompt":"58 * 7","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"97 + 7 - 62","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"39 + 31","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"36 - 17","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"((78 + 10) - 1) + 45 * 5","answer":"312"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 3) * 7 * (59 + 7)","answer":"88704"}
{"prompt":"51 - 2 * 44 * 8","answer":"-653"}
{"prompt":"33 - 49","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"14 * 10","answer":"140"}
{"prompt":"42 * (49 + 10 + 3)","answer":"2604"}
{"prompt":"99 + (89 - 1) + 7","answer":"194"}
{"prompt":"79 - 30","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"36 * 9 + 4 + 54 - 5 + 8","answer":"385"}
{"prompt":"93 + 66","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"91 + 9 * 5 * 21","answer":"1036"}
{"prompt":"((44 - 3) + 6) + 1","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"32 + 4 - 48","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"83 - 40","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"82 * (15 - 10)","answer":"410"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 8) - 68 + 9","answer":"565"}
{"prompt":"87 + (14 + 10) - 3","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"10 + 10 + 8 - 2","answer":"26"}
{"prompt":"74 * 5 + 1 - 30","answer":"341"}
{"prompt":"19 + 5 - 1 - 28 - 4 * 6","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"25 + 4","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"51 - 88 * 6","answer":"-477"}
{"prompt":"93 + 24","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"66 - 76","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"((1 * 7) - 5) * 76","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"91 + (87 + 8)","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"(64 * 7) - 59","answer":"389"}
{"prompt":"(22 * 2) + 93","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"86 * 71","answer":"6106"}
{"prompt":"78 - (49 * 8)","answer":"-314"}
{"prompt":"74 - 11","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"9 - (99 * 8) * 5","answer":"-3951"}
{"prompt":"75 + 9 - (98 - 10) * 7","answer":"-532"}
{"prompt":"63 - 91","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"((72 + 1) + 1) * 51","answer":"3774"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 4) - 67","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"7 - 13","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"93 - (97 + 9 + 2)","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"(16 - 2) + 3 - 57 + 2","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"85 + 5 * 1 * (51 + 9) * 5","answer":"1585"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 6) - 12","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"88 * 4 + (49 * 4)","answer":"548"}
{"prompt":"68 * 51","answer":"3468"}
{"prompt":"68 * 6 - 64","answer":"344"}
{"prompt":"(33 + 6 + 4) * 6","answer":"258"}
{"prompt":"(49 - 4) + 9 * 28 * 2","answer":"549"}
{"prompt":"80 + ((15 * 5) + 4)","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"47 - 24","answer":"23"}
{"prompt":"9 * 37 * 10","answer":"3330"}
{"prompt":"9 - 72","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"(14 * 9) + (49 * 2)","answer":"224"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 2) + ((61 + 9) - 10)","answer":"240"}
{"prompt":"79 + 75","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"((71 - 7) * 7) * 9 * 1","answer":"4032"}
{"prompt":"(13 - 8) - 41 - 1","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"30 + (20 * 2)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"((70 * 3) * 7) + 6","answer":"1476"}
{"prompt":"1 * 62","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"63 * 50","answer":"3150"}
{"prompt":"27 * 49","answer":"1323"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 8 - 9) - 5 - 9","answer":"377"}
{"prompt":"45 * 23","answer":"1035"}
{"prompt":"36 + (43 + 10 - 9)","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 1) - (8 + 8 * 1)","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"47 - 9 - 11 - 10","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 9) * 1 + 37","answer":"730"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 8) - ((67 * 6) * 7)","answer":"-2710"}
{"prompt":"6 - (3 + 3)","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(46 - 7) * 10 - (24 * 8)","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"35 - (8 * 6) - 1","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"43 * 20","answer":"860"}
{"prompt":"50 - (32 - 2 - 10)","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"53 + 5 + 6 + 70 + 9","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 9 + 9) * 22 * 9 - 8","answer":"71272"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 1) + 78","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"23 + 34","answer":"57"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 3 * 5) + (62 * 10)","answer":"2045"}
{"prompt":"71 - (66 - 8)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"3 * (58 - 5)","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"36 * 8 - (77 - 1)","answer":"212"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 6) + 41 * 8 - 9","answer":"745"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 2) + (69 * 3 * 4)","answer":"927"}
{"prompt":"91 * 3","answer":"273"}
{"prompt":"97 + 89","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"42 - 3 * 1 - 3","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"(18 - 8) + 1 - 53","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"(69 + 4) * 72 + 4","answer":"5260"}
{"prompt":"4 - (17 + 4)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"11 + 41 - 6","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"(51 + 6 + 9) * 19 - 8","answer":"1246"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 5) - (12 - 2)","answer":"350"}
{"prompt":"37 * 36","answer":"1332"}
{"prompt":"36 + 89","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 6) * 2 * 41","answer":"6970"}
{"prompt":"16 * 16 - 5 * 9","answer":"211"}
{"prompt":"37 - (2 * 10)","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"98 + 6 * 4 * (84 + 3 * 1)","answer":"2186"}
{"prompt":"66 - 50 - 8 * 8","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"81 * 98 + 10 - 4","answer":"7944"}
{"prompt":"24 * 6 - 58","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(79 - 10) + (8 - 5) + 3","answer":"75"}
{"prompt":"45 + 19","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 10) - (73 - 3)","answer":"890"}
{"prompt":"73 - (26 + 9)","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"((78 * 9) - 8) * 2","answer":"1388"}
{"prompt":"75 * 96","answer":"7200"}
{"prompt":"31 + 40","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"70 * (81 - 3 - 10)","answer":"4760"}
{"prompt":"3 - 4 - 15","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"100 - 8","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"84 * 47","answer":"3948"}
{"prompt":"96 + (55 + 8)","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"(57 + 5) - 3 + 79","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"51 * 25","answer":"1275"}
{"prompt":"81 * 87","answer":"7047"}
{"prompt":"(37 - 6) * 90","answer":"2790"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 1 * 3) - (15 - 5 - 10)","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"48 + 100","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"44 + 6 + ((19 * 5) - 3)","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((71 * 1) * 6)","answer":"-386"}
{"prompt":"50 * 8 - 5 + 65","answer":"460"}
{"prompt":"93 - 1 + 58","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 9) * 8 + 58","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"90 * 1 * 2 * 35","answer":"6300"}
{"prompt":"100 + ((26 * 3) + 7)","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 3 - 5) * 98","answer":"9016"}
{"prompt":"(19 * 6) - 6 * 99 + 8","answer":"-472"}
{"prompt":"62 + 1","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"(79 + 4) * (70 + 6) - 2","answer":"6306"}
{"prompt":"20 + 61","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"38 - 49","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"17 + 72","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 2) * 10 - (95 * 1)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"((53 * 8) + 4) - (37 * 9 + 10)","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 1 - 3) - 83 + 10","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"62 + 21","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"27 + 9 + 10 - 93","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"92 + 1 * 70","answer":"162"}
{"prompt":"83 * 62","answer":"5146"}
{"prompt":"68 + 49 - 4","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"29 * 5 * 1 + 2 * 5","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 8 - 4) + 4","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"(14 - 8) + 4 - 17","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"44 + 5 + 3 + (59 + 3)","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"58 + (47 * 5 + 10)","answer":"303"}
{"prompt":"33 * (14 * 10) * 9","answer":"41580"}
{"prompt":"69 * 67 - 3","answer":"4620"}
{"prompt":"(85 * 9) - 38","answer":"727"}
{"prompt":"37 + (36 * 7)","answer":"289"}
{"prompt":"(21 + 8) - 6 + 4","answer":"27"}
{"prompt":"76 - (78 + 6)","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"81 - ((8 - 8) - 2)","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"(75 - 5 * 6) * 53","answer":"2385"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 9) * 22","answer":"8118"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 9 + 2) + (47 + 4)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"12 + 61 + 9","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"59 - (45 + 1)","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"71 + 7 * (70 * 8) * 4","answer":"15751"}
{"prompt":"67 - 10 - 2 + 46","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"3 - 1 - 5","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"3 - 43","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"96 - ((83 * 3) - 5)","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"56 + 6 + (79 + 7)","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"88 - (74 - 5)","answer":"19"}
{"prompt":"87 - 3 * 5 * 3 - 8","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"16 * 8 + 64","answer":"192"}
{"prompt":"((4 * 2) * 4) + (56 * 7)","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"38 - 34 * 2 * 8","answer":"-506"}
{"prompt":"70 + 81","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"((76 * 6) - 7) + ((76 - 1) * 5)","answer":"824"}
{"prompt":"35 * 7 + 89 - 1 * 10","answer":"324"}
{"prompt":"80 * 85","answer":"6800"}
{"prompt":"40 - 2","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"83 - 47","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"1 + (4 - 10)","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(37 + 6) + (76 + 9)","answer":"128"}
{"prompt":"20 * 95","answer":"1900"}
{"prompt":"(91 - 8) * 13","answer":"1079"}
{"prompt":"74 + 66 * 4","answer":"338"}
{"prompt":"58 - (98 * 8) * 6","answer":"-4646"}
{"prompt":"73 - (42 - 2) * 1","answer":"33"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 4) + 44","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"1 * 72 * 8","answer":"576"}
{"prompt":"82 - 5 * 2 + 32","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"49 + 2 - (66 + 9)","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"58 * 46 - 1","answer":"2667"}
{"prompt":"5 - (68 + 10 + 7)","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"49 + 6","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"98 + 65 - 9 - 9","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"((93 * 9) - 1) * 23","answer":"19228"}
{"prompt":"26 - 7 * 36 - 7 + 8","answer":"-225"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 8 - 5) + 52 * 9","answer":"507"}
{"prompt":"24 + 62","answer":"86"}
{"prompt":"(53 * 8 - 10) - 61","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"82 * (73 + 9) - 2","answer":"6722"}
{"prompt":"54 * 27","answer":"1458"}
{"prompt":"6 + ((21 * 7) + 8)","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 2) * 5 * 27","answer":"4050"}
{"prompt":"59 - 62","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 7) - (26 * 4) * 1","answer":"-88"}
{"prompt":"82 * 7 * (4 - 9)","answer":"-2870"}
{"prompt":"((31 + 7) * 6) * (89 - 5) - 1","answer":"19151"}
{"prompt":"88 * (93 * 3)","answer":"24552"}
{"prompt":"35 - 6 - 1 - 3","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(55 * 10) * 5 + 60","answer":"2810"}
{"prompt":"(65 * 1) - (15 * 3 * 4)","answer":"-115"}
{"prompt":"38 * (81 - 3)","answer":"2964"}
{"prompt":"95 - ((84 + 9) - 1)","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"23 + 85","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"57 + 62","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"73 + 21 * 6","answer":"199"}
{"prompt":"((72 * 2) - 6) * 41","answer":"5658"}
{"prompt":"16 - 30","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"29 * 78 - 4","answer":"2258"}
{"prompt":"67 + 3 * 93","answer":"346"}
{"prompt":"89 - 7 - (35 * 8) * 3","answer":"-758"}
{"prompt":"78 - (21 - 6)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"97 + 1 + 47","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 6) * 50","answer":"3800"}
{"prompt":"94 + 4 * 75","answer":"394"}
{"prompt":"1 + (23 - 10)","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"21 - 49","answer":"-28"}
{"prompt":"62 + (17 * 7)","answer":"181"}
{"prompt":"20 - 4 - 96","answer":"-80"}
{"prompt":"60 * 74","answer":"4440"}
{"prompt":"5 - 4 + 31","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"86 - 6 * (45 - 10)","answer":"-124"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 10) - (7 + 7)","answer":"526"}
{"prompt":"(78 + 7) + 4 - 61","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"44 + (95 * 2 * 2)","answer":"424"}
{"prompt":"34 - 3","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"47 + 85","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(70 * 8) - 37","answer":"523"}
{"prompt":"54 * 49","answer":"2646"}
{"prompt":"84 * 2 - (6 - 5)","answer":"167"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 2 * 3) * 3","answer":"234"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 9) - 23","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"45 - (79 + 8)","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"83 * (25 * 2)","answer":"4150"}
{"prompt":"11 + 5 - 10 * 3 * 7","answer":"-194"}
{"prompt":"81 - 52","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"100 - 63","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"52 * 35","answer":"1820"}
{"prompt":"(20 * 10 - 9) + (71 * 6) + 9","answer":"626"}
{"prompt":"52 + 1 * 57","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"((60 - 10) - 4) - (100 * 6 + 6)","answer":"-560"}
{"prompt":"54 + 1 * 12","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"59 + (29 * 1)","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"45 * 2 + 49","answer":"139"}
{"prompt":"30 + 6 + (35 * 5) - 4","answer":"207"}
{"prompt":"97 - 5 * 9","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"39 * 5 + ((47 * 3) + 4)","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"(7 * 5) + 27","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"(49 + 4) + 51","answer":"104"}
{"prompt":"37 * (66 + 8)","answer":"2738"}
{"prompt":"81 - 71","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"23 * 1 * 3","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 4) + 59","answer":"395"}
{"prompt":"87 + (77 + 6)","answer":"170"}
{"prompt":"((42 + 1) - 7) * 68","answer":"2448"}
{"prompt":"(52 - 4) * (1 + 6)","answer":"336"}
{"prompt":"96 + 72","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"80 * 3 + ((10 - 3) + 5)","answer":"252"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 4) - 9 - 40 + 10","answer":"15"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 2) - 7 - 77","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"69 + 86","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"86 + ((44 + 8) + 7)","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"((97 + 2) - 8) * 91 - 2 - 7","answer":"8272"}
{"prompt":"16 + 55 + 6 + 6","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"25 + 20","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"3 * 55 * 7","answer":"1155"}
{"prompt":"38 + (79 - 5 + 7)","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"3 * 82","answer":"246"}
{"prompt":"(72 + 1 + 8) + 73","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"11 - (99 * 7 - 2)","answer":"-680"}
{"prompt":"(63 + 5) * 8 + 73","answer":"617"}
{"prompt":"41 * 67","answer":"2747"}
{"prompt":"(89 * 8) - 2 - (38 + 7 - 6)","answer":"671"}
{"prompt":"44 - 84","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(24 * 1) - 8 * 88 + 6 + 5","answer":"-669"}
{"prompt":"47 * 32","answer":"1504"}
{"prompt":"(50 * 2) + ((38 * 10) + 10)","answer":"490"}
{"prompt":"3 - 7 * 8 - (50 + 7) * 10","answer":"-623"}
{"prompt":"(24 - 1 * 4) - (33 - 3 - 9)","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"77 - 37","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"((69 + 8) - 8) - 33","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"71 - (13 * 1 * 9)","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 2) + 9 - ((52 + 7) * 2)","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"41 - 17","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"77 - 39","answer":"38"}
{"prompt":"(79 + 4 * 7) + (91 * 10)","answer":"1017"}
{"prompt":"73 + 72","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"21 + 22 - 9","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"83 - 5 - ((26 - 9) - 9)","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"36 * (38 * 2 + 4)","answer":"2880"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 10) * 7 * 21","answer":"12642"}
{"prompt":"20 - 94","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"53 + (70 * 6 + 8)","answer":"481"}
{"prompt":"21 * (85 - 6)","answer":"1659"}
{"prompt":"82 + 1 - 69","answer":"14"}
{"prompt":"18 * 86","answer":"1548"}
{"prompt":"7 - 65 - 10","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1) - 5 + 88","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"13 + 7 * 10 * 6","answer":"433"}
{"prompt":"(9 - 6) + 6 - 56","answer":"-47"}
{"prompt":"26 - (5 + 9)","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"53 * 29","answer":"1537"}
{"prompt":"3 - 90","answer":"-87"}
{"prompt":"((8 - 7) + 5) * 9","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"38 * (43 - 5)","answer":"1444"}
{"prompt":"(90 + 9) - 39","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"92 + 10 * 4","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 6) + 95 + 5","answer":"604"}
{"prompt":"((52 * 5) - 4) * (78 + 9 + 1)","answer":"22528"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 2) - 59","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"((29 - 8) + 6) + 14 + 10","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"((60 + 1) * 4) * 17","answer":"4148"}
{"prompt":"3 + 93","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 3) - 71","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"44 + 98","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"52 - (20 - 2) * 7","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"80 * 3 * 21","answer":"5040"}
{"prompt":"5 * 31","answer":"155"}
{"prompt":"40 * 10 * 96","answer":"38400"}
{"prompt":"61 * 2","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"2 * (57 + 3)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"8 + 97","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"5 - 35 + 7 * 3","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"((47 + 5) * 9) + (91 + 1) * 4","answer":"836"}
{"prompt":"26 - 2 + 10 + 86 * 9","answer":"808"}
{"prompt":"71 * 10 - 89","answer":"621"}
{"prompt":"68 * 93","answer":"6324"}
{"prompt":"66 + 6","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"94 + 58","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"93 + 72 * 10","answer":"813"}
{"prompt":"56 - 7 * 44","answer":"-252"}
{"prompt":"(13 * 10) - 3 * 73 - 7","answer":"-96"}
{"prompt":"76 - 10 * 63","answer":"-554"}
{"prompt":"40 - 5 - 6 * 30 * 3","answer":"-505"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 8) - 63","answer":"609"}
{"prompt":"14 * 6 + 5 - 35","answer":"54"}
{"prompt":"48 - (25 - 8) + 9","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"57 - 96","answer":"-39"}
{"prompt":"62 + 10 - ((46 * 7) + 5)","answer":"-255"}
{"prompt":"54 - (28 - 1) * 9","answer":"-189"}
{"prompt":"54 * 43","answer":"2322"}
{"prompt":"(50 + 10 - 8) * 8 + 3","answer":"419"}
{"prompt":"(18 + 2) + 22","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"1 * 71","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"26 * 2 * 4 * (85 + 9) + 5","answer":"19557"}
{"prompt":"56 + 4 * 3 * 70 * 2","answer":"1736"}
{"prompt":"8 * 2 + 1 * (79 * 5)","answer":"411"}
{"prompt":"42 + 9","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"72 * 8 + 99","answer":"675"}
{"prompt":"(42 + 10) * 77","answer":"4004"}
{"prompt":"56 - 1","answer":"55"}
{"prompt":"40 * 21 + 7","answer":"847"}
{"prompt":"42 * (20 + 6)","answer":"1092"}
{"prompt":"(17 * 1) * 81","answer":"1377"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 1 - 7) + (63 + 10 + 8)","answer":"114"}
{"prompt":"78 - 83","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 8) + 22 - 3 + 9","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"8 * (64 * 9)","answer":"4608"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 6) * 3 - 77","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"(8 - 3 - 3) * 22","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"55 - 55","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"86 * 41","answer":"3526"}
{"prompt":"50 * 26","answer":"1300"}
{"prompt":"87 + 33","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"(67 * 4) - 10 - 1 * 8","answer":"250"}
{"prompt":"77 * 3 + 68","answer":"299"}
{"prompt":"24 - 1 + 94 + 10","answer":"127"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 7) + 10 * (85 + 5) - 9","answer":"979"}
{"prompt":"((16 + 3) - 10) * 57","answer":"513"}
{"prompt":"(26 - 3) + 23","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"34 + 73","answer":"107"}
{"prompt":"96 + (64 - 4)","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"8 - 7 * 83","answer":"-573"}
{"prompt":"49 + 5 * (86 + 5 + 5)","answer":"529"}
{"prompt":"49 - 10","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"((56 - 10) + 4) + (49 + 10)","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"51 - ((20 + 1) + 6)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"42 - 7 + 7","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"18 + 78","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 7) - 96","answer":"478"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 5) + 3 - 55","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"71 * 2 - 9","answer":"133"}
{"prompt":"60 - 80","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"((21 + 5) * 6) - 49 - 2","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"((5 * 7) + 5) + 3","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(85 - 6) + 31","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"(30 * 2) * 7 - (76 + 2 * 5)","answer":"334"}
{"prompt":"23 * 8 * 41 * 2","answer":"15088"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 9) - 2) - 85 * 9","answer":"-670"}
{"prompt":"84 + 90","answer":"174"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 3) - 69","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"82 - 8 - 4 + 95","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"86 + 22","answer":"108"}
{"prompt":"((11 * 3) + 2) * 60","answer":"2100"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 5) - 2 + (75 - 2)","answer":"167"}
{"prompt":"44 * 13","answer":"572"}
{"prompt":"54 * (66 - 2) - 9","answer":"3447"}
{"prompt":"22 + 75","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"69 * 54","answer":"3726"}
{"prompt":"2 * 3 - 97","answer":"-91"}
{"prompt":"48 * 88 * 3 + 1","answer":"12673"}
{"prompt":"(52 * 1) * 32 * 9 - 1","answer":"14975"}
{"prompt":"5 - 6","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"53 - 56","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"76 + (82 * 9)","answer":"814"}
{"prompt":"(36 * 8) + 1 * 4 + 10","answer":"302"}
{"prompt":"((21 + 4) - 8) + 82","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"29 * 5 * 4 + 32 - 9","answer":"603"}
{"prompt":"(9 + 2) + 89 + 6","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"65 * 24","answer":"1560"}
{"prompt":"7 - (14 + 10)","answer":"-17"}
{"prompt":"5 - 3 + 98","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"91 + 52","answer":"143"}
{"prompt":"4 + (85 * 10) + 1","answer":"855"}
{"prompt":"11 - 53","answer":"-42"}
{"prompt":"89 - 100 - 3","answer":"-14"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 7) + 6","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"(72 * 7) - ((37 * 5) * 4)","answer":"-236"}
{"prompt":"27 - 4 * 7","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 9) - 9 + 11 + 6","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"45 * 9 * 100","answer":"40500"}
{"prompt":"41 + 3 + (96 - 3)","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"(5 - 6 + 2) - 45","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"72 + 3 + 8 * 23","answer":"259"}
{"prompt":"(15 + 10) - 75 * 4","answer":"-275"}
{"prompt":"6 + 74","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"76 * 34","answer":"2584"}
{"prompt":"33 - 96","answer":"-63"}
{"prompt":"(91 + 6 * 1) - ((3 * 2) - 10)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"98 * (88 - 5 - 9)","answer":"7252"}
{"prompt":"17 + (35 + 10)","answer":"62"}
{"prompt":"53 - (69 + 2 + 4)","answer":"-22"}
{"prompt":"73 - 4 + 62 * 3","answer":"255"}
{"prompt":"100 - 48","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"28 - 19","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"12 - 55","answer":"-43"}
{"prompt":"((88 + 9) - 6) + ((21 * 7) + 1)","answer":"239"}
{"prompt":"(28 - 3) + 53","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"5 - (100 + 7)","answer":"-102"}
{"prompt":"68 + (99 * 4)","answer":"464"}
{"prompt":"26 - 17","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"2 - 76","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"35 * (86 + 6)","answer":"3220"}
{"prompt":"((67 * 5) * 5) - 14","answer":"1661"}
{"prompt":"3 + 67","answer":"70"}
{"prompt":"71 + 8 * ((61 - 6) + 2)","answer":"527"}
{"prompt":"5 - 12 * 1 + 4","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"22 - 62","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"2 - 9 - 4 * 4","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 9) - 9 - 95","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(32 - 10) - 2 * 68","answer":"-114"}
{"prompt":"78 - ((34 + 5) + 4)","answer":"35"}
{"prompt":"83 - ((49 + 9) + 4)","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"96 + 54 - 10 - 10","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"36 - 15 + 3","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"32 * 3 - 80","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"36 + 81","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"8 * 89 + 7","answer":"719"}
{"prompt":"17 + 6 + 10 - 90","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"((99 * 10) * 8) - 62","answer":"7858"}
{"prompt":"(59 - 4 * 6) + 100","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"58 * 87 + 1 + 9","answer":"5056"}
{"prompt":"3 - 53 - 9 - 8","answer":"-67"}
{"prompt":"53 + 26 + 6","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"85 - 100","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"((72 + 1) * 3) - 51","answer":"168"}
{"prompt":"98 * 96","answer":"9408"}
{"prompt":"2 - 85","answer":"-83"}
{"prompt":"(54 * 3) * 60 + 10 + 10","answer":"9740"}
{"prompt":"(10 * 2) - 13 * 3","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"87 + 76","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"2 * 24","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(74 + 7) * (66 + 4) + 3","answer":"5673"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 5) * 98","answer":"7350"}
{"prompt":"(61 - 1) - 94","answer":"-34"}
{"prompt":"78 + (57 + 3)","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"87 - 82","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"((90 + 1) - 2) - 69","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"25 - 6 - 75","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"(1 - 3) - 1 + 100","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"61 + 69","answer":"130"}
{"prompt":"(27 - 9) * (84 + 3 + 3)","answer":"1620"}
{"prompt":"96 + 4 - 6 * 44","answer":"-164"}
{"prompt":"76 - 52","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"((91 + 8) * 6) - 19","answer":"575"}
{"prompt":"27 * (22 + 7)","answer":"783"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 3) + 84","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"60 + (65 - 1)","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"25 + (42 - 9 * 1)","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 2 * 5) + (17 - 10)","answer":"947"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 9) * 18","answer":"1512"}
{"prompt":"(86 * 10) + (82 + 1 - 10)","answer":"933"}
{"prompt":"6 + 76","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(84 + 3) - 5 - ((41 - 2) * 4)","answer":"-74"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 4) * (14 - 6)","answer":"736"}
{"prompt":"40 - 9 - 9 - 9 - 2","answer":"11"}
{"prompt":"77 - 82","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"(28 + 3) * 8","answer":"248"}
{"prompt":"24 + (85 + 5 + 2)","answer":"116"}
{"prompt":"(52 + 4 + 2) - 95 + 6 * 5","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"48 * 17","answer":"816"}
{"prompt":"83 * 20","answer":"1660"}
{"prompt":"56 - ((79 * 7) + 7)","answer":"-504"}
{"prompt":"95 + 1 + 12 * 7 * 4","answer":"432"}
{"prompt":"47 * 7 + 51","answer":"380"}
{"prompt":"38 * 1 + (26 - 8 * 7)","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"86 + 2 * 35 * 9 - 4","answer":"712"}
{"prompt":"67 + 91","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"57 * 25 + 4 + 7","answer":"1436"}
{"prompt":"2 * (26 - 3)","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"65 * 92","answer":"5980"}
{"prompt":"(74 * 6) + 9 * 96 + 5","answer":"1313"}
{"prompt":"18 - 18 - 10","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"54 - 5 + 29","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"59 + (71 + 3 * 5)","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"89 - ((88 - 10) + 10)","answer":"1"}
{"prompt":"54 - 4 - ((54 + 1) + 3)","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"((44 - 7) * 6) - (96 + 9)","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 1) - 36","answer":"-35"}
{"prompt":"((21 - 7) * 6) + 36 - 5","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"32 - 6 - 22","answer":"4"}
{"prompt":"47 + 9 + 2","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"39 * 97 * 4","answer":"15132"}
{"prompt":"7 + 8 + 37","answer":"52"}
{"prompt":"(1 + 7) * 90","answer":"720"}
{"prompt":"39 * 34","answer":"1326"}
{"prompt":"32 + 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"15 + 9 + 17","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"6 * 49","answer":"294"}
{"prompt":"93 - 15","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"74 * 51","answer":"3774"}
{"prompt":"23 - 7 + ((35 * 3) + 5)","answer":"126"}
{"prompt":"((32 + 7) + 7) - 36","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"38 * (86 + 1 * 1)","answer":"3306"}
{"prompt":"23 - (14 * 5) - 10","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"47 + (7 + 2)","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"77 - 91 - 4 - 2","answer":"-20"}
{"prompt":"32 - 1 + 94","answer":"125"}
{"prompt":"21 * ((45 * 7) * 6)","answer":"39690"}
{"prompt":"45 + 4 * 58","answer":"277"}
{"prompt":"8 + 1 * 88 + 6 + 9","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"88 - (16 + 10) + 5","answer":"67"}
{"prompt":"4 * 5 - 92","answer":"-72"}
{"prompt":"35 - 97","answer":"-62"}
{"prompt":"13 + 85","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 2) - 3 - 16","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"93 * 97","answer":"9021"}
{"prompt":"((7 * 10) - 5) - 84","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"((74 * 10) - 1) * 73","answer":"53947"}
{"prompt":"76 * (27 + 6) + 3","answer":"2511"}
{"prompt":"24 * 78","answer":"1872"}
{"prompt":"64 + 78","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"((79 - 5) * 3) * (98 + 8)","answer":"23532"}
{"prompt":"58 + 94","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"(23 - 2) + 48","answer":"69"}
{"prompt":"100 + 87 + 10 + 5","answer":"202"}
{"prompt":"99 - 91","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 10) + 5 + 72","answer":"1017"}
{"prompt":"75 + ((12 * 9) * 8)","answer":"939"}
{"prompt":"((59 + 4) - 8) - 95","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(75 + 10) * (61 - 3) * 9","answer":"44370"}
{"prompt":"70 * 92","answer":"6440"}
{"prompt":"12 - 44","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"89 - 21 - 6 * 3","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"7 * (95 * 10)","answer":"6650"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 4) - 2 * 32","answer":"-5"}
{"prompt":"66 - 43 - 3","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"60 * 17 * 2","answer":"2040"}
{"prompt":"89 + 5 + 9 * 72","answer":"742"}
{"prompt":"70 * 41 - 8","answer":"2862"}
{"prompt":"45 * 74","answer":"3330"}
{"prompt":"97 + 6 - 10 + (12 - 4)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"72 - 1 + 3 * 25","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"(47 - 1) - 5 + 5","answer":"46"}
{"prompt":"34 + ((44 + 4) - 1)","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"72 * (99 + 10)","answer":"7848"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 3) * 2 + (32 - 4)","answer":"198"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 5) + 62 + 7","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"51 - 77","answer":"-26"}
{"prompt":"41 * 56","answer":"2296"}
{"prompt":"17 - 8 - (49 - 3)","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"77 * 34","answer":"2618"}
{"prompt":"57 - 97","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"61 + 83 * 1 + 6","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"86 * 3 * 38 + 9","answer":"9813"}
{"prompt":"56 + 16","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"45 * 7 * 3 + 18","answer":"963"}
{"prompt":"54 + 34 + 10","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"47 + 1 - 58","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"86 - 40 + 5 * 2","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"((38 + 6) * 6) * 49","answer":"12936"}
{"prompt":"(13 - 2) * (15 - 1 + 8)","answer":"242"}
{"prompt":"16 * 28","answer":"448"}
{"prompt":"88 + (50 * 10) + 5","answer":"593"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 3) + 1 + 16","answer":"113"}
{"prompt":"13 - 7 * 23","answer":"-148"}
{"prompt":"91 + 2 - 15","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"32 + 6 + 9 * 35","answer":"353"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 2 - 8) * ((73 + 7) * 10)","answer":"-1600"}
{"prompt":"26 * 15","answer":"390"}
{"prompt":"49 + 91 * 2 + 4","answer":"235"}
{"prompt":"73 + 1 - (72 - 3 + 7)","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"16 * 88","answer":"1408"}
{"prompt":"((10 + 1) - 1) - (22 * 1) - 3","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"19 * (7 - 8 - 5)","answer":"-114"}
{"prompt":"37 - 87","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"((57 - 10) - 6) - ((75 * 10) + 5)","answer":"-714"}
{"prompt":"85 - 95","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"94 * (7 + 4 * 9)","answer":"4042"}
{"prompt":"(94 - 7) + ((42 - 1) * 3)","answer":"210"}
{"prompt":"93 + (19 * 4 * 7)","answer":"625"}
{"prompt":"20 * 5 * (6 * 6) * 4","answer":"14400"}
{"prompt":"((20 * 8) - 9) - 53","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(97 + 1) + 9 * 77 * 1","answer":"791"}
{"prompt":"46 - 2 * 46","answer":"-46"}
{"prompt":"36 * 85 * 1 * 8","answer":"24480"}
{"prompt":"55 + 3 - 60","answer":"-2"}
{"prompt":"83 * 45","answer":"3735"}
{"prompt":"42 * 2 * 34","answer":"2856"}
{"prompt":"6 - 22","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"40 + (97 + 10) - 6","answer":"141"}
{"prompt":"9 - ((15 - 5) * 10)","answer":"-91"}
{"prompt":"42 - 61","answer":"-19"}
{"prompt":"74 - 7 - (55 + 6)","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"49 - (80 - 7)","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"(46 * 2) - 8 + 65","answer":"149"}
{"prompt":"20 + 2 + 72","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"(74 - 1) * 8 - 78","answer":"506"}
{"prompt":"((16 - 6) + 8) + 25","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"3 * 9 * ((21 - 6) + 3)","answer":"486"}
{"prompt":"18 * 8 - 8 + 18","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"18 + 10","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"9 - 12","answer":"-3"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 6) * 99","answer":"3267"}
{"prompt":"83 + 94","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"92 - 6 * 77","answer":"-370"}
{"prompt":"67 - 92 - 4","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"(77 * 1) + (98 + 5) + 6","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 9 * 6) + 17","answer":"611"}
{"prompt":"16 + (37 - 4)","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"31 + 6","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"31 - 6 * 4 + 3","answer":"10"}
{"prompt":"41 * (46 + 10)","answer":"2296"}
{"prompt":"55 + 95","answer":"150"}
{"prompt":"40 * 7 * 85 - 3","answer":"23797"}
{"prompt":"28 + 16","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"25 - 3 - 4 * (60 * 1) * 3","answer":"-698"}
{"prompt":"52 + ((64 * 2) * 8)","answer":"1076"}
{"prompt":"45 + 95 - 9","answer":"131"}
{"prompt":"23 + 26","answer":"49"}
{"prompt":"54 + 6 + 34 + 3","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"95 - (57 + 3) * 4","answer":"-145"}
{"prompt":"25 * 4 + (25 + 4)","answer":"129"}
{"prompt":"(35 - 1) - 50","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"96 + 45 - 3","answer":"138"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 9 + 7) * 64","answer":"2048"}
{"prompt":"14 - 8","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"96 - 76","answer":"20"}
{"prompt":"44 - 88","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"59 + 73","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"((73 - 7) + 1) + 90","answer":"157"}
{"prompt":"88 + (47 + 9)","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"(19 + 10 * 5) - 87","answer":"-18"}
{"prompt":"(32 * 5) - 5 - 16 + 1 + 4","answer":"144"}
{"prompt":"24 * 80","answer":"1920"}
{"prompt":"(22 + 10 * 8) + (21 * 7) + 6","answer":"255"}
{"prompt":"55 * 33","answer":"1815"}
{"prompt":"14 - 2 - 3 * (47 + 3)","answer":"-138"}
{"prompt":"86 * 32","answer":"2752"}
{"prompt":"55 - ((60 - 5) - 2)","answer":"2"}
{"prompt":"(70 + 7 * 5) + (60 - 5 * 9)","answer":"120"}
{"prompt":"51 - (79 * 6)","answer":"-423"}
{"prompt":"(17 + 5 - 4) + 87","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"48 + 4 - 44","answer":"8"}
{"prompt":"13 - (27 * 10) * 5","answer":"-1337"}
{"prompt":"17 - 66","answer":"-49"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 4) + 74 - 9 * 3","answer":"124"}
{"prompt":"37 * (74 * 4) + 2","answer":"10954"}
{"prompt":"43 * 47","answer":"2021"}
{"prompt":"82 - 19","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"74 - 4 + 1 * 65","answer":"135"}
{"prompt":"(11 + 7) * 65","answer":"1170"}
{"prompt":"89 * 6 + ((91 - 9) + 2)","answer":"618"}
{"prompt":"(81 * 5) - 65","answer":"340"}
{"prompt":"19 + 29","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"95 * 4 + 70","answer":"450"}
{"prompt":"((91 + 1) - 1) + 44 * 4","answer":"267"}
{"prompt":"4 - (33 - 1) + 7","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"76 - (95 + 8) - 6","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"(36 + 9) * 56","answer":"2520"}
{"prompt":"42 - 57","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"77 + 16","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"65 + 77","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"49 * 7 * 13 + 8","answer":"4467"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 10 - 1) - 28","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"85 * 24","answer":"2040"}
{"prompt":"50 + ((43 + 1) * 10)","answer":"490"}
{"prompt":"85 + 9 + 3 - 91","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"67 * 31","answer":"2077"}
{"prompt":"88 - 41","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"99 - (79 - 4)","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"9 + (71 + 1 - 2)","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"69 - 85","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"62 - 6","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"97 - 6 * 28","answer":"-71"}
{"prompt":"58 * 2 - 68","answer":"48"}
{"prompt":"(30 - 3 + 9) - 46 * 4 - 1","answer":"-149"}
{"prompt":"89 + 28","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"20 * 90 * 4","answer":"7200"}
{"prompt":"39 * 7 * 3 * 70","answer":"57330"}
{"prompt":"64 + 8","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"33 * 78","answer":"2574"}
{"prompt":"21 * 82","answer":"1722"}
{"prompt":"36 - 92 * 6","answer":"-516"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 1) - 3 + (22 - 6) + 8","answer":"25"}
{"prompt":"38 * 4 * 73 * 10 + 2","answer":"110962"}
{"prompt":"91 * 4 - 5 * (77 - 8) * 7","answer":"-2051"}
{"prompt":"47 + 8 - (100 - 1)","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"90 - 37","answer":"53"}
{"prompt":"(11 - 9 * 7) + 28","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"29 * 38","answer":"1102"}
{"prompt":"72 * 6 - 10 - (14 * 6)","answer":"338"}
{"prompt":"(94 * 8) - (14 - 4) - 2","answer":"740"}
{"prompt":"((50 + 10) - 1) - 18","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"8 - 3 - 100","answer":"-95"}
{"prompt":"60 * 37","answer":"2220"}
{"prompt":"17 + (92 + 9)","answer":"118"}
{"prompt":"21 - 7 * 2 + 67","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"51 - 21","answer":"30"}
{"prompt":"13 + (59 - 2) * 10","answer":"583"}
{"prompt":"63 - 76","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 6) * 23","answer":"11316"}
{"prompt":"((95 + 2) - 7) + 79 * 4","answer":"406"}
{"prompt":"17 - 9 - 10 * 25 - 10","answer":"-252"}
{"prompt":"10 - 75","answer":"-65"}
{"prompt":"(68 - 9) * ((93 + 4) + 1)","answer":"5782"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 7) + (90 * 1) + 3","answer":"723"}
{"prompt":"8 + 86 * 9 - 1","answer":"781"}
{"prompt":"55 - (78 * 5 - 3)","answer":"-332"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 3) * 12","answer":"132"}
{"prompt":"(4 * 8 - 8) + (41 + 3) * 5","answer":"244"}
{"prompt":"65 - 88","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"28 + 35","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"16 * 10 + 81","answer":"241"}
{"prompt":"51 * 1","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"64 + 74 * 2","answer":"212"}
{"prompt":"(43 - 4) * 1 + 72","answer":"111"}
{"prompt":"((23 - 5) - 9) - 64","answer":"-55"}
{"prompt":"22 - 5 * (57 * 5) * 4","answer":"-5678"}
{"prompt":"35 + (39 + 5) * 3","answer":"167"}
{"prompt":"65 - 6 * 3 * (81 - 8) + 1","answer":"-1248"}
{"prompt":"(42 * 1) - (5 + 10 - 7)","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"52 * 10 - 1 - 70 + 2","answer":"451"}
{"prompt":"(99 + 5) + ((88 * 9) * 9)","answer":"7232"}
{"prompt":"(67 - 8) + 4 * 26","answer":"163"}
{"prompt":"40 - ((71 * 7) + 9)","answer":"-466"}
{"prompt":"((23 * 6) * 5) - 94 + 3 + 9","answer":"608"}
{"prompt":"39 - 53 - 2","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"34 * 8 * 8 + (15 - 1 * 2)","answer":"2189"}
{"prompt":"54 * 10 + 31","answer":"571"}
{"prompt":"51 * 37 + 5","answer":"1892"}
{"prompt":"98 * 19","answer":"1862"}
{"prompt":"75 - 5 * (80 + 6) * 10","answer":"-4225"}
{"prompt":"43 - 4 * 18 - 7 - 1","answer":"-37"}
{"prompt":"(16 - 8) * 9","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"44 * ((89 + 9) - 2)","answer":"4224"}
{"prompt":"35 - 5 + (18 - 4)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"3 * 52","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"30 * (16 + 1)","answer":"510"}
{"prompt":"((51 * 10) * 5) + 37","answer":"2587"}
{"prompt":"6 + 6 - 3 - 15","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"76 * 49","answer":"3724"}
{"prompt":"39 + 9 - 92","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"43 * 3 * (22 + 4) - 8","answer":"3346"}
{"prompt":"49 + 7","answer":"56"}
{"prompt":"(64 - 4) * 9 + (85 + 8 - 7)","answer":"626"}
{"prompt":"39 - 64","answer":"-25"}
{"prompt":"26 * ((58 * 7) * 6)","answer":"63336"}
{"prompt":"81 - 1 + 56","answer":"136"}
{"prompt":"77 * 3 * 88","answer":"20328"}
{"prompt":"22 - 51 - 9","answer":"-38"}
{"prompt":"38 - 97","answer":"-59"}
{"prompt":"92 - 6 - 2 - 58 + 7 + 9","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"15 + 16 + 8","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"16 * 73","answer":"1168"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 1) - 9 * 95","answer":"-818"}
{"prompt":"86 * 100","answer":"8600"}
{"prompt":"(65 + 2 - 7) + 100","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"(98 + 6) * 57","answer":"5928"}
{"prompt":"(60 + 7) + 48","answer":"115"}
{"prompt":"26 + 95","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"29 * (83 - 1) + 1","answer":"2379"}
{"prompt":"38 * 65","answer":"2470"}
{"prompt":"(90 - 6 + 1) * 17 * 6","answer":"8670"}
{"prompt":"55 - (98 + 8 * 9)","answer":"-115"}
{"prompt":"((39 * 2) + 4) + (64 * 1 + 8)","answer":"154"}
{"prompt":"3 + 76","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"38 + 25","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"11 * 77","answer":"847"}
{"prompt":"74 - (43 - 4) - 1","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 7) * 98 + 10 - 10","answer":"8722"}
{"prompt":"75 * 6 + ((7 - 1) * 7)","answer":"492"}
{"prompt":"53 + 47","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"62 * 9 - 91","answer":"467"}
{"prompt":"(41 - 1) - 18","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"95 * 3 - 2","answer":"283"}
{"prompt":"(10 - 4) - 50","answer":"-44"}
{"prompt":"19 + 84","answer":"103"}
{"prompt":"(96 * 4) - 10 - ((97 + 8) - 8)","answer":"277"}
{"prompt":"16 + 3 + 54","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"60 * 75","answer":"4500"}
{"prompt":"(53 + 10 - 1) - ((69 - 4) * 2)","answer":"-68"}
{"prompt":"(63 - 5 * 6) + 50","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"28 - 11","answer":"17"}
{"prompt":"1 + 2","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"76 * 81","answer":"6156"}
{"prompt":"48 * (77 - 9)","answer":"3264"}
{"prompt":"64 + 17","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"51 + 8 + (68 * 1) * 6","answer":"467"}
{"prompt":"90 - (27 - 9)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"20 - 28","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"63 * 78","answer":"4914"}
{"prompt":"5 * 26 * 7","answer":"910"}
{"prompt":"((86 * 7) * 10) - (11 - 8 * 2)","answer":"6025"}
{"prompt":"39 - 92 - 3 - 5","answer":"-61"}
{"prompt":"68 * 2 + 82","answer":"218"}
{"prompt":"21 * 32","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"77 + 57","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(68 * 6 - 3) + 38 - 3","answer":"440"}
{"prompt":"71 + 10 * 3 - 20","answer":"81"}
{"prompt":"22 - 91","answer":"-69"}
{"prompt":"6 * 17","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"(42 - 5) + (34 - 3)","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"((24 * 10) * 1) - (59 * 9) * 7","answer":"-3477"}
{"prompt":"18 + 25","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"83 * 7 * 4 - ((54 - 4) + 5)","answer":"2269"}
{"prompt":"50 - 66 + 5","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"28 + 72 * 4","answer":"316"}
{"prompt":"43 - 15","answer":"28"}
{"prompt":"16 + (86 - 9)","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"(38 - 2) * (78 - 1) - 2","answer":"2770"}
{"prompt":"51 * (63 + 1)","answer":"3264"}
{"prompt":"((12 + 8) - 6) * 74","answer":"1036"}
{"prompt":"81 + 3","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"74 * ((92 * 2) * 3)","answer":"40848"}
{"prompt":"21 + 85","answer":"106"}
{"prompt":"40 + 65","answer":"105"}
{"prompt":"85 - 7 + 8 + (11 * 10) * 2","answer":"306"}
{"prompt":"4 + 98 * 8","answer":"788"}
{"prompt":"((76 + 7) - 7) - (84 + 5)","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"83 + 51 + 8","answer":"142"}
{"prompt":"(48 * 10) * 74","answer":"35520"}
{"prompt":"95 + (47 + 1) + 8","answer":"151"}
{"prompt":"41 + 96","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"2 - 26","answer":"-24"}
{"prompt":"((51 * 2) - 9) * (31 * 10 - 4)","answer":"28458"}
{"prompt":"44 + 45","answer":"89"}
{"prompt":"((86 + 1) - 5) - 79","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"((68 - 9) * 4) * 77","answer":"18172"}
{"prompt":"67 * 9 - 8 + 47","answer":"642"}
{"prompt":"(8 * 1) - 4 + 80","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"(1 * 4) + 6 + (99 - 7)","answer":"102"}
{"prompt":"46 + 46","answer":"92"}
{"prompt":"59 * 71","answer":"4189"}
{"prompt":"32 * (84 + 5)","answer":"2848"}
{"prompt":"55 + 9 + 1 * 18","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"95 + 50","answer":"145"}
{"prompt":"68 * (47 * 6) * 3","answer":"57528"}
{"prompt":"4 + 41","answer":"45"}
{"prompt":"18 + ((40 - 10) - 4)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"14 - (74 * 10)","answer":"-726"}
{"prompt":"61 + ((82 + 1) * 6)","answer":"559"}
{"prompt":"82 + 6 - 81","answer":"7"}
{"prompt":"76 * 46","answer":"3496"}
{"prompt":"69 - 81","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"98 + 9 * 3 * 89","answer":"2501"}
{"prompt":"(86 * 1) - 43","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"56 - 97","answer":"-41"}
{"prompt":"74 * ((36 + 7) + 2)","answer":"3330"}
{"prompt":"(16 + 4) * 2","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"100 - 28","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"(70 - 4) + 3 + 87","answer":"156"}
{"prompt":"98 - 4 - 2 * 56 + 1 + 10","answer":"-7"}
{"prompt":"36 - 90","answer":"-54"}
{"prompt":"(95 + 5) - 50","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"(26 * 10) + 44","answer":"304"}
{"prompt":"(24 + 9 * 3) * 68 * 9","answer":"31212"}
{"prompt":"6 + 6 + 30","answer":"42"}
{"prompt":"81 + 47 + 6","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"(38 + 8 * 2) + (15 + 10 + 4)","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"67 * 10 * 2 + 32 * 9 + 5","answer":"1633"}
{"prompt":"(56 - 7) - 99","answer":"-50"}
{"prompt":"7 + 56","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"54 * 10 * 8","answer":"4320"}
{"prompt":"35 + 7 + 8 * 7 * 8 * 1","answer":"490"}
{"prompt":"42 + 51","answer":"93"}
{"prompt":"61 - (31 + 1)","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"19 + 1 + 1","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"(82 + 1) + 7 * 77","answer":"622"}
{"prompt":"79 + 77 * 4","answer":"387"}
{"prompt":"78 + 6 - 94","answer":"-10"}
{"prompt":"(82 * 1) - 94 - 3","answer":"-15"}
{"prompt":"40 + 1 + ((43 - 4) + 7)","answer":"87"}
{"prompt":"(47 * 9) * 92 + 5 - 4","answer":"38917"}
{"prompt":"31 + 81","answer":"112"}
{"prompt":"(51 * 3) - ((99 - 10) - 8)","answer":"72"}
{"prompt":"44 + 90","answer":"134"}
{"prompt":"((16 * 4) * 3) * 42","answer":"8064"}
{"prompt":"84 + 4","answer":"88"}
{"prompt":"((7 + 7) * 9) + 97","answer":"223"}
{"prompt":"68 - ((31 + 4) * 7)","answer":"-177"}
{"prompt":"42 * 69","answer":"2898"}
{"prompt":"((54 + 5) + 6) * 43","answer":"2795"}
{"prompt":"67 * 46","answer":"3082"}
{"prompt":"53 * 71","answer":"3763"}
{"prompt":"70 - (36 - 10)","answer":"44"}
{"prompt":"72 * 9 * 23 + 2","answer":"14906"}
{"prompt":"45 - 58","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"92 * ((97 + 10) + 9)","answer":"10672"}
{"prompt":"73 - (66 - 2)","answer":"9"}
{"prompt":"48 - 10 - 50","answer":"-12"}
{"prompt":"13 * (94 + 7)","answer":"1313"}
{"prompt":"(6 - 4) * 7 - 62 * 1 - 9","answer":"-57"}
{"prompt":"55 * 34","answer":"1870"}
{"prompt":"(58 - 8 + 4) + 83","answer":"137"}
{"prompt":"((12 * 7) * 5) + 88","answer":"508"}
{"prompt":"44 + 3","answer":"47"}
{"prompt":"(95 - 9) * 3 - 98","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"95 + (71 - 6)","answer":"160"}
{"prompt":"96 - 72","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"52 - 81","answer":"-29"}
{"prompt":"29 - ((71 + 10) + 4)","answer":"-56"}
{"prompt":"35 * 23","answer":"805"}
{"prompt":"33 * 97","answer":"3201"}
{"prompt":"67 - 68","answer":"-1"}
{"prompt":"4 - 15","answer":"-11"}
{"prompt":"(8 + 10) - 4 + 51 - 4 + 3","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"91 - 8 - 26 + 9","answer":"66"}
{"prompt":"(76 * 10 - 2) + 75","answer":"833"}
{"prompt":"(23 * 5) - (80 + 1) * 7","answer":"-452"}
{"prompt":"79 - 58","answer":"21"}
{"prompt":"68 + 5 + 22 * 2","answer":"117"}
{"prompt":"(84 * 5 * 6) - 14","answer":"2506"}
{"prompt":"17 + 7","answer":"24"}
{"prompt":"21 + 11","answer":"32"}
{"prompt":"62 * 8","answer":"496"}
{"prompt":"97 + 62","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"48 * 43","answer":"2064"}
{"prompt":"(66 + 3) - 40","answer":"29"}
{"prompt":"81 - 40","answer":"41"}
{"prompt":"34 + 3 - 82 * 6","answer":"-455"}
{"prompt":"44 - 8 + 64","answer":"100"}
{"prompt":"3 - 85","answer":"-82"}
{"prompt":"47 + (3 * 10)","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"21 + 8 * 7 * 93","answer":"5229"}
{"prompt":"30 - 6 * 7 + 80","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"(58 + 4 - 10) - 2","answer":"50"}
{"prompt":"((19 * 5) - 5) + 15 + 5","answer":"110"}
{"prompt":"17 - 4 * 95","answer":"-363"}
{"prompt":"23 + 41 * 10 - 5","answer":"428"}
{"prompt":"((1 - 10) + 7) + 79","answer":"77"}
{"prompt":"(78 * 9) - 9 + (77 * 4)","answer":"1001"}
{"prompt":"((94 - 3) + 1) * (54 * 2)","answer":"9936"}
{"prompt":"54 + 4","answer":"58"}
{"prompt":"((72 + 1) - 4) + 2","answer":"71"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 4) + 69","answer":"449"}
{"prompt":"37 - 43","answer":"-6"}
{"prompt":"16 + 27","answer":"43"}
{"prompt":"(30 + 4 + 1) - 49 * 10 * 4","answer":"-1925"}
{"prompt":"(3 * 6 * 3) * 23","answer":"1242"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 8) - 29 * 6 - 3","answer":"271"}
{"prompt":"71 + 3 + ((73 - 5) + 10)","answer":"152"}
{"prompt":"(99 * 7 + 7) - 46","answer":"654"}
{"prompt":"(98 * 10) * 52","answer":"50960"}
{"prompt":"76 - 40","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"((75 - 10) * 9) - 35","answer":"550"}
{"prompt":"10 * 27","answer":"270"}
{"prompt":"35 * 76","answer":"2660"}
{"prompt":"26 * 39","answer":"1014"}
{"prompt":"91 - (18 * 10)","answer":"-89"}
{"prompt":"22 * 14","answer":"308"}
{"prompt":"42 - 9 - 1 - 65","answer":"-33"}
{"prompt":"15 + 68 - 5","answer":"78"}
{"prompt":"(65 - 9) - 28 - 8 + 2","answer":"22"}
{"prompt":"12 - 30 * 10","answer":"-288"}
{"prompt":"(18 * 5 - 4) - 7","answer":"79"}
{"prompt":"4 * 17 * 9","answer":"612"}
{"prompt":"(6 + 4) + 21","answer":"31"}
{"prompt":"68 - 10 - 4 * 15 + 7","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"(2 - 2) * 99","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"(79 * 9) + 44","answer":"755"}
{"prompt":"49 - 94","answer":"-45"}
{"prompt":"70 - 36","answer":"34"}
{"prompt":"((80 + 8) * 2) + 3","answer":"179"}
{"prompt":"((9 - 7) - 6) * 4","answer":"-16"}
{"prompt":"94 + 3","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"92 - ((83 + 7) * 6)","answer":"-448"}
{"prompt":"23 - 3 + 3 * 25 * 1","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"73 + 2 + 8","answer":"83"}
{"prompt":"24 + 13","answer":"37"}
{"prompt":"77 + (76 + 7) + 1","answer":"161"}
{"prompt":"99 - 93","answer":"6"}
{"prompt":"16 * 3 * (85 + 3)","answer":"4224"}
{"prompt":"91 - 98 - 1","answer":"-8"}
{"prompt":"14 + 53 - 7","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"((48 * 9) - 6) * 45","answer":"19170"}
{"prompt":"96 - 37 + 9","answer":"68"}
{"prompt":"87 * 3 * 7 - ((98 * 9) + 1)","answer":"944"}
{"prompt":"55 - 10 - 27","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"84 * 48 + 2","answer":"4034"}
{"prompt":"((36 - 2) + 9) * 27","answer":"1161"}
{"prompt":"25 + (84 * 6)","answer":"529"}
{"prompt":"8 * (30 + 10)","answer":"320"}
{"prompt":"67 + 3 * 51","answer":"220"}
{"prompt":"69 - 5","answer":"64"}
{"prompt":"7 - 10 - (16 + 1) - 1","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 1) + (83 * 6 - 3)","answer":"586"}
{"prompt":"(43 + 6) + 35","answer":"84"}
{"prompt":"6 - 19","answer":"-13"}
{"prompt":"(26 + 10) - 87","answer":"-51"}
{"prompt":"(95 * 7) * 4 - (14 - 3) + 5","answer":"2654"}
{"prompt":"92 - 3 - 6 + 76","answer":"159"}
{"prompt":"63 + 80 * 2","answer":"223"}
{"prompt":"((72 - 2) - 10) - 64","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"((72 * 10) - 8) * 46","answer":"32752"}
{"prompt":"(21 - 1) - (68 * 7)","answer":"-456"}
{"prompt":"9 - 6 + 3 - 15","answer":"-9"}
{"prompt":"17 - 3 * 19","answer":"-40"}
{"prompt":"(90 * 5 - 5) - (85 - 7)","answer":"367"}
{"prompt":"16 * (2 * 1) + 8","answer":"40"}
{"prompt":"(12 + 6) - 84 + 7 + 7","answer":"-52"}
{"prompt":"((72 * 10) + 4) * (31 * 7 + 5)","answer":"160728"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 5) + 3 * 45 + 4","answer":"185"}
{"prompt":"68 + 78","answer":"146"}
{"prompt":"62 + (62 * 7)","answer":"496"}
{"prompt":"(39 - 3) - 4 * 5","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"68 * 2 + 50","answer":"186"}
{"prompt":"21 - 9","answer":"12"}
{"prompt":"37 - 34","answer":"3"}
{"prompt":"26 * 9 - (81 * 7)","answer":"-333"}
{"prompt":"58 * (77 + 10)","answer":"5046"}
{"prompt":"78 * 70","answer":"5460"}
{"prompt":"4 + 5 + 10 + 55","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"1 * 3 * 74","answer":"222"}
{"prompt":"39 - 3 + 10 - 7","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"77 * (66 + 3)","answer":"5313"}
{"prompt":"100 * 3 * 1 - 37","answer":"263"}
{"prompt":"41 * (90 * 3)","answer":"11070"}
{"prompt":"86 - 90","answer":"-4"}
{"prompt":"(51 - 6) * 21","answer":"945"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 8) + 9) - 4","answer":"469"}
{"prompt":"(66 - 8 + 2) + 61","answer":"121"}
{"prompt":"16 - 5 + 9 * 87 - 5 * 3","answer":"779"}
{"prompt":"69 + 84","answer":"153"}
{"prompt":"(55 + 5) * 6","answer":"360"}
{"prompt":"6 * (60 + 8 - 2)","answer":"396"}
{"prompt":"31 + 88","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"93 + (44 * 5 * 6)","answer":"1413"}
{"prompt":"69 - (22 + 8)","answer":"39"}
{"prompt":"95 - 6 - 15","answer":"74"}
{"prompt":"(56 * 4 + 7) - (47 + 6)","answer":"178"}
{"prompt":"36 * 53","answer":"1908"}
{"prompt":"6 - 10 - 2 - ((37 * 4) - 1)","answer":"-153"}
{"prompt":"24 - 54","answer":"-30"}
{"prompt":"56 + 41","answer":"97"}
{"prompt":"14 + 1 - 46","answer":"-31"}
{"prompt":"(39 + 2) - 73","answer":"-32"}
{"prompt":"78 * 12","answer":"936"}
{"prompt":"27 - 4 + 86","answer":"109"}
{"prompt":"(41 + 7) * 14","answer":"672"}
{"prompt":"57 + 3 + (91 + 7)","answer":"158"}
{"prompt":"45 * 89 + 2","answer":"4007"}
{"prompt":"66 + 19","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"8 * 97","answer":"776"}
{"prompt":"71 + 5 + 100","answer":"176"}
{"prompt":"42 + 2 * 5 * 51","answer":"552"}
{"prompt":"(73 + 7 - 7) + (37 - 9)","answer":"101"}
{"prompt":"(20 - 6 + 10) + 95 * 7","answer":"689"}
{"prompt":"95 * 24","answer":"2280"}
{"prompt":"93 * 58 + 7","answer":"5401"}
{"prompt":"(42 + 4) + 60 + 6 + 10","answer":"122"}
{"prompt":"92 - (22 - 8) - 5","answer":"73"}
{"prompt":"(11 * 3) - 1 + 45 + 3","answer":"80"}
{"prompt":"(100 - 1) * (92 * 7)","answer":"63756"}
{"prompt":"14 * 85 * 3","answer":"3570"}
{"prompt":"55 * 50","answer":"2750"}
{"prompt":"63 + 6 + 1 * 30 * 4 + 6","answer":"195"}
{"prompt":"(96 + 8 * 4) - (93 * 10 * 5)","answer":"-4522"}
{"prompt":"69 - ((81 + 4) + 5)","answer":"-21"}
{"prompt":"(81 - 10) - (9 - 1)","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"40 * (67 * 5)","answer":"13400"}
{"prompt":"79 * 6 * 2","answer":"948"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 9 + 2) * (76 + 1)","answer":"6853"}
{"prompt":"31 * 94","answer":"2914"}
{"prompt":"67 + 3 - 57","answer":"13"}
{"prompt":"(39 * 2) + 45","answer":"123"}
{"prompt":"77 + 2 * 21","answer":"119"}
{"prompt":"13 * 27","answer":"351"}
{"prompt":"(14 + 10) * (40 + 3) + 4","answer":"1036"}
{"prompt":"13 + 82","answer":"95"}
{"prompt":"13 * 10 - 51 * 3","answer":"-23"}
{"prompt":"44 - 8","answer":"36"}
{"prompt":"23 + 75","answer":"98"}
{"prompt":"(92 - 9 * 4) + 3 + 4","answer":"63"}
{"prompt":"63 - (60 - 10 - 3)","answer":"16"}
{"prompt":"36 - 84","answer":"-48"}
{"prompt":"45 + 6","answer":"51"}
{"prompt":"(66 - 3) * 8 - (45 * 6 * 4)","answer":"-576"}
{"prompt":"((36 + 8) + 6) * 34 + 2","answer":"1702"}
{"prompt":"29 + 53","answer":"82"}
{"prompt":"(71 * 7) + 3 - 70 + 3","answer":"433"}
{"prompt":"44 * (21 * 1 * 9)","answer":"8316"}
{"prompt":"17 * 33 + 2","answer":"563"}
{"prompt":"(50 - 2) - 54 * 6","answer":"-276"}
{"prompt":"25 + (93 * 10) + 3","answer":"958"}
{"prompt":"99 * (8 - 10) * 6","answer":"-1188"}
{"prompt":"71 * 27","answer":"1917"}
{"prompt":"57 + 21 * 8","answer":"225"}
{"prompt":"46 - 28","answer":"18"}
{"prompt":"58 * 13","answer":"754"}
{"prompt":"((10 * 3) * 9) + (82 - 10 + 10)","answer":"352"}
{"prompt":"94 + 71","answer":"165"}
{"prompt":"26 + 97 - 9 * 7","answer":"60"}
{"prompt":"81 + 6 + 8 * 27","answer":"303"}
{"prompt":"40 + 45","answer":"85"}
{"prompt":"((37 + 3) - 5) + 28 + 9 * 4","answer":"99"}
{"prompt":"((36 - 5) - 8) * 100","answer":"2300"}
{"prompt":"90 * 3 + 7 - 100","answer":"177"}
{"prompt":"13 - (30 * 7)","answer":"-197"}
{"prompt":"(41 * 8) + 9","answer":"337"}
{"prompt":"72 * 89","answer":"6408"}
{"prompt":"23 - 2 - 9 - 7","answer":"5"}
{"prompt":"30 - 30","answer":"0"}
{"prompt":"((58 * 10) + 4) * 37 * 5","answer":"108040"}
{"prompt":"(96 - 10) * 44","answer":"3784"}
{"prompt":"4 * 50","answer":"200"}
{"prompt":"84 + 10 + 2","answer":"96"}
{"prompt":"72 * 67","answer":"4824"}
{"prompt":"3 - (87 * 8)","answer":"-693"}
{"prompt":"88 + (57 + 3)","answer":"148"}
{"prompt":"(3 - 3) - 53","answer":"-53"}
{"prompt":"7 - 2 + 89","answer":"94"}
{"prompt":"((34 + 1) * 7) + 2","answer":"247"}
{"prompt":"98 * 13","answer":"1274"}
{"prompt":"92 + 4 - 3 * 45 * 6","answer":"-714"}
{"prompt":"55 * 10 - 1 - (100 + 8)","answer":"441"}
{"prompt":"21 + 2 + 4 + (80 * 8) - 5","answer":"662"}
